<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bell-Bones on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/bell-bones/</link><description>Recent content in Bell-Bones on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/bell-bones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part of Your World</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Waaaa, week 17,,, it&amp;rsquo;s here,, and I actually come with a piece of quality (thanks to the extensions lmao). This piece was inspired by @Linalifox&amp;rsquo;s submission for week 4, titled &amp;ldquo;Blue&amp;rdquo;. Their piece reminded me of mermaids, which reminded me of The Little Mermaid and my merman AU that I have for Backey,,, so I drew him and took the pose from the &amp;ldquo;Part of Your World&amp;rdquo; scene in The Little Mermaid.</description></item><item><title>oof</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This isn&amp;rsquo;t up to the usual quality of what I make, but I wanted to do something simple since I&amp;rsquo;ve felt so overwhelmed lately. Gotta love growing up and facing the crushing weight of your new responsibilities am I right? I&amp;rsquo;ll at least try to make something good for week 17 =3= (also if you want some &amp;ldquo;giant thing next to a small thing&amp;rdquo; art that&amp;rsquo;s of actual quality, go look at my submission for week 2 lol)</description></item><item><title>sometimes art is not worth having a mental breakdown over</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So&amp;hellip; I was late for once. Annnd this wasn&amp;rsquo;t even what I was working on, this is just that same warm up I posted a while back. I probably should&amp;rsquo;ve just posted this last week so I could avoid falling into a depression after crumbling under the pressure, but&amp;hellip; it wasn&amp;rsquo;t polished, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want my work on the other piece to go to waste.</description></item><item><title>That's gotta hurt</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re a monster, a loon. Everybody wants you dead, including me.&amp;rdquo; Oops, more angst! This is just a nightmare Astro has though, Backey never actually says this lol. Decided to use purposely messy lineart in this piece, I think it looks pretty decent! Astro just needs to stop snooping around in places he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; Backey doesn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate him reading his journal.</description></item><item><title>OMORI AU</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-13-335d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-13-335d/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I was gonna finish on time, but I managed to get these done! I finished watching a let&amp;rsquo;s play of OMORI recently, and it was wonderful experience&amp;hellip; I felt inspired to draw little battle portraits of my OCs in the game&amp;rsquo;s style! Was gonna draw their real world counterparts, but I&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t have the time nor energy.</description></item><item><title>Exhaustion</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-12-62d1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-12-62d1/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was going to do something cuter this week and make a lovecore aesthetic piece, buuuut I&amp;rsquo;ve just been,, so tired lately. Mom&amp;rsquo;s been keeping me up until 2 am all week for reasons so I haven&amp;rsquo;t been getting more than 5 hours of sleep per day&amp;hellip; so I decided to convey that through handwritten lettering.</description></item><item><title>Aster Flower Looking Upon a Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Kinda been stressed this week, but I managed to squeeze this piece out. Sketchier lineart than usual because it&amp;rsquo;s literally a sketch that&amp;rsquo;s cleaned up a bit lol, I&amp;rsquo;m tired and need to study for a test :p
Also check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; for a sketch done by DynoLoafer that&amp;rsquo;s basically what the guy looks like from the front lol</description></item><item><title>Prince Backey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, so,, I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like shading, but partially colored lines are cool, right? Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s an AU version of Backey where he&amp;rsquo;s a prince in a fantasy setting! Figured that an experiment with his design was long overdue lol, people can check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; to see his og outfit
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Introspection</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Did something more simple this week since I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling a little burned out. I wanted to do something cooler for this week cuz I liked the prompt buuuut I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t. Either way, this piece was partially inspired by Omori&amp;rsquo;s art style, hope people like it lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Brooke Rivers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wow! This was stressful! The time limit and outside stressors made this a particularly bad drawing experience, buuut I did finish this at the very least. There are things about it I would&amp;rsquo;ve added or changed if I had the time, but I obviously had to rush, so&amp;hellip; oh well.
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Hey you! Yeah, up here!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-7b4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-7b4a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I didn&amp;rsquo;t really get to post many wips for this piece because Discord decided it was too unholy to be seen before it was fully developed, but here it is! Did a screenshot redraw of a place called Scorched Gorge, which a desert area in Bugsnax :3</description></item><item><title>Roleplay! (and a puppet show I suppose)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes After a lot of thinking about the prompt, I&amp;rsquo;d say that I love to roleplay! Dyno and I rp all the time, so I drew us performing a puppet show! Just to give you an idea, there are 723,445 words across all our rp transcripts including ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t finished lmao
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Need a Hand?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Finally, something not last minute! I decided to be experimental, doing a lineless piece to try and draw something more simple to avoid deadline anxiety. The hand was originally supposed to look like stone, but it looks more like a bush&amp;hellip; so I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a bush now lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Family Portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had the idea to do a cute wild west family portrait featuring the gays(tm) and their daughter, so I went with it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to spend as much time on this as I wanted to, but I&amp;rsquo;m still happy with it (also here&amp;rsquo;s a non-monochrome version lol)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>A Shining Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-3-4fca/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-3-4fca/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sooo, week 3, huh? Due to school and my personal life, this came out rather rushed&amp;hellip; However, I still like the character design I came up with! The background was inspired by a certain rhythm game, kudos to you if you know the one I&amp;rsquo;m talking about ;p
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Hello there!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-16df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-16df/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, ok, I see your tiny human and large creature entries, but I raise you this,,, large human and tiny creature! But in all seriousness, whaaat, I&amp;rsquo;ve drawn something that isn&amp;rsquo;t just a character standing in a void? Shocking! I really challenged myself lol, hope I&amp;rsquo;ll continue to improve :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Honey, I'm Home!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw my oc in a dress, so I drew him in a dress! He likes wearing dresses from time to time. The sketchy plants in the bg are mostly to fill the space, but I thought they would look nice :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>