<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 16: Scaling Giants on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-16-scaling-giants/</link><description>Recent content in Week 16: Scaling Giants on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-16-scaling-giants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dynames</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-16-aea7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-16-aea7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photography + free photo edit thing again lmao.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Gundam Dynames with Lockon Stratos as pilot. idk lol
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Dynames Medium: Photography + free photo edit thing again lmao Description: Gundam Dynames with Lockon Stratos as pilot.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: At A Time Like This, Will Someone Be There For You?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-dcab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-dcab/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My first attempt at digital painting! Meh results, I think.
I tried to recreate this scenery of the Taal Volcano Island in Tagaytay, a popular tourist destination south of Manila, along a steep access road that we crossed during an official business trip where a teammate and I were doing ocular inspections of venues from the recently-concluded 30th Southeast Asian Games.</description></item><item><title>Big Skeleton</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-16-64e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-16-64e9/</guid><description> Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Almost forgot to submit :I
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Big Skeleton Medium: Pencils Description: Almost forgot to submit :I</description></item><item><title>Broccaiju</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Godzilla v Kong cut content. Actually though, heavily inspired by an old PS2 game called War of the Monsters that is a Kaiju-filled beat-em-up.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Broccaiju Medium: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT Description: Godzilla v Kong cut content.</description></item><item><title>d'Eggfsg</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw big egg. Smol soldier. In combination, they make a pretty striking pair. I&amp;rsquo;ve been having really out of the world dreams lately, and some of them feel like Neil Gaiman stories, but them sometimes they feel like this piece. It&amp;rsquo;s both familiar and not, something that we&amp;rsquo;ve all been feeling after being stuck inside for so long.</description></item><item><title>Dobby and me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is how I feel everytime I hug my cat. He is a giant things to my heart! Yeah sometimes I wanted to be smaller just to cuddle with him 🥰✨💜
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Guardian</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-16-25d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-16-25d6/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A giant golem accompanies and provides shade to desert travellers
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week 16** **Title:** Guardian **Medium:** Paint Tool SAI **Description:** A giant golem accompanies and provides shade to desert travellers **Socials:** Scimister on twitch!</description></item><item><title>It'sssss Smelbourne!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling nostalgic for blue skies and pub crawls in the city. Here&amp;rsquo;s a shot from 2017 from a bar verandah, now ssssswarming with ssssssnakes. Taking it easy on the wrist still, but I had enough in me to make this!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>oof</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This isn&amp;rsquo;t up to the usual quality of what I make, but I wanted to do something simple since I&amp;rsquo;ve felt so overwhelmed lately. Gotta love growing up and facing the crushing weight of your new responsibilities am I right? I&amp;rsquo;ll at least try to make something good for week 17 =3= (also if you want some &amp;ldquo;giant thing next to a small thing&amp;rdquo; art that&amp;rsquo;s of actual quality, go look at my submission for week 2 lol)</description></item><item><title>ooh shit</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes hey you should read kaiju no.8 its really good and big things are really cool!!! im sad i couldnt show the whole process on my stream but here it is! is it creepy yet??
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitter: cindrytuna Twitch: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Pain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-16-1985/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-16-1985/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud.
Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live Studio 11.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was going to write a 5 minute epic rock opera piece with lots of contrasts, fun guitar parts, etc, but life made it impossible. When life gives you lemons&amp;hellip;
Link:
Soundcloud: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/pain-2021-design-refresh
YT: http://papapastry.io/youtube
Spotify: http://papapastry.io/spotify
Social Media Twitter: papapastry_ Twitch: papapastry Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Rat Race</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Graphite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The idiom is defined as &amp;ldquo;an endless, self-defeating, or pointless pursuit&amp;hellip;The term is commonly associated with an exhausting, repetitive lifestyle that leaves no time for relaxation or enjoyment.&amp;quot;(thanks wikipedia) The concept was initially sketched out two years ago, but quickly shelved after major life events and and work affected my ability to put effort into it.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Fineliner 0.05 mm yay.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not cleaning my submission up today ;_; seriously sorry please make do
It&amp;rsquo;s treefolk migration season, and for woodland folk daring to climb them it&amp;rsquo;s prime time to gather food from up there.
Guys, guys, just sitting down putting in lines here and there where you feel like it is so much fun.</description></item><item><title>Mechanics love their jobs sometimes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Krita (still mouse).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t be deceived, the Blue Amazon is a killing machine. Although these robots are programmed to try to act human, they are infact very much controlled by their masters (at least that is what the master thinks). If you think you are in ara ara distance, you are in fact in danger.</description></item><item><title>Ozymandias</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</guid><description>View on Webtoons.
Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So this is an idea have had since week 7, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to pull it off and also had too many ideas for that week. However I honestly think it fits with this week&amp;rsquo;s theme better 😛 So this is based off the poem &amp;ldquo;Ozymandias&amp;rdquo; by Percy Bysshe Shelley.</description></item><item><title>The ~~Diving~~ Maternal Legendary</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (a small TW for alcohol and drug abuse) I decided to draw not my most favorite pokemon for this week, but the pokemon I respect* the most. Lugia&amp;rsquo;s past is quite depressing. The creator of Lugia, Takeshi Shudo, heavily relied on alcohol, pills and even *tranquilizers* to get his mind in the workspace, which sadly isn&amp;rsquo;t an uncommon practice with creators.</description></item><item><title>A Titan's Journey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art? 🤔
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 16 Title: A Titan&amp;#39;s Journey Medium: Clip Studio Description: To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art?</description></item><item><title>It's acting weird!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-16-fc95/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-16-fc95/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Mola mola with a few babies. They&amp;rsquo;re actually way smaller than this in scale but I have to make them visible!
lithiumreflections (IG/tumblr), lireflections (twitter)
Social Media Twitter: jaimeskelton Tumblr: lithiumreflections Instagram: lithiumreflections Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 **Title: ** It&amp;#39;s acting weird!</description></item><item><title>what is bigger, a giant bidoof or an individual's life?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes subject matters of artists like Edward Hopper tends to place equal weight for the furniture and the human matter, for example, the parallelism of the shapes of his human subject and non-human subjects, the compositions as well. Edward Hopper has invoked thought within his audience, how important is life? Are our lives just as unimportant than the furniture we buy?</description></item></channel></rss>