<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 10: Folds and Folds on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-10-folds-and-folds/</link><description>Recent content in Week 10: Folds and Folds on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-10-folds-and-folds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>silk</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/gianhet-week-10-5339/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/gianhet-week-10-5339/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: : CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes : /
rushed this one a bit lmao
Social Media Instagram: gianhet Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week 10 : title : silk medium : CSP socials : https://www.instagram.com/gianhet/ rushed this one a bit lmao</description></item><item><title>Boroboro Bobbin pants (ngl i literally almost called these boroboro bobbin bottoms LUL)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Fabric / fashion (upcycled fabric, screenprinting, and sewing).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ボロボロ (&amp;ldquo;boroboro&amp;rdquo;) often refers to an item that is worn out to the point where it is in tatters. Rather than throw it out, I find it can be a very personal and relaxing process to repair it, following similar Japanese repairing idealogy where the fix / mend also becomes a point of beauty.</description></item><item><title>Good Clothes</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-10-9303/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-10-9303/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one speaks for itself.
YouTube: YouTube External Link Spotify (latest release): Spotify External Link Apple Music (latest release): Apple External Link Link: YouTube External Link Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Implied emotion??</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Illustrator and CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Trying out gradient maps for the first time!! wow it&amp;rsquo;s super cool and colours are fresh! kinda want it to hold some sort of emotion in the fabric, what do you think?
shop.fiveclawd.com LOL
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them.</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 10: Title: Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them. Medium: Photoshop Social: https://www.twitch.tv/soleilboo</description></item><item><title>Pico's Target</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol' Pico from Pico&amp;rsquo;s School and Friday Night Funkin'. He&amp;rsquo;s a good edgy boy.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Medium: Paint Tool SAI Title: __Pico&amp;#39;s Target__ Description: Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol&amp;#39; Pico from Pico&amp;#39;s School and Friday Night Funkin&amp;#39;.</description></item><item><title>Portrait 6: Get Together</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker on paper, 9x12in.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Drew this earlier at the office since our room didn&amp;rsquo;t have internet since yesterday afternoon. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t think of anything nice, but this came to mind soon enough.
The dance is called &amp;ldquo;tinikling,&amp;rdquo; where a couple dances between two bamboo poles being clapped to the musical beat. It is somewhat similar to a waltz and a mazurka.</description></item><item><title>Prince Backey</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, so,, I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like shading, but partially colored lines are cool, right? Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s an AU version of Backey where he&amp;rsquo;s a prince in a fantasy setting! Figured that an experiment with his design was long overdue lol, people can check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; to see his og outfit
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Sunset Vibes, aka it was 30° degrees today</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes GUESS WHOES FIVECLAWD MERCH ARRIVED TODAY!!!! #notsponseredjustexcited
Thought I&amp;rsquo;d draw last week&amp;rsquo;s CMYK Dragon jacket and pair it with the Perseverance shirt cause who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want double dragons?
Bit of a quick one today cause running out of time. Yes, I did use a photo of my shirt for the shirt. No, I am not copy Cindy&amp;rsquo;s dragoon by hand, how much time do you think I have!</description></item><item><title>textile grook</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, used 5 min
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: textile grook Medium: ibispaint x Description: Sorry, used 5 min Social Media: https://www.twitch.tv/cup_o_rice</description></item><item><title>The dread beach bum La Verne</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one got away from me a bit. I intended to do something simple, I really did. All I really wanted to do was do some stronger posing than usual. I hope this fits within the prompt for this week, shes wearing clothes lmao&amp;hellip;
Anyway here is my dnd character Joselynn La Verne being no more dramatic than usual</description></item><item><title>cute outfits</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/phoebecreates-week-10-678c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/phoebecreates-week-10-678c/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: ink and watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is the beginning of my 100 outfits challenge. Yes I&amp;rsquo;m planning to do 100 of them. Ambitious? Maybe&amp;hellip;
Social Media Twitch: phoebecreates Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: cute outfits Medium: ink and watercolour Description: This is the beginning of my 100 outfits challenge.</description></item><item><title>Harlem '33/'83</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-10-f4b3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-10-f4b3/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Colored Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Harlem &amp;#39;33/&amp;#39;83 Medium: Colored Pencils Description: ? (Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!</description></item><item><title>Zelda Study</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-10-04b4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-10-04b4/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: CSP with Basic Brushes.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Cindy said I was allowed. But also, I really admire the character designs in Breath Of The Wild.
Social Media Twitch: hadespsd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Zelda Study Medium: CSP with Basic Brushes Description: Cindy said I was allowed.</description></item><item><title>Folds</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-10-66bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-10-66bc/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Edgy Basket Baller
Social Media Twitch: lyfeu Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Folds Medium: Photoshop Description: Edgy Basket Baller Social Media: www.twitch.com/lyfeu</description></item><item><title>Pulling Back From The Edge</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-10-1944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-10-1944/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Study of movement and clothing from an incredible performance by Kai during a Freestyle Roulette (link with timestamp cause y&amp;rsquo;all should watch this performance anyway YouTube External Link ) - this moment was so emotive I just felt pulled to paint it in particular. Clothing and hoomans are not my forte.</description></item><item><title>Sitting</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-10-d23d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-10-d23d/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes just a simple qurl wearing street style. uhhh lines/colouring isn’t super clean and I didn’t add shading but I like it as is tbh.
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Sitting Medium: Procreate Description: just a simple qurl wearing street style.</description></item><item><title>The Bat Man</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: The Bat Man Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick</description></item><item><title>Apple 16</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Apple.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This apple has weird fashion.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Apple 16 Medium: Apple Description: This apple has weird fashion. Social Media: https://www.instagram.com/jumpingbeansz/; https://www.twitch.tv/jumpingbeansz ;</description></item><item><title>Folds</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Folds Medium: Clip Studio Description: Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵</description></item></channel></rss>