<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kami on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/kami/</link><description>Recent content in Kami on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/kami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Everlasting Hope</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night. Why is it called Everlasting Hope? well, that&amp;rsquo;s just something i need in life i guess. hope you enjoyed it!
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6 Title: Everlasting Hope Medium: Photoshop Description: I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night.</description></item><item><title>The Vessel</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is my first time using photoshop for art, i tried making the short sword the centre piece of the piece, and i think the eyes make it pop. Hope people realise this is Itadori Yuuji from Jujutsu Kaisen
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Practice</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil , sketch pens.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is a martial arts style from India called Kalari, it&amp;rsquo;s really aggressive and involves lots of movement. I tried gesture drawing for the first time, so i guess not bad?
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Shine No Shogun</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-3-a911/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-3-a911/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Shogun of Death is a character ive been working on for a while ( i say working, its an idea in my head). Shoguns are really cool and ive been wanting to draw one so i did. The Shoguns were generals, and the shogun of death leads the army of the dead alongside his opposite, the Shogun of Light (more on that later)</description></item></channel></rss>