<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WellCookedEgg on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/artists/wellcookedegg/</link><description>Recent content in WellCookedEgg on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/artists/wellcookedegg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fusion Flare</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d try drawing them for fun :)
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 13 Title: 😳 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I drew my OC because I like her :) Week 14 Title: Fusion Flare Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;#39;d try drawing them for fun :)</description></item><item><title>😳</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-13-d1bc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-13-d1bc/</guid><description> Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I drew my OC because I like her :)
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 13 Title: 😳 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I drew my OC because I like her :) Week 14 Title: Fusion Flare Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;#39;d try drawing them for fun :)</description></item><item><title>Letter from her</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-12-bfe9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-12-bfe9/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I am not a huge fan of typography so this is my first crack at it. It was ok, maybe not my favorite lol. Though it was a good exercise for sure.
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 12 Title: Letter from her Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I am not a huge fan of typography so this is my first crack at it.</description></item><item><title>Laputa</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pressed enter before I put stuff by accident lol
&amp;ldquo;Castle in the Sky&amp;rdquo; is one of my favorite movies of all time, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d draw something inspired by it. The castle&amp;rsquo;s name is Laputa, so I named the piece accordingly.
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>The Bat Man</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: The Bat Man Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick</description></item></channel></rss>