<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 08: High Sheen on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-08-high-sheen/</link><description>Recent content in Week 08: High Sheen on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-08-high-sheen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-8-911a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-8-911a/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hi im doing this piece while you’re going through the submissions =SPEED RUn= i missed the actual stream but metal goes brrrrrr :)
it’s a life study for the blueberries im eating rn while watching u. I want to work with more bold shapes. 21 minutes)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Amalagamation: Vague Memory</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Adobe Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is probably the laziest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, lol. I had other ideas in mind, but I junked them since I can&amp;rsquo;t pull it off.
Social Media Instagram: and Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Angels in our Atmosphere</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing collage my dudes. From brainstorm to submission with was about 75 minutes. The prompt had me thinking about metal in art, so i drew images from photography (silver bromide development) to lithography/etching (metal plate prints) to digital art (like&amp;hellip; computers and stuff). The birds are just to cover her nipples</description></item><item><title>Brooke Rivers</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wow! This was stressful! The time limit and outside stressors made this a particularly bad drawing experience, buuut I did finish this at the very least. There are things about it I would&amp;rsquo;ve added or changed if I had the time, but I obviously had to rush, so&amp;hellip; oh well.
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Fixation</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A visual ode to my need for repetitious tasks and the nonsensical thoughts that pass through my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m half asleep. I love focusing on the materiality of objects and photos, so I focused on using just pieces of the photo to construct an abstract image and let it tell its own story.</description></item><item><title>Foish</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: graphic, Illustrator.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now? i love him&amp;rsquo;st tho hehehe practiced some illustrator too
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 **Title: Foish** Medium: graphic, Illustrator Description: Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now?</description></item><item><title>Just a couple of Daft Punks</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt image immediately made me think of a vinyl record so I was thinking of doing something with Daft Punk as soon as I read the prompt. I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty big fan of theirs and was disappointed to hear that they were splitting up. But boy do they have a metal sheen.</description></item><item><title>Out of Touch Tuesday</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I saw the swirl of the image and straight away wanted to do something kind of surreal but still quick and readable. I won&amp;rsquo;t lie, this probably took a bit over the 2 hour time limit, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a brainstorming session so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna count it as a work hour. Also I got the day wrong but shhh that adds to the out of touch-ness.</description></item><item><title>Swim for the Ball</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-8-f7d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-8-f7d9/</guid><description> Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: Swim for the Ball Medium: Pencil on Paper Description: Don&amp;#39;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen</description></item><item><title>The Herald</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TWO HOURS! incoherent eldritch screeching
Firstly: WHY!!!
Secondly: I would like the record to show that I did in fact completely this piece within the two hours (brainstorming included)
So for this I figured we&amp;rsquo;d go back to &amp;ldquo;basics&amp;rdquo; and hop on board the spoopy train. Since the og pics were from a church, I started thinking along the line of angels, creepy angels&amp;hellip; then got inspired by Peter Mohrbacher&amp;rsquo;s angel paintings and ended up with a Dark Souls boss 🤷‍♀️</description></item><item><title>Wall- E fan Art</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so as soon as I look at the photo the light caught my eyes immediately. I have been thinking about Wall-E a lot this week because of Do-E, and then I saw Jump in the bin submission which is &amp;ldquo;trashbin&amp;rdquo; and then my brain just blink and connect everything together&amp;hellip;.Here we go, my boy Wall-E using the photo supplied.</description></item><item><title>Jupiter Falling</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-8-bf02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-8-bf02/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Really just leaned into the original photograph, only removing the outer rim and clone stamping out some of the edge punctures. Took visual inspiration from the recent NASA/Juno pictures of Jupiter, just played with colors and swirls.
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>One Drug Please</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-8-0c0e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-8-0c0e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Alternative title: playing around with Live 11&amp;rsquo;s new cool features.
&amp;ldquo;High Sheen&amp;rdquo; reminds me of a few things. Getting high (on life) in a club, shiny lights from the sun and from stage lights, bright, natural naive feelings. &amp;ldquo;Sheen&amp;rdquo; of youth, so to speak, and stuff I have nearly no experience with at all.</description></item><item><title>1:43:51 (PB)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Oil sticks &amp;amp; oil crayons + some paper cutout.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Printed out the prompt&amp;rsquo;s image - turns out I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any black ink, just color so it looked .. yeah. Took a different approach on each of the two canvas. Finally, after painting was done, I cut out some parts of the prompt image from the paper and just sort of slapped it on.</description></item><item><title>Pretty, Ain't It?</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Someone had a mighty fine belt-buckle, so I.. borrowed it.&amp;rdquo;
This was a very interesting challenge! Decided to go for a painting-like piece with the belt-buckle being the main focus! If it&amp;rsquo;s hard to see, the texture from the resource is on the belt buckle! I timed myself and I had 7 minutes before the two hour mark!</description></item><item><title>Spicy Tuna</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional art. Copic markers and pens, gell pen..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Spicy Tuna
A delicious Japanese meal for lunch - a bowl of spicy tuna and rice with chopped onion garnish, along with a cup of maccha.
I applied the photo texture to the maccha cup, the rice bowl, and the ground tuna. I drew in gel pen white on the cup and bowl surfaces to simulate ceramic gloss.</description></item><item><title>felled tree</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes only used the picture and the colors of the picture. Plus the little tree dawing I made and a leaf brush. Forgot to stay metallic
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: felled tree Medium: ibispaint x Description: only used the picture and the colors of the picture.</description></item><item><title>High Sheen from Jimmy Neutron</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-8-41d3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-8-41d3/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Woman in armour&amp;hellip; high sheen from Jimmy Neutron
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: High Sheen from Jimmy Neutron Medium: Procreate Description: Woman in armour.</description></item><item><title>My favourite artist</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-8-02a0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-8-02a0/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: : Phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My favourite music artist Ariana Grande and her sing 34 35.
I wanted to draw her for a while but was never really good enough so I tried again and think this turned out really well
The shiny white on the cardigan jacket thingy is the light to show how it&amp;rsquo;s reflective I incorporated the wood in the base of the &amp;ldquo;snow globe?</description></item><item><title>Trashbin</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Autodesk sketch.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw the prompt, saw time-limit, thought to self &amp;ldquo;what do i draw well?&amp;rdquo;. Answer: Trash. This is a warning, dont read too much into my thinking process (colours were abstracted from the source image)
, / (cuz symbolisms)
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>