<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arancil on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/arancil/</link><description>Recent content in arancil on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/arancil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: various traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Images in the imgur link: Imgur External Link It&amp;rsquo;s been fun. Thanks everyone participating. Seeing everyone&amp;rsquo;s work in this showcase format week by week has been a really great way to share art with each other, inspire, motivate, develop and helping me and others appreciate more things about the work people do as we&amp;rsquo;re enabled to get into closer detail on the what, how &amp;amp; why in regards to the art people do.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Fineliner 0.05 mm yay.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not cleaning my submission up today ;_; seriously sorry please make do
It&amp;rsquo;s treefolk migration season, and for woodland folk daring to climb them it&amp;rsquo;s prime time to gather food from up there.
Guys, guys, just sitting down putting in lines here and there where you feel like it is so much fun.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Still very much a work in progress, but posting what&amp;rsquo;s currently on paper. Friend asked if I could make something for his wall, so I sat down and improvised some stuff, did a refined version, then an A3 sketch, now lightboxing it up to watercolor. Didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to do something for week 14, but this happened to line up with having flames, so why not!</description></item><item><title>This is where I live now</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on DoughyYeast&amp;rsquo;s headcanon
This week has been chaotic art-wise but did some fineliner cheating so you viewers probably can&amp;rsquo;t spot half the mistakes HAH! Have a good day day/night/morning/evening, everyone, you&amp;rsquo;re all lovely.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>I DON'T HAVE TIME TO COME UP WITH A TITLE ALREADY LATE AS-IS oh hang on CHOKE ME LIKE YOU HATE ME obviously sorry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-9-f05f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-9-f05f/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil, watercolor, acrylics, promarkers, various fineliners, ink, hands, anger, frustration, stress, acceptance, coffee.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so this kind of didn&amp;rsquo;t happen as intended, just smashed together everything that had color on it
consider that bit inspired by @DynoLoafer
Also @Mrop2000 was my spirit animal
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>1:43:51 (PB)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Oil sticks &amp;amp; oil crayons + some paper cutout.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Printed out the prompt&amp;rsquo;s image - turns out I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any black ink, just color so it looked .. yeah. Took a different approach on each of the two canvas. Finally, after painting was done, I cut out some parts of the prompt image from the paper and just sort of slapped it on.</description></item><item><title>placeholder edit later</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Scene: Oh no, one of the remnant forces of the humans are being hunted by the reptilian empire led by Hiss Majesty - but the sand starts rumbling and what rises out of it?
Three panel piece, there&amp;rsquo;s some storyboarding done for the pre-first-panel storytelling as well, but cut it down to two of the nicest looking key panels (+ a dramatic final one).</description></item><item><title>It's just a painting why does it have to have a title? But fine, the title as a noise, like horses neigh kind of.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Trad art, watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Interpretation of the prompt; I sat down and did some painting that I simply loved doing, no research, no finding references, no working through a concept, just doing a sketch and putting paint on paper, feeling a harmonious flow in the work itself unlike the frustration I usually feel while doing art. It was kind of nice.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: A3 watercolor, some fine liners, autumn gold ink, a color pencil from a dusty box.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes On her birthday stream, cindy&amp;rsquo;s birthday wishes were &amp;ldquo;read chainsaw man&amp;rdquo; (lol no you read it) and &amp;ldquo;draw a dragon&amp;rdquo;. So here&amp;rsquo;s the dragon. Couple weeks late, but still.</description></item><item><title>1:21 AM</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Acrylic paint (Magenta/yellow mix for orange, winsor violet with a bit of magenta for the hand).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tried to capture desperation, intensity and passion. Didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to make the indentations left by the fingers the way I wanted - the idea of the situation is someone digging her nails into the back of her lover.</description></item><item><title>Behold my stand - [BRIGHT EYES!!]</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-3-b87b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-3-b87b/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Ink (+watercolour for the red), a little bit of digital post editing to even out the whiteout and broken paper (PLEASE TEACH ME DIGITAL EDITING SOMEONE).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes DAMN IT DIDN&amp;rsquo;T KEEP THE IN CLIPBOARD WHEN DELETING THE SUBMISSION but from memory:
A JoJo-esque pre-fight peacocking scene. Imagine this being followed by the villain capturing the hero from behind, whispering some sort of mockery in the hero&amp;rsquo;s ear with his deep voice.</description></item><item><title>This is why I drink</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor (Arches A5 rough).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;In the year 20XX
Every living being on Earth
Is late for dinner&amp;rdquo;
Had to redo the whole thing after being unhappy with the first go at it - and I feel like the &amp;ldquo;SPACE&amp;rdquo; keyword wasn&amp;rsquo;t given any justice. I have some ideas on how it could have been dealt with better, but alas, we&amp;rsquo;ll just see that as part of the lesson and learning.</description></item><item><title>Plaid &amp; Lace sans Lace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was originally going for &amp;ldquo;Plaid &amp;amp; Lace&amp;rdquo; as my keywords, but &amp;hellip; no way I&amp;rsquo;m putting down work on the &amp;ldquo;Lace&amp;rdquo; part as well. The yellow is &amp;ldquo;Gold Star&amp;rdquo; ink from Diamine, the rest is fineliner, uni-ball for white and some cobalt+ultramarine for shaded areas.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>