<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 05: Royal Green on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-05-royal-green/</link><description>Recent content in Week 05: Royal Green on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-05-royal-green/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Title Too Long]</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-4a75/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-4a75/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5- Royal Green- Jade Stone I don&amp;#39;t have title for this portrait. Can someone name it?I just took on the meaning of Jade Stone which bring good luck, peace and harmony just like a smile did.</description></item><item><title>Big Green Dragon Kingdom</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-5-1d3c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-5-1d3c/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In this technical folk metal piece, I focus on changing textures. The video will explain. This piece is very experimental and not meant for human consumption.
&amp;ldquo;Royal green&amp;rdquo; is musical imagery: &amp;ldquo;cold and hard&amp;rdquo; sounds like heavy metal and &amp;ldquo;jade&amp;rdquo; implies an opulence that cuts through: the kanun and saz instruments.</description></item><item><title>Decay</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: colored pencils + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based off of the jade burial suits of the Han dynasty, which were ceremonial suits constructed from squares of jade and gold thread. There&amp;rsquo;s something very somber for me about these suits, where they are nearly identical and often have jade features placed to represent their face. also remind me never to do colored pencil drawings again cuz its too hard</description></item><item><title>Flow</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-5-f1a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-5-f1a7/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Acrylics.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took a lot of influence from the messy textures created by Jade. I made the loops start from point a to point b and have continuous flow while adding in different textures through paint splatters, sponges, and various paint strokes. I really just let it happen as I painted, while focusing on trying to create different textures.</description></item><item><title>Jade Bee</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-5-af61/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-5-af61/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A bee carved of jade, with translucent jade wings. Background flowers are a free CSP asset (ie I didn&amp;rsquo;t draw them).
IG/Tumblr lithiumreflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 5 **Title: ** Jade Bee Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: A bee carved of jade, with translucent jade wings.</description></item><item><title>Jade Dragon on plinth</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-5-8cfe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-5-8cfe/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital 3D (Blender).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not my model. I tried to model a dragon in 3D but I&amp;rsquo;m not good at sculpting, but the shading of the model, lighting and environment are my work. Added 4 pin lights to get the translucent jade effect inside the model.
Screen shot of my setup
Social Media Twitch: magus_hellwalker Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jaysom Kim</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s honestly a lot more to this but the concept was &amp;ldquo;jade teeth grills&amp;rdquo; and turned into asian fucc boi. This is like one of those pictures from a high concept idol photo book LOL///
((The bigger project will be worked on but have this pick up line as a sneak peak: Do you like curry?</description></item><item><title>Not My Forte</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Dragon shown (Astro): &amp;ldquo;Erhm&amp;hellip; are you sure all of this jade jewelry is considered attractive? There&amp;rsquo;s so many piercings&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Dragon offscreen (Backey): &amp;ldquo;Of course, your Highness! People will swoon for you and your glittery glory.&amp;rdquo; Astro: &amp;ldquo;How do you know?&amp;rdquo; Backey: &amp;ldquo;Uhm.. your Highness, word gets around eheh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; (sweating) &amp;hellip;Got this done without stress, yay!</description></item><item><title>Prosperity</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pretty busy this week, so something simple. The image of the expensive jade necklace reminded me of my string of pearls plant. Jade symbolises purification, nourishment and growth, so a plant seemed a perfect fit. My little SOP isn&amp;rsquo;t huge and majestic yet, but it grows a little and becomes a little more regal every day</description></item><item><title>Queen of the Skies</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt immediately made me think of the Rathian from Monster Hunter, the female counterpart to the series' flagship monster Rathalos. I tried to follow the prompt resource on recreating the jade effect using a small jade dragon as a reference.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Seal soapstone carving</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ocean-week-5-cdf0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ocean-week-5-cdf0/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: soapstone carving.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Although the prompt centres around green jade, I carved a piece of soapstone under the pretense of it as white jade. The design is influenced by a well known chinese poem: Quiet Night Thoughts by LiBai, it describes looking up at the moon and thinking of one’s family at home. I have lightly inked the carving to contrast the details.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: A3 watercolor, some fine liners, autumn gold ink, a color pencil from a dusty box.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes On her birthday stream, cindy&amp;rsquo;s birthday wishes were &amp;ldquo;read chainsaw man&amp;rdquo; (lol no you read it) and &amp;ldquo;draw a dragon&amp;rdquo;. So here&amp;rsquo;s the dragon. Couple weeks late, but still.</description></item><item><title>Irene</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-5-79ae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-5-79ae/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes It’s a quick piece I drew based on Irene from Red Velvet! I tried to make her look kind of like a jade statue but the reflections and lighting I don’t quite understand yet&amp;hellip; time for some studies
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jade Possessions</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-5-f303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-5-f303/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: i love airbrushes.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Master of possession by games workshop base layer chaos black, Mr surfacer 1200 for zenithal shading then vallejo green ink airbrushed. The head and any other skulls had badab black wash applied just before the vallejo green ink was sprayed on. i hate cleaning up after airbrushing. a better angle</description></item><item><title>Jade scales</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-5-1b42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-5-1b42/</guid><description> Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Ibis Paintx.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (double underscore
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5 Title : Jade scales Medium: Digital - Ibis Paintx Socials: Insta-leo__layne (double underscore</description></item><item><title>Jade Temple</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I started this piece by chaotically&amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple. it&amp;rsquo;s pretty messy &amp;lt;a:Bonk:769829350622232587&amp;gt;
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 5 Title: Jade Temple Medium: Digital (Procreate) Description: I started this piece by *chaotically*&amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple.</description></item><item><title>Jadeite</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-5-5cd3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-5-5cd3/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes When I about the prompt being Jade related. I thought of the anime Houseki no Kuni, and am eager to try my hand to personify a crystal. My goal is to design a character that fits with the existing characters.
Social Media Instagram: poruchan_920 Twitch: poru_chan Twitter: poruchan09 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Vessel</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is my first time using photoshop for art, i tried making the short sword the centre piece of the piece, and i think the eyes make it pop. Hope people realise this is Itadori Yuuji from Jujutsu Kaisen
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Need a Hand?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Finally, something not last minute! I decided to be experimental, doing a lineless piece to try and draw something more simple to avoid deadline anxiety. The hand was originally supposed to look like stone, but it looks more like a bush&amp;hellip; so I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a bush now lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Flawless</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Firstly; if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of &amp;ldquo;Kintsugi&amp;rdquo; before, you&amp;rsquo;re welcome 😛 Secondly, rendering jade is a mood&amp;hellip; cheers for that This one took me a hot minute, but I think I&amp;rsquo;m starting to get the hang of digital painting somewhat 😅
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jade Jian</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ``
I painted the outline for the sword, tried painting the jade texture, but was displeased with the result, so I went and took a photo of the metal part of a local ww2 bunker and used it to make the texture by adjusting stuff here and there. The handle has the original bunker color</description></item><item><title>Behind The Doors</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (PhotoShop).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to make something that has a backstory so basically i had a friend that loved ninjas and they passed away a few years back so i wanted to do something not just for me but for them so i used the green (jade) as a representation of harmony/peace i hope you like it 😊</description></item><item><title>Green Emerald</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</guid><description> Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Music cover
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5 Title: Green Emerald Medium: ClipStudio Description: Music cover</description></item><item><title>Here we go again</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Installation.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes stickman doesn&amp;rsquo;t go brrrrrr. stickman goes mining. but seriously though, royal green reminded me of the military (for some reason) and jade was the other prompt. so i had my uniform become be a jade mine. :P
ps i failed kindergarten, i cant use a pair of scissors &amp;lt;:cindryAAA:775498319074033674&amp;gt;
Media:
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>