<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pumpkan on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/pumpkan/</link><description>Recent content in Pumpkan on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/pumpkan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Peace is Dynamism</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @a1ewanrichards &amp;ldquo;When the land becomes graveyards&amp;rdquo; (FiveClawd External Link ) I loved this piece because it tapped into a vivid memory of playing soccer opposite sugarcane fields, watching them slowly disintegrate into flames and having the ash gently fall on us as we practiced. Life felt like it was so vividly coloured back then.</description></item><item><title>It'sssss Smelbourne!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling nostalgic for blue skies and pub crawls in the city. Here&amp;rsquo;s a shot from 2017 from a bar verandah, now ssssswarming with ssssssnakes. Taking it easy on the wrist still, but I had enough in me to make this!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Whats Left : Left handed Leftovers, vol. 1</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: markers + paper in gif.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m still dealing with wrist pain so I&amp;rsquo;m making the most of it. What do I have left? A whole other side of my body to learn to draw with! Shout out to LeftHandedToons, a comic site that I spent a lot of time on as a kid. This one&amp;rsquo;s for you</description></item><item><title>A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wrist still hurts, I want to D word
@/pumpkanart on tooter and touch
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain Medium: Procreate Description: wrist still hurts, I want to D word Socials: @/pumpkanart on tooter and touch</description></item><item><title>i suffer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-13-f4a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-13-f4a6/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes hurt my wrist so this is all I&amp;rsquo;ve got. suffering in real time
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: i suffer Medium: procreate Description: hurt my wrist so this is all I&amp;#39;ve got.</description></item><item><title>Are You Listening?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-12-2b80/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-12-2b80/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Indesign (if you prefer illustrator you can fight me).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Throwback to that time I did a graphic design degree. The hardest thing I find when designing is deciding what stupid pointless words to put on the page. I feel like, especially at uni, a lot of words are there to look pretty and have no message.</description></item><item><title>He RUINED my DREAM JOURNAL</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: paper and gold thread and glue and stuff.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes couldn&amp;rsquo;t bare to draw anything this week, so i bound a book. getting the inner pages printed was a goddamn trial, and i wish I had matt laminate for the cover bc the shiny is gross, but I like the little gold thread stars on the front and the shiny paper on the inside makes it feel very dreamy.</description></item><item><title>The dread beach bum La Verne</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one got away from me a bit. I intended to do something simple, I really did. All I really wanted to do was do some stronger posing than usual. I hope this fits within the prompt for this week, shes wearing clothes lmao&amp;hellip;
Anyway here is my dnd character Joselynn La Verne being no more dramatic than usual</description></item><item><title>wikipedia</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</guid><description> Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes yo who else misses hatsune miku
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: wikipedia Medium: Procreate Description: yo who else misses hatsune miku Social Media: @/pumpkanart on twitter and twitch</description></item><item><title>Angels in our Atmosphere</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing collage my dudes. From brainstorm to submission with was about 75 minutes. The prompt had me thinking about metal in art, so i drew images from photography (silver bromide development) to lithography/etching (metal plate prints) to digital art (like&amp;hellip; computers and stuff). The birds are just to cover her nipples</description></item><item><title>Sunset at Calico Desert</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes When I heard the prompt was about deserts and what lived in them I immediately thought of stardew valley! I love that big dragon skeleton, hungering for the sun. I was aiming for a phone background look, so please feel free to use it!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Magical girl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing character design, and with simple love the first thing I thought of was Madoka and magical girls. For ‘balance’ I made her very symmetrical. She’s inspired by roses. I can imagine her on a team of flower magical girls fighting against weed monsters of the week. Very Tokyo mew style! I wanna draw their whole team&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Prosperity</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pretty busy this week, so something simple. The image of the expensive jade necklace reminded me of my string of pearls plant. Jade symbolises purification, nourishment and growth, so a plant seemed a perfect fit. My little SOP isn&amp;rsquo;t huge and majestic yet, but it grows a little and becomes a little more regal every day</description></item><item><title>Assimilation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i read a cool tumble post about a botanist burying a lamb bone under a tree and when they came back a few months later the tree had completely absorbed it. Left it to the last minute so it’s not exactly what I had in mind but better done than not so 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Forest King</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-3-7d52/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-3-7d52/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Rubber stamp block + ink, procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Bc this prompt focusses on contrast I wanted to explore black and white stamp printing! This is the 3rd stamp I&amp;rsquo;ve done and by far the biggest. I dont have red ink so I had to add that digitally. Kinda bummed that the scan was so unkind to it, but it was a nice change from the stuff I usually do</description></item><item><title>You have new text message! High five!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wanted to draw a mermaid. I really wanted to show this massive lady with something strange and unexpected. And those nokia phones are probably the only thing that could survive the crushing depths of the deep sea
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Four of Pumpkins</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to do something elegant with pattern. However, when I streamed this like an hour ago, I was aggressively persuaded (bullied) into adding more pumpkins, and now it’s a tarot card of the suit of pumpkins. 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item></channel></rss>