<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jonasw on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jonasw/</link><description>Recent content in jonasw on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jonasw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Big Skeleton</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-16-64e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-16-64e9/</guid><description> Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Almost forgot to submit :I
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Big Skeleton Medium: Pencils Description: Almost forgot to submit :I</description></item><item><title>Hungry Firelings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-14-6699/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-14-6699/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Fire.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Look behind you, they&amp;#39;re the Captain now Medium: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR Description: Return to monke GOLD Week: 14 Title: Hungry Firelings Medium: Fire Description: SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION</description></item><item><title>Look behind you, they're the Captain now</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-13-2bfa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-13-2bfa/</guid><description> Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Return to monke GOLD
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Look behind you, they&amp;#39;re the Captain now Medium: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR Description: Return to monke GOLD Week: 14 Title: Hungry Firelings Medium: Fire Description: SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION</description></item><item><title>Six Pix Mix</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-11-6ec2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-11-6ec2/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Some different sky colors
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Six Pix Mix Medium: Watercolor Description: Some different sky colors</description></item><item><title>Harlem '33/'83</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-10-f4b3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-10-f4b3/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Colored Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ?
(Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Harlem &amp;#39;33/&amp;#39;83 Medium: Colored Pencils Description: ? (Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!</description></item><item><title>Important Dream</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-9-8e62/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-9-8e62/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat. washi tape of betrayal).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Katamari Damacy (Song) Fanart, wanted something big and bright and cheerful. Also wanted practice drawing general &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo;, and write some japanese characters.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Important Dream Medium: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat.</description></item><item><title>Swim for the Ball</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-8-f7d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-8-f7d9/</guid><description> Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: Swim for the Ball Medium: Pencil on Paper Description: Don&amp;#39;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen</description></item><item><title>Angry Bird</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-7-fbb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jonasw-week-7-fbb3/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ballpoint and hand smudge.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Who is the intruder in the desert? Is it the bird? Is it the sun? Is it Super Mario Bros?
No thanks
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Angry Bird Medium: Ballpoint and hand smudge Description: Who is the intruder in the desert?</description></item></channel></rss>