<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TheLagExpert on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/thelagexpert/</link><description>Recent content in TheLagExpert on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/thelagexpert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glass House</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-12-f76f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-12-f76f/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A bit too late cz I am busy with the exams. These are Lyrics from my favourite Song from last year it&amp;rsquo;s called Glass House by Gabbie Hanna, It has a good message behind it (I think), and it has the best music video I have ever seen, check it out if you have time.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the brave new world of me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.
Social Media Instagram: billelhambli Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Welcome to the brave new world of me Medium: Affinity photo Description: My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes reminds me of my best friend in the world (we were friends for almost 13 years, till they&amp;rsquo;ve moved to Egypt) we still talk, but it&amp;rsquo;s not like before cz we&amp;rsquo;re both a bit busy. Like that heart, our friendship became cold and hollow, with the screens being our only connection. Lol, that&amp;rsquo;s so depressive; anyway, Alexa play Driver&amp;rsquo;s license by Olivia Rodrigo.</description></item><item><title>Lonely in the Quartz desert</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-3-8cfa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-3-8cfa/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes lost in the desert, not really what I imagined (was afraid to post it), but will finish it as soon as I get better; it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to give lonely and cold vibes. Will do better next week hopefully.
Social Media Instagram: billelhambli Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item></channel></rss>