<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cindry on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/artists/cindry/</link><description>Recent content in cindry on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/artists/cindry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ooh shit</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes hey you should read kaiju no.8 its really good and big things are really cool!!! im sad i couldnt show the whole process on my stream but here it is! is it creepy yet??
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>leeeeemons</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: relief printing on note books.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes taking it easy this week with something i found relaxing and i guess soothing? something like the lemon honey i was drinking while sick. make some stamps! have a good time! take care of yourself
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>burnout</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: paper cutting photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is about burnout and how hard it is sometimes to recognise it while in haste. Just remember to take your time, recognise to take care of your body. Don&amp;rsquo;t burn yourself, it&amp;rsquo;ll take a while to recover!
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>im dying btw</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-13-4534/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-13-4534/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: digital, CSP and SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes based off true events like 1:50 PM 2/4/2021 my water was too hot to drink so i was dying. i think this has inspired me to do more 4komas tho in the future!!! i really like short fun comics, one of my favourite things to draw&amp;hellip; so i hope you like it too!</description></item><item><title>Just a normal day as an asian girl online</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-12-713c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-12-713c/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Photography and Digital Editing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TW: racism, sexism This is a response piece to the experience of being a female online. The quotes are all taken from real messages sent to me on my stream. The use of keycaps represents not only the digital nature of these messages but allude to how anonymous messages are written with magazine clippings.</description></item><item><title>Rolling Lonely Star</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hey I love the stars and I love katamari. Star gazing is something i really love doing, and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fun if a little prince came along and ruined your long exposure photography??
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Implied emotion??</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Illustrator and CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Trying out gradient maps for the first time!! wow it&amp;rsquo;s super cool and colours are fresh! kinda want it to hold some sort of emotion in the fabric, what do you think?
shop.fiveclawd.com LOL
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>ANIME AM I RIGHT</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams. wow pretty eyes yeet. huff huff huff join my giveaway LOL
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 **Title: ANIME AM I RIGHT** Medium: digital painting Description: 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams.</description></item><item><title>Foish</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: graphic, Illustrator.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now? i love him&amp;rsquo;st tho hehehe practiced some illustrator too
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 **Title: Foish** Medium: graphic, Illustrator Description: Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now?</description></item><item><title>Strange Sands</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ink on paper, a comic!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love alliteration lol! hey isn&amp;rsquo;t is kinda mysterious? I got this idea from when crabs would dig holes at the beach and spit out the water. Finding that in the desert would be super creepy&amp;hellip; also stippling is hard. I do really like this though and hope you do too!</description></item><item><title>Simple Love</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, and publication.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t like Valentines Days but I wanted to talk about what I loved, pets! Animals show love in such wonderful ways and I&amp;rsquo;m so happy!!!!
The main submission is a lil A6 zine you can fold yourself if you have a b+W a4 printer!
CHECK DISCUSSIONS ON HOW TO PRINT</description></item><item><title>Jaysom Kim</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s honestly a lot more to this but the concept was &amp;ldquo;jade teeth grills&amp;rdquo; and turned into asian fucc boi. This is like one of those pictures from a high concept idol photo book LOL///
((The bigger project will be worked on but have this pick up line as a sneak peak: Do you like curry?</description></item><item><title>Morning Breeze</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Animation, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog. Low key a vibe, animation is hell, and I hope everyone likes it!
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Morning Breeze** Medium: Animation, CSP Description: Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog.</description></item><item><title>Fire Fist Ace</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-3-6fd7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-3-6fd7/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I read one piece, everyone read one piece. Also ace is cool ace is really cool, tried to keep it simple and I really tried ;;;;
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Fire Fist Ace** Medium: Digital, SAI Description: I read one piece, everyone read one piece.</description></item><item><title>Deep Discovery</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: 2 page comic, Ink on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be weird to find light in a deep ocean dive? Kinda scary if you ask me. I love the idea of discovering something once lost, unsure if peaceful or dangerous waiting to be explored. Really just inspired by series like Made in Abyss and Jigokuraku!</description></item><item><title>Rat 1 and Rat 2</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes gay rat wedding I went a bit crazy on SAI which is a huge guilty pleasure. In the end it&amp;rsquo;s a bit cute and a good mood so I&amp;rsquo;m happy with what I made. Looking forward definitely going to use more references since i should, this is a bit surreal.
@fiveclawd</description></item></channel></rss>