<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>a1ewanrichards on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/a1ewanrichards/</link><description>Recent content in a1ewanrichards on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/a1ewanrichards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amalgamation: At A Time Like This, Will Someone Be There For You?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-dcab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-dcab/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My first attempt at digital painting! Meh results, I think.
I tried to recreate this scenery of the Taal Volcano Island in Tagaytay, a popular tourist destination south of Manila, along a steep access road that we crossed during an official business trip where a teammate and I were doing ocular inspections of venues from the recently-concluded 30th Southeast Asian Games.</description></item><item><title>Resistance 4 - Sometimes, The Heart Yearns For Mangoes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A change of pace, I think? I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really pinpoint any concept to execute for this week, but this imagery had lingered to me for a few days. Then I also remembered a 1994 poem I read from a book whose title for this I based it from.
The poem is about homesickness and wishing for a better world from a faraway place, a faraway country.</description></item><item><title>The End of Zeno's Paradox</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, entered, done, a lot of creative endeavors throughout my life, and looking back, it has been quite frustrating, to say the least. This frustration has consumed me over the past several years, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure last year was even the peak.
I&amp;rsquo;ve sold all my camera gear to help make ends meet, threw away my collection of piano sheet music (much to my older brother&amp;rsquo;s surprise), and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to go from here; I think I&amp;rsquo;ve reached my limit, whatever it may be.</description></item><item><title>Portrait 7: Ruminations</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-13-4403/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-13-4403/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Completely dissatisfied with my previous entry, so here&amp;rsquo;s a new one. I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling lonely and isolated lately for so long. I feel that nobody will ever bother to listen or understand me.
My interpretation of Otomatsu Sato from the movie &amp;ldquo;Poppoya&amp;rdquo; (Railroad Man), a stationmaster at a former coal mining town, whose train station he mans is about to close.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation - The Body Keeps The Score</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-12-8990/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-12-8990/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Felt markers and highlighters.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one was really hard to make, both physically and emotionally. I felt a lot of things doing this. These&amp;hellip; things were borne from both internal and external stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve heard throughout my life. I think&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s all I can say for now. I might expand on this elsewhere, IDK.
The concept and title is based from a book by Dr.</description></item><item><title>Undercooled 1: Please Return The Moon To Us</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker and oil pastel on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I first conceptualized a starry universe portrait theme of sorts, but I thought a landscape would be better. This is my first time using oil pastel.
The flying figure is my interpretation of a &amp;ldquo;bakunawa,&amp;rdquo; a serpent-like dragon in Philippine mythology, who is said to cause various natural phenomena, such as eclipses.</description></item><item><title>Portrait 6: Get Together</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker on paper, 9x12in.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Drew this earlier at the office since our room didn&amp;rsquo;t have internet since yesterday afternoon. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t think of anything nice, but this came to mind soon enough.
The dance is called &amp;ldquo;tinikling,&amp;rdquo; where a couple dances between two bamboo poles being clapped to the musical beat. It is somewhat similar to a waltz and a mazurka.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation - Welcome To Hell</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to express in one way or another this powerlessness I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling for a very long time now. I based part of the concept and the title from a scene in the video game Spec Ops: The Line.
Social Media Instagram: and Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Amalagamation: Vague Memory</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Adobe Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is probably the laziest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, lol. I had other ideas in mind, but I junked them since I can&amp;rsquo;t pull it off.
Social Media Instagram: and Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Resistance 3: When The Lands Become Graveyards</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-d4f0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-d4f0/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes @rjmmendoza on IG/Twitter | A1EwanRichards on Twitch
It&amp;rsquo;s not a desert in the typical sense. It&amp;rsquo;s an amalgam of sugar cane farms and the concept of &amp;ldquo;peace of the cemetery,&amp;rdquo; referring to a quote by St. Oscar Romero. The title is a rough translation of a poem by Filipino poet Axel Pinpin, originally titled &amp;ldquo;Kung Puntod na ang Lupa&amp;rdquo; (literal: If the Land is a Tomb&amp;quot;).</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: Smile and Smile</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-634a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-634a/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ink on paper, 9x12 inches..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ink on paper, 9x12 inches.
Another week, another rush job lol. I had an initial idea but I dumped it since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t execute it. I made this just now.
Anyway&amp;hellip; I tried to recreate the moment I shared with friend and a crush from around 2015. I earlier sent her a message apologizing for &amp;ldquo;being weird&amp;rdquo; (not my words) after being scolded by someone for acting weird towards two girls.</description></item><item><title>Bloody Fields</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Felt pen on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I actually struggled with the theme, but this came suddenly one day ago. Killing of farmers is still an issue in the Philippines as they struggle for genuine and lasting land reform. January 22 was also the anniversary of the Mendiola Massacre, where 13 farmers were killed when police dispersed a large farmer&amp;rsquo;s protest.</description></item><item><title>Gui</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-3-4532/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-3-4532/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Felt and ink on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I looked up the flag of Okinawa and it was perfect with what I had in mind. The man in the center is a sketch of Kamejiro Senaga, one of the pioneers of the peace movement in Okinawa to expel the US bases hosted in the islands. &amp;ldquo;Gui&amp;rdquo; is the title of a composition by Japanese composer Ryuichi Sakamoto created for a feature film about Kamejiro&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item></channel></rss>