<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vectorong on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/vectorong/</link><description>Recent content in vectorong on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/vectorong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#2021DesignRefresh Portfolio</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: E-portfolio (flipbook made on https://fliphtml5.com).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I find it&amp;rsquo;s always nice to look back whenever you complete a series / project and celebrate, so this is my way of doing so - creating a book with all the pieces I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted. I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed this challenge and trying all these new mediums, even when I felt like my brain might explode.</description></item><item><title>Rat Race</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Graphite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The idiom is defined as &amp;ldquo;an endless, self-defeating, or pointless pursuit&amp;hellip;The term is commonly associated with an exhausting, repetitive lifestyle that leaves no time for relaxation or enjoyment.&amp;quot;(thanks wikipedia) The concept was initially sketched out two years ago, but quickly shelved after major life events and and work affected my ability to put effort into it.</description></item><item><title>Bread, Butter, Boysenberry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Food.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My grandfather loved boysenberry jam, so I made a simple tribute to him and my favorite meal, breakfast. Used a knife and jam to create the basic form of a boysenberry, with bread as the &amp;ldquo;canvas&amp;rdquo; and butter to prevent it from getting soggy. Jammin with jam lol
Social Media Instagram: karen_tsugawa Twitch: vectorong Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Five Virtues</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Pyrography (woodburning).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Illustration based on the Fenghuang, a mythological bird whose body symbolizes the celestial bodies and the five tail feathers representing the five virtues of Confucius. It is said that their appearance signals the coming of a new era.
And what better way to honor my favorite mythological bird than to burn in directly into some wood with fire LOL</description></item><item><title>Then She Fell”</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-13-8b9e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-13-8b9e/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Mixed media (plaster strips, paper clay, paint), Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Inspired by the song Bad Dream by Tatsuya Kitani (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lkYeBXXHgY4)
*I&amp;rsquo;m forced to live a meaningless and unreasonable tragedy
Who the hell said “after rain comes fair weather”
I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine this bad dream ending*
The mask is referencing a Hannya mask that&amp;rsquo;s used in Noh theater, which is used in the performances to depict female demons that are filled with jealousy.</description></item><item><title>The Comfy Chair</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-12-9bfb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-12-9bfb/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Ink + Marker, Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Inspired by the range of Italian designer Massimo Vignelli&amp;rsquo;s work, and that &amp;ldquo;If you can design one thing, you can design everything.&amp;rdquo; Often I feel as a designer and artist, we&amp;rsquo;re directed to only learn a specific &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; of skills, when in reality all your knowledge ends up coming into play in some form.</description></item><item><title>Cancri</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Relief printing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on my initial wonder (and subsequent terror) of the galaxy, where I would try to find my favorite constellations in the night sky. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of a parallels to the ocean; so unknown, beautiful, yet also terrifying to think about in its vastness. Also a reference to myself and my group of friends, since many of us happen to be born during the Cancer season.</description></item><item><title>Boroboro Bobbin pants (ngl i literally almost called these boroboro bobbin bottoms LUL)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Fabric / fashion (upcycled fabric, screenprinting, and sewing).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ボロボロ (&amp;ldquo;boroboro&amp;rdquo;) often refers to an item that is worn out to the point where it is in tatters. Rather than throw it out, I find it can be a very personal and relaxing process to repair it, following similar Japanese repairing idealogy where the fix / mend also becomes a point of beauty.</description></item><item><title>Repetition, Reminisce, Reflection</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Suminagashi (Japanese ink marbling technique) on handmade paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;It reflects me. It reflects you&amp;hellip;Two lines become one&amp;rdquo; - Mirrors by STUTS (ft. SUMIN, Daichi Yamamoto &amp;amp; CHINZA DOPENESS) (the song I was vibin to while making this piece: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wdwzLaljOzw)
While working alongside printmaking friends on a group zoom call, I was suddenly taken back to a time where we were all gathered together at our university&amp;rsquo;s studio, working until the sky was dark and blasting music three octaves too loud.</description></item><item><title>Fixation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A visual ode to my need for repetitious tasks and the nonsensical thoughts that pass through my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m half asleep. I love focusing on the materiality of objects and photos, so I focused on using just pieces of the photo to construct an abstract image and let it tell its own story.</description></item><item><title>Seconds in Sand</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (shot w/ a Canon 40D).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s often times when I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in an internal &amp;lsquo;desert&amp;rsquo;, where ideas don&amp;rsquo;t come easily and time slips by. Yet somehow the creative spark is always hovering in between this barren space and the looming deadline, and often I just find myself having to be patient for the right moment rather than to grasp at the sands.</description></item><item><title>Paper Pond</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Origami + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Going back to my first art love - paper. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been surrounded by paper and origami ever since I was kid, and wanted to pay homage to both my roots and the medium that has so much potential. Also I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting a piece to bring in the two parts of my heritage in one piece; my last name roughly translates to &amp;lsquo;ferry across the river&amp;rsquo; and my chinese name means &amp;lsquo;yellow love lotus&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Decay</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: colored pencils + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based off of the jade burial suits of the Han dynasty, which were ceremonial suits constructed from squares of jade and gold thread. There&amp;rsquo;s something very somber for me about these suits, where they are nearly identical and often have jade features placed to represent their face. also remind me never to do colored pencil drawings again cuz its too hard</description></item><item><title>Façade</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ink + paper collage.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Delving a bit personal with this piece. Often there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between the person I present to others - usually my business persona I use for my work that seems to have everything orderly and &amp;lsquo;put together&amp;rsquo;, while my internal self always feels like it&amp;rsquo;s in a state of at least minor chaos and has to navigate the unknown without guidance.</description></item><item><title>Tesseract</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-3-f068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-3-f068/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Vector illustration.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Rather than a finalized illustration, I wanted to use this week as a way to push myself to complete a concept art for a story I&amp;rsquo;ve been slowly developing. A lot of the story revolved around shapes with very graphic elements, so I wanted to push that and also do a medium completely different from the previous weeks.</description></item><item><title>Little Dragons</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Gyotaku (traditional jp printmaking method using ink on fish, tho I used shrimp for this so I guess ebitaku lol) + dyed paper napkin.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had a dream a while back of seeing a group of shrimp, much larger than possible in real life, and having the feeling I was amidst something otherworldly. Rather than seeing them as food, I wanted to show the shrimp in their element and with regal-ness akin to dragons.</description></item><item><title>Origin Point</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Processing (program) + Java.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Circle created with Java code that randomizes the spiral variance and the stroke; I wanted to challenge myself to learn a new programming language this year since I enjoy using them for both work and side projects. I&amp;rsquo;d love to be able to do a different medium for each week if I&amp;rsquo;m able.</description></item></channel></rss>