<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Space Warfare Development on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/artists/space-warfare-development/</link><description>Recent content in Space Warfare Development on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/artists/space-warfare-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spicy Tuna</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional art. Copic markers and pens, gell pen..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Spicy Tuna
A delicious Japanese meal for lunch - a bowl of spicy tuna and rice with chopped onion garnish, along with a cup of maccha.
I applied the photo texture to the maccha cup, the rice bowl, and the ground tuna. I drew in gel pen white on the cup and bowl surfaces to simulate ceramic gloss.</description></item><item><title>Coconut Crab</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-36dc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-36dc/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional, Copic markers.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: &amp;#34;Coconut Crab&amp;#34; Medium: Traditional, Copic markers Description: Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.</description></item><item><title>Harbinger</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-3-66c9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-3-66c9/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional, Copic markers &amp;amp; pens.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took a regular goldfinch, and jammed it full of steroids and heavy metal. &amp;ldquo;Beware the red moonlight, Across the Black Forest night, The deathwings in the tree, Kill everything they see.&amp;rdquo;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item></channel></rss>