<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TITAN011 on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/titan011/</link><description>Recent content in TITAN011 on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/titan011/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Titan's Journey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art? 🤔
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 16 Title: A Titan&amp;#39;s Journey Medium: Clip Studio Description: To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art?</description></item><item><title>Durian at sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decide to try something new this week so i tried animation for the first time&amp;hellip;yea&amp;hellip;its hard 🥲 Could only use 24 frames cause of clipstudio&amp;rsquo;s restriction. Does anyone have any recommendation for 2d animation software? 🎞️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>His name is Shiro 🔥</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked &amp;lt;:UUUdrake:779990724212293642&amp;gt;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: His name is Shiro 🔥 Medium: Clip studio Description: Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked &amp;lt;:UUUdrake:779990724212293642&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>Spicy Expressions</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-13-a56d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-13-a56d/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Beginning of a ego fueled Spicy food challenge #What&amp;rsquo;s ur spice tolerance? 🔥 🔥 🔥
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Spicy Expressions Medium: Clip studio Description: The Beginning of a ego fueled Spicy food challenge #What&amp;#39;s ur spice tolerance?</description></item><item><title>Set Sail to find the legendary Mandrake farm &lt;:OOOdrake:779973582298021890></title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-aba0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-aba0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decided to utilize everything I’ve learned in these past few months (perspective, anatomy, value, color etc.) Conclusion: this was a very humbling experience (I was a bit overwhelmed / kinda gave up on the ship towards the end) xD – I will keep practicing ✍️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Folds</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Folds Medium: Clip Studio Description: Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵</description></item><item><title>Do what make you happy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don’t think I’ll have time to do week 8 art cause of midterms but I manage to finish week 6 ; Life can be a little stressful sometimes so take the time to do the things u love; happy late lunar new year everyone 😃
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Dune Surfing</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</guid><description> Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes has anyone ever tried it? &amp;lt;:blobhyperthink:800558786515435560&amp;gt;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Medium: clip studio Title: Dune Surfing Description: has anyone ever tried it? &amp;lt;:blobhyperthink:800558786515435560&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>Green Emerald</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</guid><description> Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Music cover
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5 Title: Green Emerald Medium: ClipStudio Description: Music cover</description></item><item><title>Sleepless Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn’t use one color but I tried to stick with cold colors? Worked on value and tones? Is floating considered rhythm and movement? (Honestly idk, still new to all these art vocabulary xD). i hope this respect the rules of the challenge &amp;lt;:PepeHands:779990751429918720&amp;gt; Implemented some contrast and circle shape from week 3 challenge so I don’t forget the notions I’ve learned.</description></item><item><title>Brain Echo</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-3-e808/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-3-e808/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Bit out of my comfort zone but tried to do something artsy
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: Brain Echo Medium: Clipstudio Description: Bit out of my comfort zone but tried to do something artsy</description></item><item><title>King of the Sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week:2 Title: King of the Sea Medium: Clipstudio Description: Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.</description></item></channel></rss>