<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-11-atmosphere-spectrum/</link><description>Recent content in Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-11-atmosphere-spectrum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Six Pix Mix</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-11-6ec2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-11-6ec2/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Some different sky colors
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Six Pix Mix Medium: Watercolor Description: Some different sky colors</description></item><item><title>Yesterday</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-11-ebfe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-11-ebfe/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Few word.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A smattering of haikus for my first (and late ehehe) design refresh. Enjoy!
I mumble and groan
Basking in her warm embrace
Good morning, sunshine
Just as the wind blows,
As the clouds and trees just be,
I think of nothing.
Accompany me
Ebony night, Lake Shore Drive
What&amp;rsquo;s for dinner, beans?
Unfathomable
Magnificent, glorious
Twinkling far away</description></item><item><title>Aster Flower Looking Upon a Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Kinda been stressed this week, but I managed to squeeze this piece out. Sketchier lineart than usual because it&amp;rsquo;s literally a sketch that&amp;rsquo;s cleaned up a bit lol, I&amp;rsquo;m tired and need to study for a test :p
Also check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; for a sketch done by DynoLoafer that&amp;rsquo;s basically what the guy looks like from the front lol</description></item><item><title>Bruh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-11-4cdb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-11-4cdb/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes No time to draw something this week so instead I decided on a quick little design. One is a lil goth boy and the other is his pastel bf
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Cancri</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Relief printing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on my initial wonder (and subsequent terror) of the galaxy, where I would try to find my favorite constellations in the night sky. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of a parallels to the ocean; so unknown, beautiful, yet also terrifying to think about in its vastness. Also a reference to myself and my group of friends, since many of us happen to be born during the Cancer season.</description></item><item><title>He RUINED my DREAM JOURNAL</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: paper and gold thread and glue and stuff.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes couldn&amp;rsquo;t bare to draw anything this week, so i bound a book. getting the inner pages printed was a goddamn trial, and i wish I had matt laminate for the cover bc the shiny is gross, but I like the little gold thread stars on the front and the shiny paper on the inside makes it feel very dreamy.</description></item><item><title>Hydrangea Star Gazer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you. I love you to the moon and back.
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Hydrangea Star Gazer Medium: Watercolour Description: There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you.</description></item><item><title>Rolling Lonely Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hey I love the stars and I love katamari. Star gazing is something i really love doing, and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fun if a little prince came along and ruined your long exposure photography??
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Island</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-11-eb4c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-11-eb4c/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Music.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This song features the feeling of oppressive clouds and weather, harsh harmonies and clashing timbres.
This song isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;soft&amp;rdquo; but I wrote it by surrealist writing about the sea, the land, and the sky. I wrote back then: &amp;ldquo;The concept [is] a man on an island panicking and struggling to survive against the weather and wildlife.</description></item><item><title>This is where I live now</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on DoughyYeast&amp;rsquo;s headcanon
This week has been chaotic art-wise but did some fineliner cheating so you viewers probably can&amp;rsquo;t spot half the mistakes HAH! Have a good day day/night/morning/evening, everyone, you&amp;rsquo;re all lovely.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Week 11 head stuck in the clouds</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-11-4301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-11-4301/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A simple one, again. Just a mood I sometimes feel, wonder what it&amp;rsquo;s like up there aye.
urmom 11.0
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 11 Title: Week 11 head stuck in the clouds Medium: Procreate Description: A simple one, again.</description></item><item><title>“you would make the sky a gijinka” - enoki</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ** Used the two references above (an image of a dark sunset and a clear midnight sky)* to create some fantastical characters and I had plans to do two more for *Dawn and **Noon, but time prevails
I need to stop making non-human things human
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>glitch clouds inc</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Medium: Procreate Title: glitch clouds inc Description: sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe</description></item><item><title>Impressionable Sky</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-11-b3a9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-11-b3a9/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photomanipulation.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sick this week so keeping it simple and quick - photomanipulation focused on clouds over the mountains (original photograph also my own).
lithiumreflections (tumblr, IG), lireflections (twitter)
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 **Title: ** Impressionable Sky Medium: Photomanipulation Description: Sick this week so keeping it simple and quick - photomanipulation focused on clouds over the mountains (original photograph also my own).</description></item><item><title>Liminal Sky</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love the sky at dusk, a storm looming on the horizon. The brilliant colours doomed to a few moments before the sky grows dark and the rain begins. That liminal space where you just look at the sky in awe.
Trying to get better at digital painting. Think I got the vibe at least 😊</description></item><item><title>They Come Out at Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Getting into dragons again more than I usually do, so I decided to draw some dragon silhouette&amp;rsquo;s against a pretty night sky! I learned an easy trick to making galaxy/night sky patterns awhile back, so I put that to use in the top part of the screen! I like how this came out, even if it&amp;rsquo;s more simple because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy and tired with the new time change.</description></item><item><title>Undercooled 1: Please Return The Moon To Us</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker and oil pastel on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I first conceptualized a starry universe portrait theme of sorts, but I thought a landscape would be better. This is my first time using oil pastel.
The flying figure is my interpretation of a &amp;ldquo;bakunawa,&amp;rdquo; a serpent-like dragon in Philippine mythology, who is said to cause various natural phenomena, such as eclipses.</description></item><item><title>Cloudy Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Cloudy Night Medium: Photoshop Description: I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart</description></item><item><title>Set Sail to find the legendary Mandrake farm</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-0fee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-0fee/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decided to utilize everything I’ve learned in these past few months (perspective, anatomy, value, color etc.) Conclusion: this was a very humbling experience (I was a bit overwhelmed / kinda gave up on the ship towards the end) xD – I will keep practicing ✍️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Are we at the weekends yet?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw this artist&amp;rsquo;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired. also, i like weekends.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Are we at the weekends yet? Medium: Krita Description: Saw this artist&amp;#39;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired.</description></item><item><title>Laputa</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pressed enter before I put stuff by accident lol
&amp;ldquo;Castle in the Sky&amp;rdquo; is one of my favorite movies of all time, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d draw something inspired by it. The castle&amp;rsquo;s name is Laputa, so I named the piece accordingly.
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Passive smoking</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x and phone photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds. Was pretty, smelled chimney smoke. Wanted to make something fun.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Passive smoking Medium: ibispaint x and phone photo Description: Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds.</description></item></channel></rss>