<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Goblet on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/goblet/</link><description>Recent content in Goblet on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/goblet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mechanics love their jobs sometimes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Krita (still mouse).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t be deceived, the Blue Amazon is a killing machine. Although these robots are programmed to try to act human, they are infact very much controlled by their masters (at least that is what the master thinks). If you think you are in ara ara distance, you are in fact in danger. (didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to finish)</description></item><item><title>Tightrope banana.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paper, permanent marker..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, life happened and I forgot. Here take this shitpost instead. Balance!
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 15 Title: Tightrope banana. Medium: Paper, permanent marker. Description: Sorry, life happened and I forgot.</description></item><item><title>My cat is on fire</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Played around with a photo of my cat.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: My cat is on fire Medium: Krita Description: Played around with a photo of my cat.</description></item><item><title>&lt;:cuporiGun:825806539918278686></title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-13-40e8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-13-40e8/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes remade my emote. made the expression better. (first one is the new one)
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: &amp;lt;:cuporiGun:825806539918278686&amp;gt; Medium: Krita Description: remade my emote.</description></item><item><title>Passive smoking</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x and phone photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds. Was pretty, smelled chimney smoke. Wanted to make something fun.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Passive smoking Medium: ibispaint x and phone photo Description: Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds.</description></item><item><title>textile grook</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, used 5 min
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: textile grook Medium: ibispaint x Description: Sorry, used 5 min Social Media: https://www.twitch.tv/cup_o_rice</description></item><item><title>Color factory</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</guid><description>&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1CrUiHBniouCtC2vncknVcsFT4cf-kVRzb--YlfKXxWA/edit?usp=sharing&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1gTLvTGH5YJR-HCZVPsqqFtvuOGw0Hy2c_Gx1WwQkUAMtqOuiyX3Dl_MWeI5uB3Nfd_VG6DjrlDvtw=w1200-h630-p&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;External link image preview for generic website.&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: survival Minecraft.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1CrUiHBniouCtC2vncknVcsFT4cf-kVRzb--YlfKXxWA/edit?usp=sharing
Decided to use minecraft since I was in quarantine during the vacation and had time. Needed green dye to mix into cyan dye and so I made a cactus farm and built a factory around it. uses mostly blocks and stuff you can make from the dyes (also a little stone).</description></item><item><title>felled tree</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes only used the picture and the colors of the picture. Plus the little tree dawing I made and a leaf brush. Forgot to stay metallic
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: felled tree Medium: ibispaint x Description: only used the picture and the colors of the picture.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Sandy Point! Population: me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes dropped randomly in death valley on google maps and used that as my reference. Drew a bighorn&amp;rsquo;s head, decided to make it a sassy cowboy.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Welcome to Sandy Point!</description></item><item><title>Ducks by docks</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like ducks. A mama duck loves her ducklings. I love the water texture stamp.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: Ducks by docks Medium: Krita with mouse Description: I like ducks.</description></item><item><title>Jade Jian</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ``
I painted the outline for the sword, tried painting the jade texture, but was displeased with the result, so I went and took a photo of the metal part of a local ww2 bunker and used it to make the texture by adjusting stuff here and there. The handle has the original bunker color</description></item><item><title>Orange jump</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Orange jump ** Medium: Krita with mouse Description: Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.</description></item><item><title>cold inside</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-3-9ea7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-3-9ea7/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint and phone photos.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission Template ``Week:
a view from my house at opposite ends of the year. Could have been a bigger contrast if we had snow, but we don&amp;rsquo;t atm.
``
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Submission Template ``Week: Title: cold inside Medium: ibispaint and phone photos Description: a view from my house at opposite ends of the year.</description></item><item><title>simple angler pog</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission Template ``
just wanted to make something really simple
``
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Submission Template ``Week: 2 Title: simple angler pog Medium: ibispaint x Description: just wanted to make something really simple Social Media: ``</description></item></channel></rss>