<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 14: Absolute Fire on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-14-absolute-fire/</link><description>Recent content in Week 14: Absolute Fire on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-14-absolute-fire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PK Fire</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-14-3200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-14-3200/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I missed the last few weeks so here’s a combination of them as comic!!
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14, 15, 16 Title: PK Fire Medium: Procreate Description: I missed the last few weeks so here’s a combination of them as comic!</description></item><item><title>My Protective Assistant</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was late, sad. &amp;lt;:CattoCry:800558786418835477&amp;gt; Buut I got this done tho! I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved whenever I got the change to draw fire and fire effects. Again, I actually learned a technique on youtube on how to do this, and I think it works out really well for my style! This is dragon Backey (I know they&amp;rsquo;re also cowboys, please don&amp;rsquo;t ask how many alternate universes we have) attacking a rowdy dragon who got too aggro with Prince Astro!</description></item><item><title>Burnt Out</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-14-2f2a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-14-2f2a/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Photograph/Free Photo Editing Thingymajig.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes feeling a bit burnt out
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week: 14 Title: Burnt Out Medium: Photograph/Free Photo Editing Thingymajig Description: feeling a bit burnt out</description></item><item><title>Fusion Flare</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d try drawing them for fun :)
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 13 Title: 😳 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I drew my OC because I like her :) Week 14 Title: Fusion Flare Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;#39;d try drawing them for fun :)</description></item><item><title>A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wrist still hurts, I want to D word
@/pumpkanart on tooter and touch
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain Medium: Procreate Description: wrist still hurts, I want to D word Socials: @/pumpkanart on tooter and touch</description></item><item><title>Anarchy Loves Fire</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate (and DaVinci Resolve).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a piece of an animatic I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on about an anarchist pig and his contemporaries and their relationship with violence. (edit: it&amp;rsquo;s a little heavy so pls don&amp;rsquo;t be wearing headphones if you&amp;rsquo;re not used to heavy music)
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>burnout</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: paper cutting photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is about burnout and how hard it is sometimes to recognise it while in haste. Just remember to take your time, recognise to take care of your body. Don&amp;rsquo;t burn yourself, it&amp;rsquo;ll take a while to recover!
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Cindy Should Pay Me to Moderate</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-14-92c3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-14-92c3/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (Cindy please play this song first).
So of course &amp;ldquo;fire&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;rapping&amp;rdquo; but Cindy also mentioned &amp;ldquo;value&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;contrast&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;bright&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;heart&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;too much.&amp;rdquo; So that&amp;rsquo;s what I used to write the bars.
This is the first non-meme rap song I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written. I could have gone down the meme route but it&amp;rsquo;s more challenging if I welcome people cringing at my lyrics and rap voice.</description></item><item><title>Fiery heart</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/shredarbayn-week-14-1e42/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/shredarbayn-week-14-1e42/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Charcoal &amp;amp; Watercolour on 110gsm Dollar-store Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes With fire on my mind, I thought of Calcifer and how Howl ate the shooting star! (Howl&amp;rsquo;s Moving Castle 2005)
Timelapse https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-7cvM7f3Ps
This was my first endeavor with watercolour and wanted to give it a red hot go (haha) I used a charcoal pencil to free hand the foundation which took me approximately 1 hour to accomplish.</description></item><item><title>Flames of Phlegethos</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Let&amp;rsquo;s draw another one of my D&amp;amp;D characters, because dang it! Why not!? Met Athenaeum; tiefling lore bard/warlock and general wielder of hell fire. So fun fact, when I started digital art about a year ago one of my first pieces was of Ath doing neato flame shit. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d revisit the concept with this one.</description></item><item><title>Hearts on Fire</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-14-c105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-14-c105/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Digital/Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get to finish this up with polish but I enjoyed making the flames.
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Instagram: lithiumreflections Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 **Title: ** Hearts on Fire Medium: Digital/Clip Studio Paint Description: Didn&amp;#39;t quite get to finish this up with polish but I enjoyed making the flames.</description></item><item><title>hey girl bites lip</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-14-d441/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-14-d441/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: procrate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I started this in January but i changed up a lot of things in the last 1 hour like the clouds and i moved like half the facial anatomy Socaisl: https://frogglasses.carrd.co/
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 14 Title: hey girl *bites lip* Medium: procrate I started this in January but i changed up a lot of things in the last 1 hour like the clouds and i moved like half the facial anatomy Socaisl: https://frogglasses.</description></item><item><title>Hungry Firelings</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jonasw-week-14-6699/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jonasw-week-14-6699/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Fire.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Look behind you, they&amp;#39;re the Captain now Medium: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR Description: Return to monke GOLD Week: 14 Title: Hungry Firelings Medium: Fire Description: SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION</description></item><item><title>OH SHIT DID I MAKE IT ON TIME? (actual title: extinguished)</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/eggyolk-week-14-762c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/eggyolk-week-14-762c/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: LMFAO HELP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes AAAAAAAAAAH (actual figured my take would be on the idea of the death of a fire? extinguished. ye)
urmomr1.4505
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 TITLE: OH SHIT DID I MAKE IT ON TIME?</description></item><item><title>Once in a while</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: procreate pocket.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night&amp;hellip; ( ok you can have more than one 😆😆😆)
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Once in a while Medium: procreate pocket Description: have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night.</description></item><item><title>The End of Zeno's Paradox</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, entered, done, a lot of creative endeavors throughout my life, and looking back, it has been quite frustrating, to say the least. This frustration has consumed me over the past several years, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure last year was even the peak.
I&amp;rsquo;ve sold all my camera gear to help make ends meet, threw away my collection of piano sheet music (much to my older brother&amp;rsquo;s surprise), and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to go from here; I think I&amp;rsquo;ve reached my limit, whatever it may be.</description></item><item><title>The Five Virtues</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Pyrography (woodburning).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Illustration based on the Fenghuang, a mythological bird whose body symbolizes the celestial bodies and the five tail feathers representing the five virtues of Confucius. It is said that their appearance signals the coming of a new era.
And what better way to honor my favorite mythological bird than to burn in directly into some wood with fire LOL</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Still very much a work in progress, but posting what&amp;rsquo;s currently on paper. Friend asked if I could make something for his wall, so I sat down and improvised some stuff, did a refined version, then an A3 sketch, now lightboxing it up to watercolor. Didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to do something for week 14, but this happened to line up with having flames, so why not!</description></item><item><title>comfy spot</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/piacine-week-14-e01a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/piacine-week-14-e01a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The fire is warm, comforting, bright. Just warms your cold toes and the tip of the nose after a cold walk along the beach at night time.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 14 Title: comfy spot Medium: Procreate Description: The fire is warm, comforting, bright.</description></item><item><title>My cat is on fire</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Played around with a photo of my cat.
Social Media Twitter: cuporice Twitch: cuporice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: My cat is on fire Medium: Krita Description: Played around with a photo of my cat.</description></item><item><title>That's gotta hurt</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re a monster, a loon. Everybody wants you dead, including me.&amp;rdquo; Oops, more angst! This is just a nightmare Astro has though, Backey never actually says this lol. Decided to use purposely messy lineart in this piece, I think it looks pretty decent! Astro just needs to stop snooping around in places he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; Backey doesn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate him reading his journal.</description></item><item><title>idk</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-14-d670/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-14-d670/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like the concept of this peicr and I&amp;rsquo;m on spring break now so I can acctually participate. My drawing skills arnt the best compared to others in this discord but this still fun improving and taking part
Social Media Instagram: leolayne Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>His name is Shiro 🔥</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked &amp;lt;:UUUdrake:779990724212293642&amp;gt;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: His name is Shiro 🔥 Medium: Clip studio Description: Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked &amp;lt;:UUUdrake:779990724212293642&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>Fire Sale</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita w/ mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Think about the value
Social Media Twitch: jumpingbeansz Instagram: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Fire Sale Medium: Krita w/ mouse Description: Think about the value Social Media: https://www.twitch.com/jumpingbeansz</description></item></channel></rss>