<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DoughYeast on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/doughyeast/</link><description>Recent content in DoughYeast on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/doughyeast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>“you would make the sky a gijinka” - enoki</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ** Used the two references above (an image of a dark sunset and a clear midnight sky)* to create some fantastical characters and I had plans to do two more for **Dawn* and **Noon, but time prevails
I need to stop making non-human things human
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Bog</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, Pixaloop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At Camp Laywick, Raya’s peers are unable to see the silhouette of her distress against the thick of the fog&amp;hellip;
yet she is unable to see the silhouette beneath the water&amp;hellip;
[ I went for a “cover of a horror novel for teen readers” approach and did some video-editing to further portray rhythm and movement &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt; ]</description></item><item><title>Cindy’s Imaginary Friend</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-3-d3de/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-3-d3de/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes no flash photography!!
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Cindy’s Imaginary Friend** Medium: Procreate Description: no flash photography!! Social Media: https://instagram.com/Dough.Yeast || https://twitch.tv/DoughYeast</description></item><item><title>The Deep End</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Manga-inspired illustration where a warrior meets their maker in the Deep Realm &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt;
( Resubmitting the piece I had just done, because I was honestly disappointed in how much of the hatch work was covered and I didn’t want to do another red piece this upcoming week. Had to switch it up! )
https://instagram/dough.</description></item><item><title>Noodle Dancer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: **Noodle Dancer** Medium: Procreate Description: Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛 Social Media: https://instagram.</description></item></channel></rss>