<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 06: Simple Love on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-06-simple-love/</link><description>Recent content in Week 06: Simple Love on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-06-simple-love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do what make you happy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don’t think I’ll have time to do week 8 art cause of midterms but I manage to finish week 6 ; Life can be a little stressful sometimes so take the time to do the things u love; happy late lunar new year everyone 😃
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>A Flash of Peace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-6-68da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-6-68da/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A blanket, the sound of rain, a chill breeze, and distant thunder&amp;hellip; these were the things I summoned up when I thought about simple joys in my life. This is pretty outside my comfort zone but I like the piece still.
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Nian Gao, old and new</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes For this years cny my mom shared some old memories of her grandma making nian gao and having mom man the steamer for hours until it was done. We then made some ourselves as a way of passing on a tradition I never knew we had. My mom doesn&amp;rsquo;t normally share fond memories of her childhood so this felt like something worth commemorating.</description></item><item><title>Tenacity (Year of the Ox)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eyyojimbo-week-6-fd6f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eyyojimbo-week-6-fd6f/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought I’d do a piece that describes the appreciation I have for the resilience of humankind through the struggles that we’ve faced this past year, and how that strength will continue into the next. Going for a Magic the Gathering vibe. Also, this is my first post so hello!
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Perspectives of Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-6-9323/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-6-9323/</guid><description> Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The cubes are symbolic of the fragments of love and how each fragment, although individually &amp;lsquo;rough-edged&amp;rsquo; can together create a smooth whole 🙂
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Title: Perspectives of Love** Medium: Paint Tool SAI Description: The cubes are symbolic of the fragments of love and how each fragment, although individually &amp;#39;rough-edged&amp;#39; can together create a smooth whole 🙂 Socials: @Scimister on twitch</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: Smile and Smile</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-634a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-634a/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ink on paper, 9x12 inches..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ink on paper, 9x12 inches.
Another week, another rush job lol. I had an initial idea but I dumped it since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t execute it. I made this just now.
Anyway&amp;hellip; I tried to recreate the moment I shared with friend and a crush from around 2015. I earlier sent her a message apologizing for &amp;ldquo;being weird&amp;rdquo; (not my words) after being scolded by someone for acting weird towards two girls.</description></item><item><title>Ghosties</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was meant to be a Week 5 submission but it fits Week 6 for me too. I love my OCs, and it&amp;rsquo;s been great to have them as a creative &amp;amp; emotional outlet! (Also love being able to finish art even if it&amp;rsquo;s not on time LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>It's just a painting why does it have to have a title? But fine, the title as a noise, like horses neigh kind of.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Trad art, watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Interpretation of the prompt; I sat down and did some painting that I simply loved doing, no research, no finding references, no working through a concept, just doing a sketch and putting paint on paper, feeling a harmonious flow in the work itself unlike the frustration I usually feel while doing art. It was kind of nice.</description></item><item><title>Love in the air</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-6-834b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-6-834b/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: : Ibis paint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes twitch: leo_d3mom
based from girl in red . I&amp;rsquo;m part of the LGBTQ+ community and it basically represents us
Sorry the is a mess also I&amp;rsquo;m a growing artist so sorry if it&amp;rsquo;s bad it cringe
Medium : Ibis paint x
Sorry the is a mess
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Midnight Magic Musings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The late nights we stay up talking about D&amp;amp;D. Those quiet moments when the rest of the world is asleep. We bounce dumb ideas off each other just to see where they&amp;rsquo;ll land. You have no idea how much I appreciate my Resident Wizard&amp;hellip;
On the art side of things; I really enjoy drawing characters and their interactions, and believe it or not, I do like drawing cute things 😛</description></item><item><title>Paper Aeroplanes demo.mp3, collab with @papapastry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud.
&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1v7MNRHeg6fDwUsURPJAf1XSptglTolwA1KtohM_4Rbk/edit?usp=sharing&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/DzStfDmiFSHCKCch-gREcsborTcl4f1HQagguSE9Jlm9flwfPjFpq4w2C6VW5_KVyXIZQ5YM_maGPw=w1200-h630-p&amp;quot; alt=&amp;quot;External link image preview for generic website.&amp;quot; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A demo track of our collab song &amp;lsquo;Paper Aeroplanes&amp;rsquo;, capturing an instance between two lovers and what their simple but gentle love brings.
paper aeroplanes DEMO track: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/fuck-so-late-god-fucking-damnit the lyrics were based off poetry i wrote: https://docs.</description></item><item><title>Paper Pond</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Origami + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Going back to my first art love - paper. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been surrounded by paper and origami ever since I was kid, and wanted to pay homage to both my roots and the medium that has so much potential. Also I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting a piece to bring in the two parts of my heritage in one piece; my last name roughly translates to &amp;lsquo;ferry across the river&amp;rsquo; and my chinese name means &amp;lsquo;yellow love lotus&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Roleplay! (and a puppet show I suppose)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes After a lot of thinking about the prompt, I&amp;rsquo;d say that I love to roleplay! Dyno and I rp all the time, so I drew us performing a puppet show! Just to give you an idea, there are 723,445 words across all our rp transcripts including ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t finished lmao
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Self portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;rsquo;s still a long way to go. so here it is first time drawing myself haha
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6- Simple love Title: Self portrait Description: Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;#39;s still a long way to go.</description></item><item><title>Slice of Life</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Cutting close again, wowie! Oh well, I like how this came out even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a few doodles of me and my best friend! She&amp;rsquo;s the light of my life and I love her with all my heart, she makes me so incredibly happy and has probably indirectly saved my life. Oh, and she&amp;rsquo;s in the server, so expect a long-ass wall of appreciation in discussions eventually!</description></item><item><title>solemn night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/okie.dokie.enoki-week-6-42f0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/okie.dokie.enoki-week-6-42f0/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i didn’t want to study so i made this ❤️ pov: you’re god but also a third wheel&amp;lt;/3
Social Media Instagram: okie.dokie.enoki Twitch: okie_dokie_enoki Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week: 6 title: solemn night medium: procreate description: i didn’t want to study so i made this ❤️ pov: you’re god but also a third wheel&amp;lt;/3 social: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Sweet Nothings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Modelling Clay (Sculpey).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A lot of people give chocolates for Valentines and other romantic holidays. I&amp;rsquo;m not a huge fan of chocolate but I really like the little gourmet ones. I think these ones will last a little longer than most.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Week 6 &lt;:eyeleft:800396950012035081> &lt;:mylips:800398060710526976> &lt;:eyeleft:800396950012035081></title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-6-ca60/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-6-ca60/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The earliest time I can remember myself loving drawing was when I was 5 and completely immersed in the given task of drawing a yellow house with a red roof, with apple trees, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite quarter sun. Something about the way the pencil felt scraping across the paper encapsulated me, and before I knew it, 3 hours had past before I even looked away from the page.</description></item><item><title>Dreams in TechieLand</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-6-f17c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-6-f17c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes San Francisco, sunsets, stargazing, and day dreaming are what inspired this piece. 🙂 The simple things.
Social Media Instagram: austeezus Twitter: psykoframe Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: Dreams in TechieLand Medium: Krita Description: San Francisco, sunsets, stargazing, and day dreaming are what inspired this piece.</description></item><item><title>Simple Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</guid><description>Direct link to a .pdf file.
Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, and publication.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t like Valentines Days but I wanted to talk about what I loved, pets! Animals show love in such wonderful ways and I&amp;rsquo;m so happy!!!!
The main submission is a lil A6 zine you can fold yourself if you have a b+W a4 printer!</description></item><item><title>Cyber Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes reminds me of my best friend in the world (we were friends for almost 13 years, till they&amp;rsquo;ve moved to Egypt) we still talk, but it&amp;rsquo;s not like before cz we&amp;rsquo;re both a bit busy. Like that heart, our friendship became cold and hollow, with the screens being our only connection. Lol, that&amp;rsquo;s so depressive; anyway, Alexa play Driver&amp;rsquo;s license by Olivia Rodrigo.</description></item><item><title>inanimate objects that give me comfort</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</guid><description> Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;rsquo;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: inanimate objects that give me comfort Medium: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil Description: I don&amp;#39;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;#39;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down</description></item><item><title>Magical girl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing character design, and with simple love the first thing I thought of was Madoka and magical girls. For ‘balance’ I made her very symmetrical. She’s inspired by roses. I can imagine her on a team of flower magical girls fighting against weed monsters of the week. Very Tokyo mew style! I wanna draw their whole team&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Everlasting Hope</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night. Why is it called Everlasting Hope? well, that&amp;rsquo;s just something i need in life i guess. hope you enjoyed it!
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6 Title: Everlasting Hope Medium: Photoshop Description: I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night.</description></item><item><title>Ducks by docks</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like ducks. A mama duck loves her ducklings. I love the water texture stamp.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: Ducks by docks Medium: Krita with mouse Description: I like ducks.</description></item><item><title>It's Not Living (If It's Not With You)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-6-185c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-6-185c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to do a non paint style for this one and was hugely hugely inspired by elliotisacoolguy on twitch and made something in his style. The title comes from this great The 1975 song, recc you all listen to it!. I made a few options just to make it a bit more interesting</description></item><item><title>The introspection of self, the different facades of life and embrace of the multifaceted appearences</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Video of beansz wearing clothing (aka i ran out of mediums, time to recycle).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In life we wear many masks (or shirts cuz i dont know the art of 变脸, aka chinese face mask changing), they are the many aspects of self, whether or not we like it or not. The introspection of the multiple sides is what makes us individuals and whole.</description></item></channel></rss>