<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mrtnong on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/artists/mrtnong/</link><description>Recent content in mrtnong on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/artists/mrtnong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jade Temple</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I started this piece by chaotically&amp;lt;a:ultrafastparrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple. it&amp;rsquo;s pretty messy &amp;lt;a:Bonk:769829350622232587&amp;gt;
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 5 Title: Jade Temple Medium: Digital (Procreate) Description: I started this piece by *chaotically*&amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple.</description></item><item><title>cat&lt;a:B8vibe:776693937498095637> (cant think of a title xd)</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes It&amp;rsquo;s my first time creating something graphic art-y I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt;
(might stream sometime in 2021 &amp;lt;a:ultrafastparrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; )
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: cat&amp;lt;a:B8_vibe:776693937498095637&amp;gt; (cant think of a title xd) Medium: Procreate Description: It&amp;#39;s my first time creating something *graphic art-y* I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt; Socials: https://www.</description></item></channel></rss>