<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 09: Bold Strokes on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-09-bold-strokes/</link><description>Recent content in Week 09: Bold Strokes on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-09-bold-strokes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome to the brave new world of me</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.
Social Media Instagram: billelhambli Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Welcome to the brave new world of me Medium: Affinity photo Description: My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.</description></item><item><title>7/11 Burrito</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-9-d52c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-9-d52c/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Bold strokes&amp;rdquo; sounds upbeat, aggressive, complex, and coloured by live instrumentals.
Before the &amp;lsquo;rona there was live music. For those who have not been in a crowd or performed contemporary music, there is nothing like it. Every mistake, every ad lib: the energy is secondary to nothing. It is extremely obvious when watching some of the best bands out there that everybody is having so much fun.</description></item><item><title>ANIME AM I RIGHT</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams. wow pretty eyes yeet. huff huff huff join my giveaway LOL
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 **Title: ANIME AM I RIGHT** Medium: digital painting Description: 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams.</description></item><item><title>Be Bold and Believe</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tomorrow I will compete in my Jiu Jisu tournament so I try to keep my mind calm and did something related to my feelings. the moment I&amp;rsquo;m on the mat is the moment I feel alive. 6 mins. only 6 mins to see how far I have become compared to myself yesterday. Control my nerves and believe in my techniques, execute fast and believe I&amp;rsquo;ve got this.</description></item><item><title>Color factory</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</guid><description>View on Google Docs.
Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: survival Minecraft.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1CrUiHBniouCtC2vncknVcsFT4cf-kVRzb--YlfKXxWA/edit?usp=sharing
Decided to use minecraft since I was in quarantine during the vacation and had time. Needed green dye to mix into cyan dye and so I made a cactus farm and built a factory around it. uses mostly blocks and stuff you can make from the dyes (also a little stone). Tried to make it look like it pollutes the river (dug out custom rivers and had them flow into the swamp biome for extra dirty effect).</description></item><item><title>Flame Soul spirit</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lyfeu-week-9-0514/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lyfeu-week-9-0514/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A soul entrapped in a body of rock burning its desire to live once more enabling the rock to become its own , the colour at the top i feel is where the soul of the fire and spirit clashing and trying to compromise with each other to both live within the body
twitch/tv/Lyfeu</description></item><item><title>Hi! I like shorts! They're comfy and easy to wear!</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/winsome-week-9-ca4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/winsome-week-9-ca4a/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (Photo set).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Celebrating the 25th Anniversary of Pokemon and myself, with a Pokemon that I like a lot. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;m still a youngster trainer class.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>I DON'T HAVE TIME TO COME UP WITH A TITLE ALREADY LATE AS-IS oh hang on CHOKE ME LIKE YOU HATE ME obviously sorry</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/arancil-week-9-7061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/arancil-week-9-7061/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil, watercolor, acrylics, promarkers, various fineliners, ink, hands, anger, frustration, stress, acceptance, coffee.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so this kind of didn&amp;rsquo;t happen as intended, just smashed together everything that had color on it
consider that bit inspired by @DynoLoafer
Also @jonasw was my spirit animal
Social Media Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Instagram: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Introspection</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Did something more simple this week since I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling a little burned out. I wanted to do something cooler for this week cuz I liked the prompt buuuut I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t. Either way, this piece was partially inspired by Omori&amp;rsquo;s art style, hope people like it lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>iPod Nano</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;rsquo;d enjoy from the prompt. (Late as usual LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: iPod Nano Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: I&amp;#39;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;#39;d enjoy from the prompt.</description></item><item><title>POV you find another VHS tape, and your sleep deprived self slots it in the player…</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes !!!epilepsy warning!!!
rhythm and flow? say no more.. didn’t have much time this week so this was a very quickly put-together and rushed but i found this super funky cmyk filter on insta… this was such a headache to edit lol, but hope you enjoy!! you asked for statement so… i look like a giant but i promise you it’s 60% camera angle 40% my 8” pole heels xd</description></item><item><title>wikipedia</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</guid><description> Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes yo who else misses hatsune miku
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: wikipedia Medium: Procreate Description: yo who else misses hatsune miku Social Media: @/pumpkanart on twitter and twitch</description></item><item><title>Chromatic Dragon</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is what happens when I stare at Hydro74&amp;rsquo;s work for long enough&amp;hellip; Something very different for me, but I really love how this turned out! A CMYK Dragon, just for you Cindy 😘 Technically based of the Black Dragons from D&amp;amp;D cause I&amp;rsquo;m a nerd. Enjoy!
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>CMY</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-9-7236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-9-7236/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wow this hurts my eyes. This was meant to be like a 10 min sketch and it looks like one, but I spent more like 30 mins on it.
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: CMY Medium: Photoshop Description: Wow this hurts my eyes.</description></item><item><title>Repetition, Reminisce, Reflection</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Suminagashi (Japanese ink marbling technique) on handmade paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;It reflects me. It reflects you&amp;hellip;Two lines become one&amp;rdquo; - Mirrors by STUTS (ft. SUMIN, Daichi Yamamoto &amp;amp; CHINZA DOPENESS) (the song I was vibin to while making this piece: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wdwzLaljOzw) While working alongside printmaking friends on a group zoom call, I was suddenly taken back to a time where we were all gathered together at our university&amp;rsquo;s studio, working until the sky was dark and blasting music three octaves too loud.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation - Welcome To Hell</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to express in one way or another this powerlessness I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling for a very long time now. I based part of the concept and the title from a scene in the video game Spec Ops: The Line.
Social Media Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Instagram: and Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Berry Dragon</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-9-8bb3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-9-8bb3/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Adapted public domain artwork (https://flic.kr/p/hS7KBV) - given fresh lines and CYMK colors.
twitter lireflections, IG/tumblr lithiumreflections
Social Media Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Instagram: lithiumreflections Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 **Title: ** Berry Dragon Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: Adapted public domain artwork (https://flic.</description></item><item><title>Important Dream</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jonasw-week-9-8e62/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jonasw-week-9-8e62/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat. washi tape of betrayal).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Katamari Damacy (Song) Fanart, wanted something big and bright and cheerful. Also wanted practice drawing general &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo;, and write some japanese characters.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Important Dream Medium: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Collage</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Wow I&amp;rsquo;m the first one submitting this week? That&amp;rsquo;s weird. Anyways, I decided for this week to draw a bunch of dragons because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide on just one with all the thumbnails I made! Each piece has it&amp;rsquo;s own title, as well as a color palette of only 10 colors (9 not including black) and wow it makes this bright!</description></item><item><title>Judgement</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-9-3785/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-9-3785/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: When I thought of what to draw for this theme I thought cyberpunk and cool flashing lights. I realized I wasn&amp;rsquo;t that good at the subject yet and would need time to develop it so instead I went to my mor comfortable style.
This piece represents an innocent girl who never did anything wrong until she made a single mistake.</description></item><item><title>This is the literal worst shit i have created, i think my parent think im weird.</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw a dude making cool advertisement with a TV as background and thought &amp;quot; hmmmm seems easy&amp;quot; then i proceed to do stupid things. my parents saw me do stupid things, and editing is hell. overall i rate the experience 4/10, maybe i would increase the score if I were more familiar with video editing</description></item></channel></rss>