<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soleilboo on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/soleilboo/</link><description>Recent content in soleilboo on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/soleilboo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dobby and me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is how I feel everytime I hug my cat. He is a giant things to my heart! Yeah sometimes I wanted to be smaller just to cuddle with him 🥰✨💜
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>still life</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project. All photos for reference taken by me. My DMs are open if anyone want to join.
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week15 Title: still life Medium: watercolour Description: Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project.</description></item><item><title>Once in a while</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: procreate pocket.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night&amp;hellip; ( ok you can have more than one 😆😆😆)
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Once in a while Medium: procreate pocket Description: have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night.</description></item><item><title>“uhmmm Mine!!! It’s mine”</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-13-62e9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-13-62e9/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: digital,photoshop+procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I’m late but here it is
the title said it all I guess 🥺🥺🥺
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: I’m late but here it is Week: 13 Title: “uhmmm Mine!</description></item><item><title>Disappear</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-12-f36b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-12-f36b/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes English is my second language and I’m having fun with all suffix and prefix. Google said “dis” = “a Latin prefix meaning “apart,” “asunder,” “away,” “utterly,” or having a privative, negative, or reversing force&amp;hellip;. Also my art always revolving around my daily life so this work inspired by this week little getaway trip&amp;hellip; I’m disappeared into nature now&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Hydrangea Star Gazer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you. I love you to the moon and back.
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Hydrangea Star Gazer Medium: Watercolour Description: There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you.</description></item><item><title>Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 10: Title: Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them. Medium: Photoshop Social: https://www.twitch.tv/soleilboo</description></item><item><title>Be Bold and Believe</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tomorrow I will compete in my Jiu Jisu tournament so I try to keep my mind calm and did something related to my feelings. the moment I&amp;rsquo;m on the mat is the moment I feel alive. 6 mins. only 6 mins to see how far I have become compared to myself yesterday. Control my nerves and believe in my techniques, execute fast and believe I&amp;rsquo;ve got this.</description></item><item><title>Wall- E fan Art</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so as soon as I look at the photo the light caught my eyes immediately. I have been thinking about Wall-E a lot this week because of Do-E, and then I saw Jump in the bin submission which is &amp;ldquo;trashbin&amp;rdquo; and then my brain just blink and connect everything together&amp;hellip;.Here we go, my boy Wall-E using the photo supplied.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Everyone have their own desert to carry. And flower can grow in the desert you know 🙂
Inspiration: orange sand colour of Australian desert and Goodenia-one of Australian desert Plants Combined with my goal of digital portrait painting this year.
Hope you all enjoy this work.
And yes flowers can grow in the desert.</description></item><item><title>Self portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;rsquo;s still a long way to go. so here it is first time drawing myself haha
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6- Simple love Title: Self portrait Description: Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;#39;s still a long way to go.</description></item><item><title>for this portrait. Can someone name it?I just took on the meaning of Jade Stone which bring good luck, peace and harmony just like a smile did.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-ba11/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-ba11/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5- Royal Green- Jade Stone I don&amp;#39;t have title for this portrait. Can someone name it?I just took on the meaning of Jade Stone which bring good luck, peace and harmony just like a smile did.</description></item></channel></rss>