<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 07: Disturbed Desert on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-07-disturbed-desert/</link><description>Recent content in Week 07: Disturbed Desert on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-07-disturbed-desert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Desert~~ (Creative I know)~~</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-7-c62c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-7-c62c/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Keeping a focus on form, shape, and color contrast.
IG/tumblr: lithiumreflections
((Oops initially uploaded with a layer missing))
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 **Title: ** Desert~~ (Creative I know)~~ Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: Keeping a focus on form, shape, and color contrast.</description></item><item><title>Angry Bird</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-7-fbb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-7-fbb3/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ballpoint and hand smudge.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Who is the intruder in the desert? Is it the bird? Is it the sun? Is it Super Mario Bros?
No thanks
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Angry Bird Medium: Ballpoint and hand smudge Description: Who is the intruder in the desert?</description></item><item><title>Academy, Disrepair</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;rsquo;t normally draw backgrounds. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a colour scheme I liked that worked with the monochrome sketch so I kept it minimal.
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Academy, Disrepair Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;#39;t normally draw backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Desert Plains</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-7-a9a8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-7-a9a8/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I fucking love NieR:Automata.
Social Media Instagram: poruchan_920 Twitch: poru_chan Twitter: poruchan09 Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Desert Plains Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I fucking love NieR:Automata. Social Media: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>desert strands</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 80 minute speed draw this time happy with the result though ! inspired by a lot of the stippling i&amp;rsquo;ve seen entered by the amazing artists in this week&amp;rsquo;s submissions ! attempted to tie the sand dunes into the hair? no real reason why other than i thought it might be fun to try ;; (to whom it may concern at turnitin, originally submitted at 11:57pm)</description></item><item><title>Dune Surfing</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</guid><description> Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes has anyone ever tried it?
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Medium: clip studio Title: Dune Surfing Description: has anyone ever tried it?</description></item><item><title>Footprints</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-7-9d88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-7-9d88/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes YouTube External Link (Headphones will benefit you for this song).
&amp;ldquo;Desert&amp;rdquo; to me means the mixolydian mode (a tonal &amp;ldquo;pattern&amp;rdquo;). You know, like The Beatles (Norwegian Wood, I Feel Fine) and a lot of classic rock around that era. &amp;ldquo;Space&amp;rdquo; sounds like space emulation: reverb. The theme also influenced the lyrics greatly, which were written before the music.</description></item><item><title>Hey you! Yeah, up here!</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-aa73/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-aa73/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I didn&amp;rsquo;t really get to post many wips for this piece because Discord decided it was too unholy to be seen before it was fully developed, but here it is! Did a screenshot redraw of a place called Scorched Gorge, which a desert area in Bugsnax :3</description></item><item><title>placeholder edit later</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Scene: Oh no, one of the remnant forces of the humans are being hunted by the reptilian empire led by Hiss Majesty - but the sand starts rumbling and what rises out of it?
Three panel piece, there&amp;rsquo;s some storyboarding done for the pre-first-panel storytelling as well, but cut it down to two of the nicest looking key panels (+ a dramatic final one).</description></item><item><title>SOL 0</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This morning the Perseverance Rover landed safely in the Jezero Crater on Mars. It&amp;rsquo;s NASA&amp;rsquo;s fifth Rover to land on the red planet and, other than Curiosity, is the only thing &amp;lsquo;alive&amp;rsquo; on the dusty world.
Art wise, a bit of a quick and dirty one. (Was starting to run out of time 😅) I used the 3D model viewer of Perseverance to get the rover as accurate as possible.</description></item><item><title>Strange Sands</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ink on paper, a comic!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love alliteration lol!
hey isn&amp;rsquo;t is kinda mysterious? I got this idea from when crabs would dig holes at the beach and spit out the water. Finding that in the desert would be super creepy&amp;hellip; also stippling is hard. I do really like this though and hope you do too!</description></item><item><title>The Sandstorm</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TW FOR &amp;ldquo;BLOOD&amp;rdquo; (just in case)
This sandstorm is fogging up my judgement. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see you. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see my goddamn hand out in front of me&amp;hellip; Please. Don&amp;rsquo;t blame yourself, none of this is your fault. I was the one who killed them, can&amp;rsquo;t you see the blood? Just.</description></item><item><title>Three Celebrations (Change)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography, Clay Figure &amp;amp; Cake.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 3 white chocolate caramel souffle cakes to celebrate three different events.
Growth: 1st cake for Herschel&amp;rsquo;s birthday, sadly we missed his birthday party due to lockdown.
Goodbyes: 2nd cake for my roommate who decided his job wasn&amp;rsquo;t worth his sanity anymore and quit.
New Beginnings: 3rd cake for my friend Pete who&amp;rsquo;s moving to a new place!</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Everyone have their own desert to carry. And flower can grow in the desert you know 🙂
Inspiration: orange sand colour of Australian desert and Goodenia-one of Australian desert Plants Combined with my goal of digital portrait painting this year.
Hope you all enjoy this work.
And yes flowers can grow in the desert.</description></item><item><title>Rain Over the Desert</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-7-42e5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-7-42e5/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A panorama of a rainstorm passing through the Sonoran Desert
500px External Link Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Rain Over the Desert Medium: Photography Description: A panorama of a rainstorm passing through the Sonoran Desert Social Media: https://500px.</description></item><item><title>Resistance 3: When The Lands Become Graveyards</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-6498/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-6498/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes @rjmmendoza on IG/Twitter | A1EwanRichards on Twitch
It&amp;rsquo;s not a desert in the typical sense. It&amp;rsquo;s an amalgam of sugar cane farms and the concept of &amp;ldquo;peace of the cemetery,&amp;rdquo; referring to a quote by St. Oscar Romero. The title is a rough translation of a poem by Filipino poet Axel Pinpin, originally titled &amp;ldquo;Kung Puntod na ang Lupa&amp;rdquo; (literal: If the Land is a Tomb&amp;quot;).</description></item><item><title>Seconds in Sand</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (shot w/ a Canon 40D).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s often times when I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in an internal &amp;lsquo;desert&amp;rsquo;, where ideas don&amp;rsquo;t come easily and time slips by. Yet somehow the creative spark is always hovering in between this barren space and the looming deadline, and often I just find myself having to be patient for the right moment rather than to grasp at the sands.</description></item><item><title>Skull</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-7-c59a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-7-c59a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes big skull&amp;hellip; in desert&amp;hellip; giant? Who kno&amp;hellip;.?
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Skull Medium: Procreate Description: big skull... in desert... giant? Who kno....? Socials: @paintsepsi on everything!</description></item><item><title>Sunset at Calico Desert</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes When I heard the prompt was about deserts and what lived in them I immediately thought of stardew valley! I love that big dragon skeleton, hungering for the sun. I was aiming for a phone background look, so please feel free to use it!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Sandy Point! Population: me</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes dropped randomly in death valley on google maps and used that as my reference. Drew a bighorn&amp;rsquo;s head, decided to make it a sassy cowboy.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Welcome to Sandy Point!</description></item><item><title>Ghost City (ft bad cropping)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The huge creature was a character that I had written about, inspired by League of Legend&amp;rsquo;s RekSai and Pokemon&amp;rsquo;s Garchomp. styles influenced by chinese/japanese calligraphy cuz was triggered that i had to do a calligraphy work in non-chinese/japanese materials.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Desert heat</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: blender.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i wanted to try a new something new so instead of photoshop i used blender this is my first time using the program and i think it came out pretty good i dont really have a but i hope I did a ok job 😊
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>