<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 01: Yellow Lines on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-01-yellow-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Week 01: Yellow Lines on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-01-yellow-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>It Spins</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-1-d71e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-1-d71e/</guid><description> The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: 3D Digital.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 3 hoops that are spinning on the X, Y and Z axis respectfully
Social Media Twitch: magus_hellwalker Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 (I know I&amp;#39;m late) Title: It Spins Medium: 3D Digital Description: 3 hoops that are spinning on the X, Y and Z axis respectfully</description></item><item><title>Luminated Darkness</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-1-ce9d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-1-ce9d/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So I finally finished my week 1 prompt. Full time momma here. But wanted to share even tho I’m late !
pretty much the darkness symbolizes my emotions how they tend to take over. The sun here is shining light and making me see the positive things in life.
Twitch:MoonlitNarcy
Social Media Instagram: moonlit_narcy Twitter: moonlit_narcy Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Four of Pumpkins</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to do something elegant with pattern. However, when I streamed this like an hour ago, I was aggressively persuaded (bullied) into adding more pumpkins, and now it’s a tarot card of the suit of pumpkins. 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>sunny day, pouring rain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to try play with the rain patterns but rushed them a little. References are godsend. I was going for a minimal editorial look and limited pallette because those are outside of my comfort zone.
Social Media Instagram: jrchlp.png Twitter: jorchaelp Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Distance...</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/madboi-week-1-608f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/madboi-week-1-608f/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: : Traditional (fine liner, artist pitt pen, paper).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Distancing concept from the WiFi Symbol applied to current situation
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week : 1 Title : Distance... Medium : Traditional (fine liner, artist pitt pen, paper) Description : Distancing concept from the WiFi Symbol applied to current situation</description></item><item><title>egg galaxy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow! with some stars.
rybaris
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: egg galaxy Medium: csp Description: a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow!</description></item><item><title>Noodle Dancer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: **Noodle Dancer** Medium: Procreate Description: Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛 Social Media: https://instagram.</description></item><item><title>Plaid &amp; Lace sans Lace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was originally going for &amp;ldquo;Plaid &amp;amp; Lace&amp;rdquo; as my keywords, but &amp;hellip; no way I&amp;rsquo;m putting down work on the &amp;ldquo;Lace&amp;rdquo; part as well. The yellow is &amp;ldquo;Gold Star&amp;rdquo; ink from Diamine, the rest is fineliner, uni-ball for white and some cobalt+ultramarine for shaded areas.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Rat 1 and Rat 2</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes gay rat wedding
I went a bit crazy on SAI which is a huge guilty pleasure. In the end it&amp;rsquo;s a bit cute and a good mood so I&amp;rsquo;m happy with what I made. Looking forward definitely going to use more references since i should, this is a bit surreal.
@fiveclawd</description></item><item><title>upon sunflowers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: digital, procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes going for simple w line work + pantone yellow. i also really love sunflowers. like a lot.
an accompanying haiku:
like the sunflowers / i look towards the sunlight /
to moving forwards / Social Media Instagram: charmandaar_ Twitch: charmandaar Twitter: charmandaar_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Week 1 submission 👁️ 👄 👁️</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-1-3d18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-1-3d18/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes done in ~6 hours.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: Week 1 submission 👁️ 👄 👁️ Medium: Procreate Description: done in ~6 hours. Socials: urmom</description></item><item><title>sparkly mandrake</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes here&amp;rsquo;s a sparkly mandrake gif that I made, file was too big so I had to resize it to fit
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: sparkly mandrake Medium: photoshop Description: here&amp;#39;s a sparkly mandrake gif that I made, file was too big so I had to resize it to fit</description></item><item><title>Honey, I'm Home!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw my oc in a dress, so I drew him in a dress! He likes wearing dresses from time to time. The sketchy plants in the bg are mostly to fill the space, but I thought they would look nice :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Just a Peep</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/boyf-week-1-b79d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/boyf-week-1-b79d/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca64.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought for a second, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do though I knew I wanted to use my OC. It sorta just flowed and this was the outcome. I kinda like it though sorta don&amp;rsquo;t lol.
Social Media Instagram: _daniluvsyou Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>New Year's Compass</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-1-8366/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-1-8366/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes An eight point radial design in the style of a compass rose. Lines are all in the Pantone Yellow, while the background is two shades of blue: classic blue (2020&amp;rsquo;s Pantone color of the year) inside the design and a darker contrasted blue outside of it.
IG/Tumblr @Lithiumreflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Origin Point</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Processing (program) + Java.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Circle created with Java code that randomizes the spiral variance and the stroke; I wanted to challenge myself to learn a new programming language this year since I enjoy using them for both work and side projects. I&amp;rsquo;d love to be able to do a different medium for each week if I&amp;rsquo;m able.</description></item><item><title>Yellow Ice Bar</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-1-7b09/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-1-7b09/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Switch Harv&amp;rsquo;s Island.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I cannot art so here are yellow ACNH vibes, maybe (big maybe) I&amp;rsquo;ll actually draw for future weeks
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: Yellow Ice Bar Medium: Switch Harv&amp;#39;s Island Description: I cannot art so here are yellow ACNH vibes, maybe (big maybe) I&amp;#39;ll actually draw for future weeks</description></item><item><title>flush</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/malorbaker-week-1-86f3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/malorbaker-week-1-86f3/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: ms paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sideways yellow waterfall there is harmony in all the whoosh&amp;rsquo;s and they are also lines i win
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: flush Medium: ms paint Description: sideways yellow waterfall there is harmony in all the whoosh&amp;#39;s and they are also lines i win</description></item><item><title>Objects</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ramen-week-1-c830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ramen-week-1-c830/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i made this at 2 am. there is something special about this drawing. i really like all of these objects. i love ducks, bananas, stars, the sun, sunflowers, lemon, and cheese. i dont really like paprika tbh, but its yellow anyways :3
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Profile</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-1-cce9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-1-cce9/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate Digital Painting.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Basically a portrait of a model but using the Pantone colour of the year as the background. I thought the brightness of the yellow really stood out and so I ended up really appreciating the way it turned out!
(Sorry hope I did this right lol)
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Bowl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: MS Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes simple geometry shape of a bowl highlighted using pre-programmed algorithm of MS Paint, the yellow used to demonstrate the 3 dimensionality of bowl&amp;hellip; aaaa theres a cat in it &amp;hellip;. oh welp if it fits, it sits ¯_(ツ)_/¯
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>