<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 15: Back to Basics on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-15-back-to-basics/</link><description>Recent content in Week 15: Back to Basics on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/themes/week-15-back-to-basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>sometimes art is not worth having a mental breakdown over</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So&amp;hellip; I was late for once. Annnd this wasn&amp;rsquo;t even what I was working on, this is just that same warm up I posted a while back. I probably should&amp;rsquo;ve just posted this last week so I could avoid falling into a depression after crumbling under the pressure, but&amp;hellip; it wasn&amp;rsquo;t polished, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want my work on the other piece to go to waste.</description></item><item><title>Red Delicious with a Red Delicious</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Whoopsies, I&amp;rsquo;m late again! Oh well, school finals are happening right now and, particularly in math (I&amp;rsquo;m a grade ahead of my peers in it) homework likes to pile up. But, even if I&amp;rsquo;m late, I know that this would&amp;rsquo;ve came out really bad if I rushed it, so I took my time and.</description></item><item><title>tomatoes are the potatoes of fruit</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-15-0547/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-15-0547/</guid><description> Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: gw acrylic paint for mini figures.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes tomato potato
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 15 Title: tomatoes are the potatoes of fruit Medium: gw acrylic paint for mini figures Description: tomato potato</description></item><item><title>Bread, Butter, Boysenberry</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Food.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My grandfather loved boysenberry jam, so I made a simple tribute to him and my favorite meal, breakfast. Used a knife and jam to create the basic form of a boysenberry, with bread as the &amp;ldquo;canvas&amp;rdquo; and butter to prevent it from getting soggy. Jammin with jam lol
Social Media Instagram: karen_tsugawa Twitch: vectorong Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Hades</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-15-a473/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/papapastry-week-15-a473/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud.
Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Fruity Loops Studio 20.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Fruit doesn&amp;rsquo;t really make a lot of noise, at least nothing that sounds pleasant. My banana ocarina was not shelf-stable.
But I get what Cindy&amp;rsquo;s trying to do here. The analogue for basics for musicians is, I dunno, first pieces? Drills? Fur Elise? Wonderwall? Well, I learned music production using FL Studio (Fruity Loops) which is a funny coincidence, so I&amp;rsquo;ll use that.</description></item><item><title>hEhE LEmon bUTt but also strawberry and coffee is kinda vibes</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/eggyolk-week-15-69ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/eggyolk-week-15-69ac/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes been having late nights with strawberries and coffees. ALSO HONESTLY HIGHKEY INSPIRED BY MIMI&amp;rsquo;S LEMON OBVIOUSLY HEHEHEHE, and some shirt designs that i peeped a couple nights ago.
urmom 15.0 hurhur
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 15 Title: hEhE LEmon bUTt but also strawberry and coffee is kinda vibes Medium: Procreate Description: been having late nights with strawberries and coffees.</description></item><item><title>leeeeemons</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: relief printing on note books.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes taking it easy this week with something i found relaxing and i guess soothing? something like the lemon honey i was drinking while sick. make some stamps! have a good time! take care of yourself
Social Media Twitter: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Instagram: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>still life</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project. All photos for reference taken by me. My DMs are open if anyone want to join.
Social Media Twitch: soleilboo Instagram: soleil.boo Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week15 Title: still life Medium: watercolour Description: Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project.</description></item><item><title>Tightrope banana.</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paper, permanent marker..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, life happened and I forgot. Here take this shitpost instead. Balance!
Social Media Twitter: cuporice Twitch: cuporice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 15 Title: Tightrope banana. Medium: Paper, permanent marker. Description: Sorry, life happened and I forgot.</description></item><item><title>Whats Left : Left handed Leftovers, vol. 1</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: markers + paper in gif.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m still dealing with wrist pain so I&amp;rsquo;m making the most of it. What do I have left? A whole other side of my body to learn to draw with! Shout out to LeftHandedToons, a comic site that I spent a lot of time on as a kid. This one&amp;rsquo;s for you</description></item><item><title>Resistance 4 - Sometimes, The Heart Yearns For Mangoes</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A change of pace, I think? I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really pinpoint any concept to execute for this week, but this imagery had lingered to me for a few days. Then I also remembered a 1994 poem I read from a book whose title for this I based it from.
The poem is about homesickness and wishing for a better world from a faraway place, a faraway country.</description></item><item><title>Still Life Succulents</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-15-438c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/lithium-week-15-438c/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes No fruit around and I decided I&amp;rsquo;d go more for the still life angle of the assignment using my succulent pot as a base (yes, it&amp;rsquo;s sparse for now, but it&amp;rsquo;ll have new cuttings soon.)
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Instagram: lithiumreflections Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>#1 Sour Lemon</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mimichair-week-15-906c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/mimichair-week-15-906c/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Adobe Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I actually love the sourness of lemons ~ that is what lemons are known for too. What if we could give an award to a lemon? that would be judged by sourness wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it 😌
Social Media Twitch: mimichair Instagram: mimichair.art Twitter: mimikuchan Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Durian at sea</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decide to try something new this week so i tried animation for the first time&amp;hellip;yea&amp;hellip;its hard 🥲 Could only use 24 frames cause of clipstudio&amp;rsquo;s restriction. Does anyone have any recommendation for 2d animation software? 🎞️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>illiteracy</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: chinese calligraphy.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The art philosophy known as &amp;ldquo;Nanyang Art Style&amp;rdquo; is a fusion of western and eastern art style. Often, pioneers of this art styles employed western mediums and materials, paired with subject matters of eastern origins / things you commonly see in asia. Some of the pioneering artists are Georgette Chen, Liu Kang etc.</description></item></channel></rss>