<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Farewell Glance</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-17-93bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-17-93bc/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A glance back at the months of creation, experimentation, and learning. Style inspired on &amp;ldquo;upon sunflowers&amp;rdquo; by Charmandaar from week one! Just really liked the simple lines and two-color aspect.
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Footprints</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-17-9d88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-17-9d88/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
Alternative title - I had an idea, but I suck at timing
So you all remember @papapastry&amp;rsquo;s week 7 song? Well I was do, and I was gonna do a cover, but instead I made a cover&amp;hellip; still plan to make a cover
Also, I am still learning clipstudio (Pumpka, I blame you entirely) So the actual piece: I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about that damn red panda since week 7!</description></item><item><title>Hatsune Miku plays the hits feat. Kagamine Rin</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-17-a86b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-17-a86b/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A big ol' wheres waldo of past submissions! I&amp;rsquo;m super late so I&amp;rsquo;ll probs tag the appropriate tags later. Design Refresh has really been an exercise in time management lmao. Inspired by @papapastry week 3 entry! And everyone else, its been a wild ride. (Also ngl this is very unfinished lmao)
medias:</description></item><item><title>I AM LITERAL SPED</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-17-fcd6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-17-fcd6/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t really reuse any pieces, moreso a reflection piece now that everything&amp;rsquo;s coming to an end. This challenge has honestly made me pump out more work than I have in the last&amp;hellip;.decade LOL, and it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been possible without everyone who participated, inspiring each other. YOU ALL INSPIRE ME. YEAH YOU LIKE THAT CHEESE?</description></item><item><title>Mandrake Reflecting</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @arren&amp;rsquo;s Week 1 submission &amp;ldquo;Sparkly Mandrake&amp;rdquo; (https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/) This was one of the first pieces I saw when watching design refresh and it really captured my attention. I utilised my own Mandrake model from Week 7 (https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/). I tried to capture a video of it to replicate the glitter of the original gif, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t look very good.</description></item><item><title>Shorts</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-7ac3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-7ac3/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10/11 Suite, Steinberg Cubase 5, FL Studio 12/20, &amp;amp; DaVinci Resolve.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hey team, this 8-minute video would do best when left to last. Thanks!
Submission 5/5.
I took a work from every week (without repeats of artists) and wrote 30 second shorts for each one. Most of these shorts are from work that I wrote in the past that has not seen the light of day.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: various traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Images in the imgur link: https://imgur.com/a/xaqXvNg
It&amp;rsquo;s been fun. Thanks everyone participating. Seeing everyone&amp;rsquo;s work in this showcase format week by week has been a really great way to share art with each other, inspire, motivate, develop and helping me and others appreciate more things about the work people do as we&amp;rsquo;re enabled to get into closer detail on the what, how &amp;amp; why in regards to the art people do.</description></item><item><title>[Title Too Long]</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-17-4a75/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-17-4a75/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
I chose to base this week&amp;rsquo;s drawing on a1ewanrichards&amp;rsquo;s work. The subjects, the markers, the honesty of the strokes really amazes me.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: So this week I am not submitting anything really, but I did draw something based on the prompt (attached image is more proof than anything else).</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: Ewan's Summer - Season's End</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-17-eeb3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-17-eeb3/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint, Adobe Photoshop, and E-portfolio (Flip Book made on https://fliphtml5.com/).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes [REVISED, REUPLOAD] This is my own refresh/summary of my past works, with in-depth elaboration for each work. Each entry is lengthy, so for the sake of the actual showcase, please read the foreword and the Week 17 instead, especially the finale where I wrote something special, hopefully.</description></item><item><title>fruit that isn't fruit</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-17-8df0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-17-8df0/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: keeb.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes shutuphamish (twitch)
for a while i didn&amp;rsquo;t have an idea for the final refresh, but i knew i wanted to enter. i missed (a lot) more showcases than i wanted to at the start and only entered twice before this (and really only one good entry) but i&amp;rsquo;ve been here the whole time, watching vods and enjoying the submissions!</description></item><item><title>Inspiration</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-17-cbc8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-17-cbc8/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Toon Boom Harmony.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I am late but still on time for the showcase Thanks to all the deadline extensions I was still able to make the morphing gif idea I had for this!
Because I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to draw anything dedicated for Designrefresh at all I decided to do all of them at once on the final week.</description></item><item><title>Keep It Simple</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-17-1b83/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-17-1b83/</guid><description>Direct link to a .pdf file.Direct link to a .pdf file.
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Publication with InDesign.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I made a zine that is basically a doodling book where I included previous submissions to serve as inspiration. Thought this would be a fun thing that people can print off themselves and keep as a sketch book to fill out as something to do after the project is over.</description></item><item><title>Lonely Light</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-342b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-342b/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 11 Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 3/5.
Preamble:
I planned to do a colossal anthology of pieces, week after week, each with different artists to create a storyline and a concept EP in addition to the five pieces of work I actually did for the final week of the refresh. The planning document I have for that clocks in at just under 2,000 words, uses art from 16 artists, and is a coming-of-age story about an immortal wizard.</description></item><item><title>Medley</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-95b8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-95b8/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 11 Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes If time is a factor, please skip this for the showcase!
Submission 4/5.
A throwback to all of my audio pieces (all 17 of them!) over the design refresh.
YT: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xOJWodLB3Y
SC: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/medley-2021-design-refresh
Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>MUSE</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-17-7c5e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-17-7c5e/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop/ digital painting/ cover album.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So this is it! This is finale of 17 weeks of Designrefesh! I participated in this awesome community since week 5 and haven’t dropped a single prompt! I’m proud of myself for this commitment. Thank you @cindry for hosting and everyone who helping and participating! You all inspired me to stick to this all along.</description></item><item><title>Peace is Dynamism</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @a1ewanrichards &amp;ldquo;When the land becomes graveyards&amp;rdquo; (https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-d4f0/) I loved this piece because it tapped into a vivid memory of playing soccer opposite sugarcane fields, watching them slowly disintegrate into flames and having the ash gently fall on us as we practiced. Life felt like it was so vividly coloured back then.</description></item><item><title>Re:dux</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-093b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-093b/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Since I had more time than I initially thought, I decided to add a little more to the piece! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I need to say more than I initially wrote in the original piece but I hope you enjoy the Directors Extended Cut of the piece haha
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>wittle whale</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-17-05c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-17-05c2/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: wood, knife.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
liked the whale from the deep sea week (2). Inspired by bright sea by arren. Made from spalted birch
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: wittle whale Medium: wood, knife Description: liked the whale from the deep sea week (2).</description></item><item><title>Part of Your World</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Waaaa, week 17,,, it&amp;rsquo;s here,, and I actually come with a piece of quality (thanks to the extensions lmao). This piece was inspired by @Linalifox&amp;rsquo;s submission for week 4, titled &amp;ldquo;Blue&amp;rdquo;. Their piece reminded me of mermaids, which reminded me of The Little Mermaid and my merman AU that I have for Backey,,, so I drew him and took the pose from the &amp;ldquo;Part of Your World&amp;rdquo; scene in The Little Mermaid.</description></item><item><title>End of a Chapter</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-17-3f12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-17-3f12/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Nothing fancy for the last week of the design refresh 2021 as I want to take this time to praise all the wonderful artists that submitted their art. It was only a few month ago that a picked up my first drawing tablet and started digital art (I was so scared to even use colors 🤣 ).</description></item><item><title>#2021DesignRefresh Portfolio</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: E-portfolio (flipbook made on https://fliphtml5.com).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I find it&amp;rsquo;s always nice to look back whenever you complete a series / project and celebrate, so this is my way of doing so - creating a book with all the pieces I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted. I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed this challenge and trying all these new mediums, even when I felt like my brain might explode.</description></item><item><title>Re:create</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-ac8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-ac8e/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wowwww, another side profile of an anime girl, how creative of me&amp;hellip;. I tried to incorporate some of my previous works in this piece&amp;hellip; Week 1 - with the yellow background, Week 3 - Red Circle with the red earrings, Week 4 - Murky silhouette with the persona style art, Week 8 - high sheen from jimmy neutron, Week 9 - the devil girl that I drew, Week 10 - Folds and folds and the anime style.</description></item><item><title>things you use to look at yourself with (the musical/remix)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-a37a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-a37a/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Whatever beans used + Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 2/5.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist. Thanks to @jumpingbeans for the script and visuals.
I used a guitar with a steel slide, a special piano that uses one string per key (originally created by David Klavins), and Balinese Gamelan instruments.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=87LKV9dcaj4
Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>refresh.fiveclawd.com</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-09eb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-09eb/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Go + Hugo, Python..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 1/5.
Yeah, this totally counts.
No need to showcase it, I just wanted to pad my stats. Five submissions!
https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/
Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week**: 17 **Title:** refresh.</description></item><item><title>ThankEgg</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ive ran out of ideas and time
; https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ;
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: ThankEgg Medium: video Description: ive ran out of ideas and time Social Media: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Under the Sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-2-41fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-2-41fd/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Game, Animal Crossing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (I didn’t actually post at the time so here we are&amp;hellip;)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Under the Sea Medium: Game, Animal Crossing Description: (I didn’t actually post at the time so here we are.</description></item><item><title>Dynames</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-16-aea7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-16-aea7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photography + free photo edit thing again lmao.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Gundam Dynames with Lockon Stratos as pilot. idk lol
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Dynames Medium: Photography + free photo edit thing again lmao Description: Gundam Dynames with Lockon Stratos as pilot.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: At A Time Like This, Will Someone Be There For You?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-9695/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-16-9695/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My first attempt at digital painting! Meh results, I think.
I tried to recreate this scenery of the Taal Volcano Island in Tagaytay, a popular tourist destination south of Manila, along a steep access road that we crossed during an official business trip where a teammate and I were doing ocular inspections of venues from the recently-concluded 30th Southeast Asian Games.</description></item><item><title>Big Skeleton</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-16-64e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-16-64e9/</guid><description> Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Almost forgot to submit :I
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Big Skeleton Medium: Pencils Description: Almost forgot to submit :I</description></item><item><title>Broccaiju</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Godzilla v Kong cut content. Actually though, heavily inspired by an old PS2 game called War of the Monsters that is a Kaiju-filled beat-em-up.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Broccaiju Medium: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT Description: Godzilla v Kong cut content.</description></item><item><title>d'Eggfsg</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw big egg. Smol soldier. In combination, they make a pretty striking pair. I&amp;rsquo;ve been having really out of the world dreams lately, and some of them feel like Neil Gaiman stories, but them sometimes they feel like this piece. It&amp;rsquo;s both familiar and not, something that we&amp;rsquo;ve all been feeling after being stuck inside for so long.</description></item><item><title>Dobby and me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-16-39f7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is how I feel everytime I hug my cat. He is a giant things to my heart! Yeah sometimes I wanted to be smaller just to cuddle with him 🥰✨💜
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Guardian</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-16-25d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-16-25d6/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A giant golem accompanies and provides shade to desert travellers
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week 16** **Title:** Guardian **Medium:** Paint Tool SAI **Description:** A giant golem accompanies and provides shade to desert travellers **Socials:** Scimister on twitch!</description></item><item><title>It'sssss Smelbourne!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-16-ca58/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling nostalgic for blue skies and pub crawls in the city. Here&amp;rsquo;s a shot from 2017 from a bar verandah, now ssssswarming with ssssssnakes. Taking it easy on the wrist still, but I had enough in me to make this!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>oof</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-16-b445/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This isn&amp;rsquo;t up to the usual quality of what I make, but I wanted to do something simple since I&amp;rsquo;ve felt so overwhelmed lately. Gotta love growing up and facing the crushing weight of your new responsibilities am I right? I&amp;rsquo;ll at least try to make something good for week 17 =3= (also if you want some &amp;ldquo;giant thing next to a small thing&amp;rdquo; art that&amp;rsquo;s of actual quality, go look at my submission for week 2 lol)</description></item><item><title>ooh shit</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-16-8ba4/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting on photograph, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes hey you should read kaiju no.8 its really good and big things are really cool!!! im sad i couldnt show the whole process on my stream but here it is! is it creepy yet??
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Pain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-16-1985/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-16-1985/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live Studio 11.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was going to write a 5 minute epic rock opera piece with lots of contrasts, fun guitar parts, etc, but life made it impossible. When life gives you lemons&amp;hellip;
Link:
Soundcloud: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/pain-2021-design-refresh
YT: http://papapastry.io/youtube
Spotify: http://papapastry.io/spotify
Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Rat Race</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-16-eca9/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Graphite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The idiom is defined as &amp;ldquo;an endless, self-defeating, or pointless pursuit&amp;hellip;The term is commonly associated with an exhausting, repetitive lifestyle that leaves no time for relaxation or enjoyment.&amp;quot;(thanks wikipedia) The concept was initially sketched out two years ago, but quickly shelved after major life events and and work affected my ability to put effort into it.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-16-911a/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Fineliner 0.05 mm yay.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not cleaning my submission up today ;_; seriously sorry please make do
It&amp;rsquo;s treefolk migration season, and for woodland folk daring to climb them it&amp;rsquo;s prime time to gather food from up there.
Guys, guys, just sitting down putting in lines here and there where you feel like it is so much fun.</description></item><item><title>Mechanics love their jobs sometimes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-16-7100/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Krita (still mouse).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t be deceived, the Blue Amazon is a killing machine. Although these robots are programmed to try to act human, they are infact very much controlled by their masters (at least that is what the master thinks). If you think you are in ara ara distance, you are in fact in danger. (didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to finish)</description></item><item><title>Ozymandias</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So this is an idea have had since week 7, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to pull it off and also had too many ideas for that week. However I honestly think it fits with this week&amp;rsquo;s theme better 😛
So this is based off the poem &amp;ldquo;Ozymandias&amp;rdquo; by Percy Bysshe Shelley.</description></item><item><title>PK Fire</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-14-3200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-14-3200/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I missed the last few weeks so here’s a combination of them as comic!!
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14, 15, 16 Title: PK Fire Medium: Procreate Description: I missed the last few weeks so here’s a combination of them as comic!</description></item><item><title>The ~~Diving~~ Maternal Legendary</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (a small TW for alcohol and drug abuse) I decided to draw not my most favorite pokemon for this week, but the pokemon I respect* the most. Lugia&amp;rsquo;s past is quite depressing. The creator of Lugia, Takeshi Shudo, heavily relied on alcohol, pills and even *tranquilizers* to get his mind in the workspace, which sadly isn&amp;rsquo;t an uncommon practice with creators.</description></item><item><title>A Titan's Journey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-16-872f/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art? 🤔
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 16 Title: A Titan&amp;#39;s Journey Medium: Clip Studio Description: To improve as an artist its important to try new things so i decided to draw with no line art ✍️ My first take on gaming concept art?</description></item><item><title>It's acting weird!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-16-fc95/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-16-fc95/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Mola mola with a few babies. They&amp;rsquo;re actually way smaller than this in scale but I have to make them visible!
lithiumreflections (IG/tumblr), lireflections (twitter)
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 **Title: ** It&amp;#39;s acting weird!</description></item><item><title>sometimes art is not worth having a mental breakdown over</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-15-6259/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So&amp;hellip; I was late for once. Annnd this wasn&amp;rsquo;t even what I was working on, this is just that same warm up I posted a while back. I probably should&amp;rsquo;ve just posted this last week so I could avoid falling into a depression after crumbling under the pressure, but&amp;hellip; it wasn&amp;rsquo;t polished, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want my work on the other piece to go to waste.</description></item><item><title>what is bigger, a giant bidoof or an individual's life?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes subject matters of artists like Edward Hopper tends to place equal weight for the furniture and the human matter, for example, the parallelism of the shapes of his human subject and non-human subjects, the compositions as well. Edward Hopper has invoked thought within his audience, how important is life? Are our lives just as unimportant than the furniture we buy?</description></item><item><title>Red Delicious with a Red Delicious</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Whoopsies, I&amp;rsquo;m late again! Oh well, school finals are happening right now and, particularly in math (I&amp;rsquo;m a grade ahead of my peers in it) homework likes to pile up. But, even if I&amp;rsquo;m late, I know that this would&amp;rsquo;ve came out really bad if I rushed it, so I took my time and.</description></item><item><title>tomatoes are the potatoes of fruit</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-15-0547/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-15-0547/</guid><description> The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: gw acrylic paint for mini figures.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes tomato potato
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 15 Title: tomatoes are the potatoes of fruit Medium: gw acrylic paint for mini figures Description: tomato potato</description></item><item><title>Bread, Butter, Boysenberry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-15-78d8/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Food.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My grandfather loved boysenberry jam, so I made a simple tribute to him and my favorite meal, breakfast. Used a knife and jam to create the basic form of a boysenberry, with bread as the &amp;ldquo;canvas&amp;rdquo; and butter to prevent it from getting soggy. Jammin with jam lol
Social Media Instagram: karen_tsugawa Twitch: vectorong Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Hades</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-15-a473/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-15-a473/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Fruity Loops Studio 20.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Fruit doesn&amp;rsquo;t really make a lot of noise, at least nothing that sounds pleasant. My banana ocarina was not shelf-stable.
But I get what Cindy&amp;rsquo;s trying to do here. The analogue for basics for musicians is, I dunno, first pieces? Drills? Fur Elise? Wonderwall? Well, I learned music production using FL Studio (Fruity Loops) which is a funny coincidence, so I&amp;rsquo;ll use that.</description></item><item><title>hEhE LEmon bUTt but also strawberry and coffee is kinda vibes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-15-69ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-15-69ac/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes been having late nights with strawberries and coffees. ALSO HONESTLY HIGHKEY INSPIRED BY MIMI&amp;rsquo;S LEMON OBVIOUSLY HEHEHEHE, and some shirt designs that i peeped a couple nights ago.
urmom 15.0 hurhur
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 15 Title: hEhE LEmon bUTt but also strawberry and coffee is kinda vibes Medium: Procreate Description: been having late nights with strawberries and coffees.</description></item><item><title>leeeeemons</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-15-8495/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: relief printing on note books.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes taking it easy this week with something i found relaxing and i guess soothing? something like the lemon honey i was drinking while sick. make some stamps! have a good time! take care of yourself
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>still life</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-15-1453/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project. All photos for reference taken by me. My DMs are open if anyone want to join.
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week15 Title: still life Medium: watercolour Description: Collection of my ongoing still life fruit project.</description></item><item><title>Tightrope banana.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-15-c2a4/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paper, permanent marker..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, life happened and I forgot. Here take this shitpost instead. Balance!
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 15 Title: Tightrope banana. Medium: Paper, permanent marker.</description></item><item><title>Whats Left : Left handed Leftovers, vol. 1</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-15-2fdb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: markers + paper in gif.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m still dealing with wrist pain so I&amp;rsquo;m making the most of it. What do I have left? A whole other side of my body to learn to draw with! Shout out to LeftHandedToons, a comic site that I spent a lot of time on as a kid. This one&amp;rsquo;s for you</description></item><item><title>Resistance 4 - Sometimes, The Heart Yearns For Mangoes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-15-4b55/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A change of pace, I think? I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really pinpoint any concept to execute for this week, but this imagery had lingered to me for a few days. Then I also remembered a 1994 poem I read from a book whose title for this I based it from.
The poem is about homesickness and wishing for a better world from a faraway place, a faraway country.</description></item><item><title>Still Life Succulents</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-15-438c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-15-438c/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes No fruit around and I decided I&amp;rsquo;d go more for the still life angle of the assignment using my succulent pot as a base (yes, it&amp;rsquo;s sparse for now, but it&amp;rsquo;ll have new cuttings soon.)
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>#1 Sour Lemon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-15-906c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-15-906c/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Adobe Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I actually love the sourness of lemons ~ that is what lemons are known for too. What if we could give an award to a lemon? that would be judged by sourness wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it 😌
Social Media Instagram: mimichair.art Twitch: mimichair Twitter: mimikuchan Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Durian at sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-15-66fb/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decide to try something new this week so i tried animation for the first time&amp;hellip;yea&amp;hellip;its hard 🥲 Could only use 24 frames cause of clipstudio&amp;rsquo;s restriction. Does anyone have any recommendation for 2d animation software? 🎞️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>illiteracy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: chinese calligraphy.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The art philosophy known as &amp;ldquo;Nanyang Art Style&amp;rdquo; is a fusion of western and eastern art style. Often, pioneers of this art styles employed western mediums and materials, paired with subject matters of eastern origins / things you commonly see in asia. Some of the pioneering artists are Georgette Chen, Liu Kang etc.</description></item><item><title>My Protective Assistant</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was late, sad. Buut I got this done tho! I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved whenever I got the change to draw fire and fire effects. Again, I actually learned a technique on youtube on how to do this, and I think it works out really well for my style! This is dragon Backey (I know they&amp;rsquo;re also cowboys, please don&amp;rsquo;t ask how many alternate universes we have) attacking a rowdy dragon who got too aggro with Prince Astro!</description></item><item><title>Burnt Out</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-14-2f2a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-14-2f2a/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Photograph/Free Photo Editing Thingymajig.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes feeling a bit burnt out
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week: 14 Title: Burnt Out Medium: Photograph/Free Photo Editing Thingymajig Description: feeling a bit burnt out</description></item><item><title>Fusion Flare</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-14-845f/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d try drawing them for fun :)
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 13 Title: 😳 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I drew my OC because I like her :) Week 14 Title: Fusion Flare Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;#39;d try drawing them for fun :)</description></item><item><title>😳</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-13-d1bc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-13-d1bc/</guid><description> Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I drew my OC because I like her :)
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 13 Title: 😳 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I drew my OC because I like her :) Week 14 Title: Fusion Flare Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: Reshiram is my favorite fire type pokemon, so I figured I&amp;#39;d try drawing them for fun :)</description></item><item><title>A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-14-9ae5/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wrist still hurts, I want to D word
@/pumpkanart on tooter and touch
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: A contract for the vain, the price paid in pain Medium: Procreate Description: wrist still hurts, I want to D word Socials: @/pumpkanart on tooter and touch</description></item><item><title>Anarchy Loves Fire</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate (and DaVinci Resolve).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a piece of an animatic I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on about an anarchist pig and his contemporaries and their relationship with violence. (edit: it&amp;rsquo;s a little heavy so pls don&amp;rsquo;t be wearing headphones if you&amp;rsquo;re not used to heavy music)</description></item><item><title>burnout</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-14-8305/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: paper cutting photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is about burnout and how hard it is sometimes to recognise it while in haste. Just remember to take your time, recognise to take care of your body. Don&amp;rsquo;t burn yourself, it&amp;rsquo;ll take a while to recover!
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Cindy Should Pay Me to Moderate</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-14-92c3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-14-92c3/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (Cindy please play this song first).
So of course &amp;ldquo;fire&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;rapping&amp;rdquo; but Cindy also mentioned &amp;ldquo;value&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;contrast&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;bright&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;heart&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;too much.&amp;rdquo; So that&amp;rsquo;s what I used to write the bars.
This is the first non-meme rap song I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written. I could have gone down the meme route but it&amp;rsquo;s more challenging if I welcome people cringing at my lyrics and rap voice.</description></item><item><title>Coming Up Spades</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-13-fc72/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-13-fc72/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Volume warning.
To play with expressiveness would be the opposite of playing robotically. Adding the &amp;ldquo;face&amp;rdquo; to that means it&amp;rsquo;s also about passion and improvisation. When you add the voice, it&amp;rsquo;s about falsetto, belting, loudness, distortion, mistakes, and roughness.
Lines means melody lines, emphasis is about progression/phrase changes over time. &amp;ldquo;Look at me&amp;rdquo; represents the boisterous pride of what is being sung and represented.</description></item><item><title>Fiery heart</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/shredarbayn-week-14-1e42/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/shredarbayn-week-14-1e42/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Charcoal &amp;amp; Watercolour on 110gsm Dollar-store Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes With fire on my mind, I thought of Calcifer and how Howl ate the shooting star! (Howl&amp;rsquo;s Moving Castle 2005)
Timelapse
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-7cvM7f3Ps
This was my first endeavor with watercolour and wanted to give it a red hot go (haha) I used a charcoal pencil to free hand the foundation which took me approximately 1 hour to accomplish.</description></item><item><title>Flames of Phlegethos</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Let&amp;rsquo;s draw another one of my D&amp;amp;D characters, because dang it! Why not!?
Met Athenaeum; tiefling lore bard/warlock and general wielder of hell fire.
So fun fact, when I started digital art about a year ago one of my first pieces was of Ath doing neato flame shit. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d revisit the concept with this one.</description></item><item><title>Hearts on Fire</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-14-c105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-14-c105/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Digital/Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get to finish this up with polish but I enjoyed making the flames.
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 **Title: ** Hearts on Fire Medium: Digital/Clip Studio Paint Description: Didn&amp;#39;t quite get to finish this up with polish but I enjoyed making the flames.</description></item><item><title>hey girl bites lip</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-14-d441/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-14-d441/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: procrate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I started this in January but i changed up a lot of things in the last 1 hour like the clouds and i moved like half the facial anatomy
Socaisl: https://frogglasses.carrd.co/
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 14 Title: hey girl *bites lip* Medium: procrate I started this in January but i changed up a lot of things in the last 1 hour like the clouds and i moved like half the facial anatomy Socaisl: https://frogglasses.</description></item><item><title>Hungry Firelings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-14-6699/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-14-6699/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Fire.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Look behind you, they&amp;#39;re the Captain now Medium: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR Description: Return to monke GOLD Week: 14 Title: Hungry Firelings Medium: Fire Description: SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION</description></item><item><title>Look behind you, they're the Captain now</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-13-2bfa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-13-2bfa/</guid><description> Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Return to monke
GOLD
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Look behind you, they&amp;#39;re the Captain now Medium: Watercolor, GOLD COLOR Description: Return to monke GOLD Week: 14 Title: Hungry Firelings Medium: Fire Description: SPEEDRUN SUBMISSION</description></item><item><title>OH SHIT DID I MAKE IT ON TIME? (actual title: extinguished)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-14-762c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-14-762c/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: LMFAO HELP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes AAAAAAAAAAH (actual figured my take would be on the idea of the death of a fire? extinguished. ye)
urmomr1.4505
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 TITLE: OH SHIT DID I MAKE IT ON TIME?</description></item><item><title>Once in a while</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-14-52b8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: procreate pocket.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night&amp;hellip; ( ok you can have more than one 😆😆😆)
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Once in a while Medium: procreate pocket Description: have yourself a little girlled marshmallow in this cold winter night.</description></item><item><title>The End of Zeno's Paradox</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-14-acb9/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, entered, done, a lot of creative endeavors throughout my life, and looking back, it has been quite frustrating, to say the least. This frustration has consumed me over the past several years, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure last year was even the peak.
I&amp;rsquo;ve sold all my camera gear to help make ends meet, threw away my collection of piano sheet music (much to my older brother&amp;rsquo;s surprise), and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure where to go from here; I think I&amp;rsquo;ve reached my limit, whatever it may be.</description></item><item><title>The Five Virtues</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-14-de8e/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Pyrography (woodburning).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Illustration based on the Fenghuang, a mythological bird whose body symbolizes the celestial bodies and the five tail feathers representing the five virtues of Confucius. It is said that their appearance signals the coming of a new era.
And what better way to honor my favorite mythological bird than to burn in directly into some wood with fire LOL</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-14-911a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Still very much a work in progress, but posting what&amp;rsquo;s currently on paper. Friend asked if I could make something for his wall, so I sat down and improvised some stuff, did a refined version, then an A3 sketch, now lightboxing it up to watercolor. Didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to do something for week 14, but this happened to line up with having flames, so why not!</description></item><item><title>comfy spot</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/piacine-week-14-e01a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/piacine-week-14-e01a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The fire is warm, comforting, bright. Just warms your cold toes and the tip of the nose after a cold walk along the beach at night time.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 14 Title: comfy spot Medium: Procreate Description: The fire is warm, comforting, bright.</description></item><item><title>My cat is on fire</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-14-b10a/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Played around with a photo of my cat.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: My cat is on fire Medium: Krita Description: Played around with a photo of my cat.</description></item><item><title>That's gotta hurt</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-14-aee4/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re a monster, a loon. Everybody wants you dead, including me.&amp;rdquo; Oops, more angst! This is just a nightmare Astro has though, Backey never actually says this lol. Decided to use purposely messy lineart in this piece, I think it looks pretty decent! Astro just needs to stop snooping around in places he shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; Backey doesn&amp;rsquo;t appreciate him reading his journal.</description></item><item><title>idk</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-14-d670/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-14-d670/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like the concept of this peicr and I&amp;rsquo;m on spring break now so I can acctually participate.
My drawing skills arnt the best compared to others in this discord but this still fun improving and taking part
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>His name is Shiro 🔥</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-14-04ca/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: His name is Shiro 🔥 Medium: Clip studio Description: Antagonist: The Main Character of this anime just arrived im fucked</description></item><item><title>Fire Sale</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita w/ mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Think about the value
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Fire Sale Medium: Krita w/ mouse Description: Think about the value Social Media: https://www.twitch.com/jumpingbeansz</description></item><item><title>“uhmmm Mine!!! It’s mine”</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-13-62e9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-13-62e9/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: digital,photoshop+procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I’m late but here it is
the title said it all I guess 🥺🥺🥺
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: I’m late but here it is Week: 13 Title: “uhmmm Mine!</description></item><item><title>Fake Animu Screenshot</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-13-b7c6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-13-b7c6/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook pro &amp;amp; paint.net.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Super last minute submission, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss two weeks in a row!
So you know when you have a plan, but then you realise you did not give yourself enough time?
&amp;hellip;yeah that was me 😅
Originally was gonna have like 3 or 4 fake screenshots. But time is a cruel mistress.</description></item><item><title>Fragments of Remembrance</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/suavestrawberry-week-13-0fde/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/suavestrawberry-week-13-0fde/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes this is a comic I made with my friends a couple months ago currently we are working on episode 2 after a hiatus and I hope you enjoy the first episode. I put a lot of heart into it and I hope to become a WEBTOON original one day</description></item><item><title>Fuck</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-13-fd44/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-13-fd44/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, Audio/Ableton Live 10 Suite, Adoble Premiere Pro CC.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes lmao haven&amp;rsquo;t drawn since year 9 and i&amp;rsquo;m in my mid twenties now so good time to start over
i drew this in around five minutes
context: woke up at 4pm today and had an hour to write a song. wasn&amp;rsquo;t gonna happen so here&amp;rsquo;s a rerun and some art, and a reason why i shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be allowed near a drawing tablet ever again</description></item><item><title>im dying btw</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-13-4534/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-13-4534/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: digital, CSP and SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes based off true events like 1:50 PM 2/4/2021
my water was too hot to drink so i was dying.
i think this has inspired me to do more 4komas tho in the future!!! i really like short fun comics, one of my favourite things to draw&amp;hellip; so i hope you like it too!</description></item><item><title>Introspection</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-13-9eca/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-13-9eca/</guid><description>Your browser does not support the audio element.Your browser does not support the audio element. Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Keyboard, and some words..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The first thing I thought of when looking at the title of this week&amp;rsquo;s prompt was introspection. I wanted to explore poetry a bit more so I did some reading on limericks and worked with that structure. So the first one titled SeemsGood* is about my general high school experience.</description></item><item><title>i suffer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-13-f4a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-13-f4a6/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes hurt my wrist so this is all I&amp;rsquo;ve got. suffering in real time
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: i suffer Medium: procreate Description: hurt my wrist so this is all I&amp;#39;ve got.</description></item><item><title>Lorem Ipsum</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-12-6dbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-12-6dbd/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop/Premiere Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes whoops I missed last week but here we gooooo
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 12 Title: Lorem Ipsum Medium: Photoshop/Premiere Pro Description: whoops I missed last week but here we gooooo Socials: @paintsepsi on everything!</description></item><item><title>OMORI AU</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-13-335d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-13-335d/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I was gonna finish on time, but I managed to get these done! I finished watching a let&amp;rsquo;s play of OMORI recently, and it was wonderful experience&amp;hellip; I felt inspired to draw little battle portraits of my OCs in the game&amp;rsquo;s style! Was gonna draw their real world counterparts, but I&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t have the time nor energy.</description></item><item><title>Portrait 7: Ruminations</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-13-ace6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-13-ace6/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Completely dissatisfied with my previous entry, so here&amp;rsquo;s a new one. I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling lonely and isolated lately for so long. I feel that nobody will ever bother to listen or understand me.
My interpretation of Otomatsu Sato from the movie &amp;ldquo;Poppoya&amp;rdquo; (Railroad Man), a stationmaster at a former coal mining town, whose train station he mans is about to close.</description></item><item><title>P̷̑̚Ä̴́̅I̴͒̚N̷̈͠F̵̳̂Ű̷͓L̵̛͝ ̶̓̏B̷̈́̔L̴̅̂Ī̶̈́S̵̓̾S̷̐̐</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-13-77c7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-13-77c7/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes bright colors, just as a warning &amp;ldquo;AST̶̉̽Ŕ̴̊O̷͑͑, ASTRO! P̷̦͠L̸͋̒Ẽ̷̙A̶̓̔S̵̓̉É̶̅!̴̏̾ ̷̀̂B̶̐̚L̸͑̍I̸̺̓N̷͗̾K̵͌̾ ̴̕͝A̷͗̚T̶̂͌ ̴̐̓M̶̐̀E̵̍́!̵̄̌ WHAT HAPPENED? W̶̟̉H̶̒͗Ÿ̵́͂ ̶̘̇D̶̽͜I̴̛̓D̴̯̂ ̸̈́̂T̷̀͊H̵̋̓Í̶͙S̶̍̆ ̴̅͆Ḧ̵́APPEN?! NO! WAKE UP WAKE UP!!&amp;rdquo;
(Don&amp;rsquo;t bother trying to read that if you struggle lmao) I got this piece in, yay! More crazy eyes and insight into the story lol. If only this were an April Fools so Astro could go &amp;ldquo;It was just a prank, bro!</description></item><item><title>Selfie</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-13-3864/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-13-3864/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes my gf likes to take pics with my mirror lmao.
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Selfie Medium: Procreate Description: my gf likes to take pics with my mirror lmao.</description></item><item><title>Some Pig</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-13-d52f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-13-d52f/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Animal portrait with an emphasis on exaggerated proportions for distinct features - tiny eyes, big nose, super pudgy.
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections / twitter lireflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 **Title: ** Some Pig Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: Animal portrait with an emphasis on exaggerated proportions for distinct features - tiny eyes, big nose, super pudgy.</description></item><item><title>Then She Fell”</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-13-8b9e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-13-8b9e/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Mixed media (plaster strips, paper clay, paint), Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Inspired by the song Bad Dream by Tatsuya Kitani (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lkYeBXXHgY4)
*I&amp;rsquo;m forced to live a meaningless and unreasonable tragedy
Who the hell said “after rain comes fair weather”
I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine this bad dream ending*
The mask is referencing a Hannya mask that&amp;rsquo;s used in Noh theater, which is used in the performances to depict female demons that are filled with jealousy.</description></item><item><title>Life of Avocados</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/piacine-week-13-915b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/piacine-week-13-915b/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The daily life of avocados. Here I will present to you today, to make you all aware of how appalling avocado cruelty really is and why it must be stopped. #savetheavocados
(My imagination when I was working on an avocado farm)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Spicy Expressions</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-13-a56d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-13-a56d/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Beginning of a ego fueled Spicy food challenge #What&amp;rsquo;s ur spice tolerance? 🔥 🔥 🔥
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Spicy Expressions Medium: Clip studio Description: The Beginning of a ego fueled Spicy food challenge #What&amp;#39;s ur spice tolerance?</description></item><item><title>Things you use to see yourself with</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-13-0c7e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-13-0c7e/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: MS paint /some online video compiler.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My sister took my computer, so i used a potato to do this work.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-13-911a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-13-911a/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes remade my emote. made the expression better. (first one is the new one)
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 13 Title: Medium: Krita Description: remade my emote.</description></item><item><title>Trust</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-12-2f81/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-12-2f81/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes really rushed submission school is hectic. Saw this quote somewhere and really liked it so I decided to do like a little image.which turned out to be like a tatto design 😂 hope you enjou
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation - The Body Keeps The Score</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-12-8990/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-12-8990/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Felt markers and highlighters.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one was really hard to make, both physically and emotionally. I felt a lot of things doing this. These&amp;hellip; things were borne from both internal and external stuff I&amp;rsquo;ve heard throughout my life. I think&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s all I can say for now. I might expand on this elsewhere, IDK.
The concept and title is based from a book by Dr.</description></item><item><title>Crazy Bird</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-12-6b6a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-12-6b6a/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I made it after all, sweet! Anyways, I decided to use a sharp type of typography I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the past to help emphasize the power in this picture. Yes this is the gay cowboys (I draw them both as humans and as people.) No spoilers for part 2, (part 1 is finished) but someone is struck by a smooth criminal.</description></item><item><title>Disappear</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-12-f36b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-12-f36b/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes English is my second language and I’m having fun with all suffix and prefix. Google said “dis” = “a Latin prefix meaning “apart,” “asunder,” “away,” “utterly,” or having a privative, negative, or reversing force&amp;hellip;. Also my art always revolving around my daily life so this work inspired by this week little getaway trip&amp;hellip; I’m disappeared into nature now&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Exhaustion</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-12-62d1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-12-62d1/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was going to do something cuter this week and make a lovecore aesthetic piece, buuuut I&amp;rsquo;ve just been,, so tired lately. Mom&amp;rsquo;s been keeping me up until 2 am all week for reasons so I haven&amp;rsquo;t been getting more than 5 hours of sleep per day&amp;hellip; so I decided to convey that through handwritten lettering.</description></item><item><title>Glass House</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-12-f76f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-12-f76f/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A bit too late cz I am busy with the exams. These are Lyrics from my favourite Song from last year it&amp;rsquo;s called Glass House by Gabbie Hanna, It has a good message behind it (I think), and it has the best music video I have ever seen, check it out if you have time.</description></item><item><title>Just a normal day as an asian girl online</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-12-713c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-12-713c/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Photography and Digital Editing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TW: racism, sexism
This is a response piece to the experience of being a female online. The quotes are all taken from real messages sent to me on my stream. The use of keycaps represents not only the digital nature of these messages but allude to how anonymous messages are written with magazine clippings.</description></item><item><title>Noodle Bar</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-12-972c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-12-972c/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This week&amp;rsquo;s theme has given me completely free rein on what I wanted to write. I fulfilled the theme entirely through the video. It&amp;rsquo;s visual and it&amp;rsquo;s words innit.
I was going to do kinetic typography but I had ten minutes to learn, which I determined to not be enough time. Songwriting process: noodle two chords, sing in a bathroom, noodle some more.</description></item><item><title>Reach</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-12-b350/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-12-b350/</guid><description> Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i mek hand gif
urmom 12.0
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 12 Title: Reach Medium: Procreate Description: i mek hand gif socials: urmom 12.0</description></item><item><title>Are You Listening?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-12-2b80/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-12-2b80/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Indesign (if you prefer illustrator you can fight me).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Throwback to that time I did a graphic design degree. The hardest thing I find when designing is deciding what stupid pointless words to put on the page. I feel like, especially at uni, a lot of words are there to look pretty and have no message.</description></item><item><title>Letter from her</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-12-bfe9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-12-bfe9/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I am not a huge fan of typography so this is my first crack at it. It was ok, maybe not my favorite lol. Though it was a good exercise for sure.
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>unspoken words of affirmation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-12-9763/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-12-9763/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes not sure if this counts as typography hahaha oOPs but uhh i really like writing even tho my handwriting is illegible at times so i honestly just wrote what came to mind which is that hm i guess i’m havin a tough time lately and i know a lot of my community is as well, so i kind of wrote this as a reminder for them (and myself, and you!</description></item><item><title>RELAX</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-12-78e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-12-78e9/</guid><description>Direct link to a .zip file.
Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ever had anxiety or panic and heard the word relax? That&amp;rsquo;s a bit of what I tried to capture here. The inner font with harmful/intrusive thoughts I made from my own handwriting and you can download it (linked in next message) and use it if you like.</description></item><item><title>Six Pix Mix</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-11-6ec2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-11-6ec2/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Some different sky colors
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Six Pix Mix Medium: Watercolor Description: Some different sky colors</description></item><item><title>The Comfy Chair</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-12-9bfb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-12-9bfb/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Ink + Marker, Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Inspired by the range of Italian designer Massimo Vignelli&amp;rsquo;s work, and that &amp;ldquo;If you can design one thing, you can design everything.&amp;rdquo; Often I feel as a designer and artist, we&amp;rsquo;re directed to only learn a specific &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; of skills, when in reality all your knowledge ends up coming into play in some form.</description></item><item><title>wrod</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-12-215e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-12-215e/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: gif.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes im clown, im illiterate, face go brrrrrrr (had to resubmit, the previous submission had weird colouring issues )
edit: redid the gif, its still giving the weird coloured background thingy, even though on my comp its not like that, idk whats going on, so i guess its epilepsy warning.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Yesterday</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-11-ebfe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrgreeyne-week-11-ebfe/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Few word.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A smattering of haikus for my first (and late ehehe) design refresh. Enjoy!
I mumble and groan
Basking in her warm embrace
Good morning, sunshine
Just as the wind blows,
As the clouds and trees just be,
I think of nothing.
Accompany me
Ebony night, Lake Shore Drive
What&amp;rsquo;s for dinner, beans?
Unfathomable
Magnificent, glorious
Twinkling far away</description></item><item><title>Aster Flower Looking Upon a Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-11-e2ea/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Kinda been stressed this week, but I managed to squeeze this piece out. Sketchier lineart than usual because it&amp;rsquo;s literally a sketch that&amp;rsquo;s cleaned up a bit lol, I&amp;rsquo;m tired and need to study for a test :p
Also check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; for a sketch done by DynoLoafer that&amp;rsquo;s basically what the guy looks like from the front lol</description></item><item><title>Bruh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-11-4cdb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-11-4cdb/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes No time to draw something this week so instead I decided on a quick little design. One is a lil goth boy and the other is his pastel bf
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Cancri</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-11-3c65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Relief printing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on my initial wonder (and subsequent terror) of the galaxy, where I would try to find my favorite constellations in the night sky. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of a parallels to the ocean; so unknown, beautiful, yet also terrifying to think about in its vastness. Also a reference to myself and my group of friends, since many of us happen to be born during the Cancer season.</description></item><item><title>He RUINED my DREAM JOURNAL</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-11-49d3/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: paper and gold thread and glue and stuff.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes couldn&amp;rsquo;t bare to draw anything this week, so i bound a book. getting the inner pages printed was a goddamn trial, and i wish I had matt laminate for the cover bc the shiny is gross, but I like the little gold thread stars on the front and the shiny paper on the inside makes it feel very dreamy.</description></item><item><title>Hydrangea Star Gazer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-11-b79c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you. I love you to the moon and back.
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Hydrangea Star Gazer Medium: Watercolour Description: There are 9,096 stars in the sky and I know one of them is you.</description></item><item><title>Rolling Lonely Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-11-1d65/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hey I love the stars and I love katamari. Star gazing is something i really love doing, and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be fun if a little prince came along and ruined your long exposure photography??
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Island</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-11-eb4c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-11-eb4c/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Music.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This song features the feeling of oppressive clouds and weather, harsh harmonies and clashing timbres.
This song isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;soft&amp;rdquo; but I wrote it by surrealist writing about the sea, the land, and the sky. I wrote back then: &amp;ldquo;The concept [is] a man on an island panicking and struggling to survive against the weather and wildlife.</description></item><item><title>This is where I live now</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-11-fb4d/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based on DoughyYeast&amp;rsquo;s headcanon
This week has been chaotic art-wise but did some fineliner cheating so you viewers probably can&amp;rsquo;t spot half the mistakes HAH! Have a good day day/night/morning/evening, everyone, you&amp;rsquo;re all lovely.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Week 11 head stuck in the clouds</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-11-4301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-11-4301/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A simple one, again. Just a mood I sometimes feel, wonder what it&amp;rsquo;s like up there aye.
urmom 11.0
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 11 Title: Week 11 head stuck in the clouds Medium: Procreate Description: A simple one, again.</description></item><item><title>“you would make the sky a gijinka” - enoki</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-11-33d0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ** Used the two references above (an image of a dark sunset and a clear midnight sky)* to create some fantastical characters and I had plans to do two more for **Dawn* and **Noon, but time prevails
I need to stop making non-human things human
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>glitch clouds inc</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Medium: Procreate Title: glitch clouds inc Description: sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe</description></item><item><title>Impressionable Sky</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-11-b3a9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-11-b3a9/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photomanipulation.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sick this week so keeping it simple and quick - photomanipulation focused on clouds over the mountains (original photograph also my own).
lithiumreflections (tumblr, IG), lireflections (twitter)
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 **Title: ** Impressionable Sky Medium: Photomanipulation Description: Sick this week so keeping it simple and quick - photomanipulation focused on clouds over the mountains (original photograph also my own).</description></item><item><title>Liminal Sky</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love the sky at dusk, a storm looming on the horizon. The brilliant colours doomed to a few moments before the sky grows dark and the rain begins. That liminal space where you just look at the sky in awe.
Trying to get better at digital painting. Think I got the vibe at least 😊</description></item><item><title>They Come Out at Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Getting into dragons again more than I usually do, so I decided to draw some dragon silhouette&amp;rsquo;s against a pretty night sky! I learned an easy trick to making galaxy/night sky patterns awhile back, so I put that to use in the top part of the screen! I like how this came out, even if it&amp;rsquo;s more simple because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy and tired with the new time change.</description></item><item><title>Undercooled 1: Please Return The Moon To Us</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-11-6c7f/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker and oil pastel on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I first conceptualized a starry universe portrait theme of sorts, but I thought a landscape would be better. This is my first time using oil pastel.
The flying figure is my interpretation of a &amp;ldquo;bakunawa,&amp;rdquo; a serpent-like dragon in Philippine mythology, who is said to cause various natural phenomena, such as eclipses.</description></item><item><title>Cloudy Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Cloudy Night Medium: Photoshop Description: I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart</description></item><item><title>Set Sail to find the legendary Mandrake farm</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-0fee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-11-0fee/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Decided to utilize everything I’ve learned in these past few months (perspective, anatomy, value, color etc.) Conclusion: this was a very humbling experience (I was a bit overwhelmed / kinda gave up on the ship towards the end) xD – I will keep practicing ✍️
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Are we at the weekends yet?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw this artist&amp;rsquo;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired. also, i like weekends.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Are we at the weekends yet? Medium: Krita Description: Saw this artist&amp;#39;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired.</description></item><item><title>Laputa</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-11-a1f0/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pressed enter before I put stuff by accident lol
&amp;ldquo;Castle in the Sky&amp;rdquo; is one of my favorite movies of all time, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d draw something inspired by it. The castle&amp;rsquo;s name is Laputa, so I named the piece accordingly.
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Passive smoking</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-11-03ba/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x and phone photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds. Was pretty, smelled chimney smoke. Wanted to make something fun.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Passive smoking Medium: ibispaint x and phone photo Description: Went skiing, had fun, saw happy little clouds.</description></item><item><title>silk</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/gianhet-week-10-5339/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/gianhet-week-10-5339/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: : CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes : /
rushed this one a bit lmao
Social Media Instagram: gianhet Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week 10 : title : silk medium : CSP socials : https://www.instagram.com/gianhet/ rushed this one a bit lmao</description></item><item><title>Boroboro Bobbin pants (ngl i literally almost called these boroboro bobbin bottoms LUL)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-10-5062/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Fabric / fashion (upcycled fabric, screenprinting, and sewing).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ボロボロ (&amp;ldquo;boroboro&amp;rdquo;) often refers to an item that is worn out to the point where it is in tatters. Rather than throw it out, I find it can be a very personal and relaxing process to repair it, following similar Japanese repairing idealogy where the fix / mend also becomes a point of beauty.</description></item><item><title>Good Clothes</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-10-9303/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-10-9303/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one speaks for itself.
Twitter: &amp;lt;&amp;gt; YouTube: http://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4nay640JrxBZhNMiVIYTFg?sub_confirmation=1 Spotify (latest release): https://open.spotify.com/album/02mN7iFb1ZGfIQlJvUATgc?si=JDQri4OMRNCAIrXyi4I1hg Apple Music (latest release): https://music.apple.com/us/album/lost-pastry-child/1556553688?uo=4&amp;amp;app=apple+music Link: https://youtu.be/KwACnHlAEmY
Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week:** 10 **Title:** Good Clothes **Medium:** Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite **Description:** This one speaks for itself.</description></item><item><title>Implied emotion??</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-10-43db/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Illustrator and CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Trying out gradient maps for the first time!! wow it&amp;rsquo;s super cool and colours are fresh! kinda want it to hold some sort of emotion in the fabric, what do you think?
shop.fiveclawd.com LOL
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-10-fa9b/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 10: Title: Jiu jitsu The Art of Folding Clothes While People are Still in Them. Medium: Photoshop Social: https://www.twitch.tv/soleilboo</description></item><item><title>Pico's Target</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol' Pico from Pico&amp;rsquo;s School and Friday Night Funkin'. He&amp;rsquo;s a good edgy boy.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Medium: Paint Tool SAI Title: __Pico&amp;#39;s Target__ Description: Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol&amp;#39; Pico from Pico&amp;#39;s School and Friday Night Funkin&amp;#39;.</description></item><item><title>Portrait 6: Get Together</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-10-aaa2/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Felt marker on paper, 9x12in.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Drew this earlier at the office since our room didn&amp;rsquo;t have internet since yesterday afternoon. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t think of anything nice, but this came to mind soon enough.
The dance is called &amp;ldquo;tinikling,&amp;rdquo; where a couple dances between two bamboo poles being clapped to the musical beat. It is somewhat similar to a waltz and a mazurka.</description></item><item><title>Prince Backey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-10-a407/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, so,, I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like shading, but partially colored lines are cool, right? Anyway, here&amp;rsquo;s an AU version of Backey where he&amp;rsquo;s a prince in a fantasy setting! Figured that an experiment with his design was long overdue lol, people can check &amp;lt;#794059396165926913&amp;gt; to see his og outfit
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Sunset Vibes, aka it was 30° degrees today</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes GUESS WHOES FIVECLAWD MERCH ARRIVED TODAY!!!! #notsponseredjustexcited
Thought I&amp;rsquo;d draw last week&amp;rsquo;s CMYK Dragon jacket and pair it with the Perseverance shirt cause who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want double dragons?
Bit of a quick one today cause running out of time. Yes, I did use a photo of my shirt for the shirt. No, I am not copy Cindy&amp;rsquo;s dragoon by hand, how much time do you think I have!</description></item><item><title>textile grook</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-10-5a04/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sorry, used 5 min
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: textile grook Medium: ibispaint x Description: Sorry, used 5 min Social Media: https://www.twitch.tv/cup_o_rice</description></item><item><title>The dread beach bum La Verne</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-10-104e/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This one got away from me a bit. I intended to do something simple, I really did. All I really wanted to do was do some stronger posing than usual. I hope this fits within the prompt for this week, shes wearing clothes lmao&amp;hellip;
Anyway here is my dnd character Joselynn La Verne being no more dramatic than usual</description></item><item><title>cute outfits</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/phoebecreates-week-10-678c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/phoebecreates-week-10-678c/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: ink and watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is the beginning of my 100 outfits challenge. Yes I&amp;rsquo;m planning to do 100 of them. Ambitious? Maybe&amp;hellip;
Social Media Twitch: phoebecreates Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: cute outfits Medium: ink and watercolour Description: This is the beginning of my 100 outfits challenge.</description></item><item><title>Harlem '33/'83</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-10-f4b3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-10-f4b3/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Colored Pencils.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Harlem &amp;#39;33/&amp;#39;83 Medium: Colored Pencils Description: ? (Wanted to reupload to fix how dark it was, sorry!</description></item><item><title>Zelda Study</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-10-04b4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-10-04b4/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: CSP with Basic Brushes.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Cindy said I was allowed. But also, I really admire the character designs in Breath Of The Wild.
Social Media Twitch: hadespsd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Zelda Study Medium: CSP with Basic Brushes Description: Cindy said I was allowed.</description></item><item><title>Folds</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-10-66bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-10-66bc/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Edgy Basket Baller
Social Media Twitch: lyfeu Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Folds Medium: Photoshop Description: Edgy Basket Baller Social Media: www.twitch.com/lyfeu</description></item><item><title>Pulling Back From The Edge</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-10-1944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-10-1944/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Study of movement and clothing from an incredible performance by Kai during a Freestyle Roulette (link with timestamp cause y&amp;rsquo;all should watch this performance anyway https://youtu.be/XFUyeYrCcN0?t=280) - this moment was so emotive I just felt pulled to paint it in particular. Clothing and hoomans are not my forte.
lithiumreflections (IG, tumblr, twitter)</description></item><item><title>Sitting</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-10-d23d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-10-d23d/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes just a simple qurl wearing street style. uhhh lines/colouring isn’t super clean and I didn’t add shading but I like it as is tbh.
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Sitting Medium: Procreate Description: just a simple qurl wearing street style.</description></item><item><title>The Bat Man</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/wellcookedegg-week-10-992c/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick
Social Media Twitter: well_egg Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: The Bat Man Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I went for some baggier street wear cause street wear is sick</description></item><item><title>Apple 16</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Apple.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This apple has weird fashion.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Apple 16 Medium: Apple Description: This apple has weird fashion. Social Media: https://www.instagram.com/jumpingbeansz/; https://www.twitch.tv/jumpingbeansz ;</description></item><item><title>Folds</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-10-66bc/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Folds Medium: Clip Studio Description: Baggy fashion kimono wear 🇯🇵</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the brave new world of me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-9-70ee/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.
Social Media Instagram: billelhambli Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Welcome to the brave new world of me Medium: Affinity photo Description: My new year resolution in 2021 was to start a new chapter after the long and exhausting rollercoaster called 2020.</description></item><item><title>7/11 Burrito</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-9-d52c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-9-d52c/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Bold strokes&amp;rdquo; sounds upbeat, aggressive, complex, and coloured by live instrumentals.
Before the &amp;lsquo;rona there was live music. For those who have not been in a crowd or performed contemporary music, there is nothing like it. Every mistake, every ad lib: the energy is secondary to nothing. It is extremely obvious when watching some of the best bands out there that everybody is having so much fun.</description></item><item><title>ANIME AM I RIGHT</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-9-c756/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: digital painting.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams. wow pretty eyes yeet. huff huff huff join my giveaway LOL
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 **Title: ANIME AM I RIGHT** Medium: digital painting Description: 30 min speed run submission, i want to live out my high school artist dreams.</description></item><item><title>Be Bold and Believe</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-9-2b7b/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tomorrow I will compete in my Jiu Jisu tournament so I try to keep my mind calm and did something related to my feelings. the moment I&amp;rsquo;m on the mat is the moment I feel alive. 6 mins. only 6 mins to see how far I have become compared to myself yesterday. Control my nerves and believe in my techniques, execute fast and believe I&amp;rsquo;ve got this.</description></item><item><title>Color factory</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-9-6e62/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: survival Minecraft.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1CrUiHBniouCtC2vncknVcsFT4cf-kVRzb--YlfKXxWA/edit?usp=sharing
Decided to use minecraft since I was in quarantine during the vacation and had time. Needed green dye to mix into cyan dye and so I made a cactus farm and built a factory around it. uses mostly blocks and stuff you can make from the dyes (also a little stone).</description></item><item><title>Flame Soul spirit</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-9-0514/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lyfeu-week-9-0514/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A soul entrapped in a body of rock burning its desire to live once more enabling the rock to become its own , the colour at the top i feel is where the soul of the fire and spirit clashing and trying to compromise with each other to both live within the body
twitch/tv/Lyfeu</description></item><item><title>Hi! I like shorts! They're comfy and easy to wear!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-9-c5dc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-9-c5dc/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (Photo set).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Celebrating the 25th Anniversary of Pokemon and myself, with a Pokemon that I like a lot. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;m still a youngster trainer class.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>I DON'T HAVE TIME TO COME UP WITH A TITLE ALREADY LATE AS-IS oh hang on CHOKE ME LIKE YOU HATE ME obviously sorry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-9-f05f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-9-f05f/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil, watercolor, acrylics, promarkers, various fineliners, ink, hands, anger, frustration, stress, acceptance, coffee.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so this kind of didn&amp;rsquo;t happen as intended, just smashed together everything that had color on it
consider that bit inspired by @DynoLoafer
Also @Mrop2000 was my spirit animal
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Introspection</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-9-9eca/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Did something more simple this week since I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling a little burned out. I wanted to do something cooler for this week cuz I liked the prompt buuuut I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t. Either way, this piece was partially inspired by Omori&amp;rsquo;s art style, hope people like it lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>iPod Nano</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;rsquo;d enjoy from the prompt. (Late as usual LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: iPod Nano Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: I&amp;#39;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;#39;d enjoy from the prompt.</description></item><item><title>POV you find another VHS tape, and your sleep deprived self slots it in the player…</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes !!!epilepsy warning!!!
rhythm and flow? say no more.. didn’t have much time this week so this was a very quickly put-together and rushed but i found this super funky cmyk filter on insta… this was such a headache to edit lol, but hope you enjoy!! you asked for statement so… i look like a giant but i promise you it’s 60% camera angle 40% my 8” pole heels xd</description></item><item><title>wikipedia</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-9-1267/</guid><description> Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes yo who else misses hatsune miku
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: wikipedia Medium: Procreate Description: yo who else misses hatsune miku Social Media: @/pumpkanart on twitter and twitch</description></item><item><title>Chromatic Dragon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is what happens when I stare at Hydro74&amp;rsquo;s work for long enough&amp;hellip; Something very different for me, but I really love how this turned out!
A CMYK Dragon, just for you Cindy 😘
Technically based of the Black Dragons from D&amp;amp;D cause I&amp;rsquo;m a nerd. Enjoy!
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>CMY</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-9-7236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-9-7236/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wow this hurts my eyes. This was meant to be like a 10 min sketch and it looks like one, but I spent more like 30 mins on it.
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: CMY Medium: Photoshop Description: Wow this hurts my eyes.</description></item><item><title>Repetition, Reminisce, Reflection</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-9-fe02/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Suminagashi (Japanese ink marbling technique) on handmade paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;It reflects me. It reflects you&amp;hellip;Two lines become one&amp;rdquo; - Mirrors by STUTS (ft. SUMIN, Daichi Yamamoto &amp;amp; CHINZA DOPENESS) (the song I was vibin to while making this piece: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wdwzLaljOzw)
While working alongside printmaking friends on a group zoom call, I was suddenly taken back to a time where we were all gathered together at our university&amp;rsquo;s studio, working until the sky was dark and blasting music three octaves too loud.</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation - Welcome To Hell</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-9-7020/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to express in one way or another this powerlessness I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling for a very long time now. I based part of the concept and the title from a scene in the video game Spec Ops: The Line.
Social Media Instagram: and Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Berry Dragon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-9-8bb3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-9-8bb3/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Adapted public domain artwork (https://flic.kr/p/hS7KBV) - given fresh lines and CYMK colors.
twitter lireflections, IG/tumblr lithiumreflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 **Title: ** Berry Dragon Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: Adapted public domain artwork (https://flic.</description></item><item><title>Important Dream</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-9-8e62/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-9-8e62/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat. washi tape of betrayal).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Katamari Damacy (Song) Fanart, wanted something big and bright and cheerful. Also wanted practice drawing general &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo;, and write some japanese characters.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: Important Dream Medium: Color Pencils (CMYK) and fineliner pen on paper (feat.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Collage</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Wow I&amp;rsquo;m the first one submitting this week? That&amp;rsquo;s weird. Anyways, I decided for this week to draw a bunch of dragons because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide on just one with all the thumbnails I made! Each piece has it&amp;rsquo;s own title, as well as a color palette of only 10 colors (9 not including black) and wow it makes this bright!</description></item><item><title>Judgement</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-9-3785/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-9-3785/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: When I thought of what to draw for this theme I thought cyberpunk and cool flashing lights.
I realized I wasn&amp;rsquo;t that good at the subject yet and would need time to develop it so instead I went to my mor comfortable style.
This piece represents an innocent girl who never did anything wrong until she made a single mistake.</description></item><item><title>This is the literal worst shit i have created, i think my parent think im weird.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw a dude making cool advertisement with a TV as background and thought &amp;quot; hmmmm seems easy&amp;quot; then i proceed to do stupid things. my parents saw me do stupid things, and editing is hell. overall i rate the experience 4/10, maybe i would increase the score if I were more familiar with video editing</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-8-911a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/frog-glasses-week-8-911a/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hi im doing this piece while you’re going through the submissions =SPEED RUn= i missed the actual stream but metal goes brrrrrr :)
it’s a life study for the blueberries im eating rn while watching u. I want to work with more bold shapes. 21 minutes)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Amalagamation: Vague Memory</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-8-6f53/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Adobe Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is probably the laziest thing I&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, lol. I had other ideas in mind, but I junked them since I can&amp;rsquo;t pull it off.
Social Media Instagram: and Instagram: rjmmendoza444 Twitch: a1ewanrichards Twitch: a1ewanrichards#0881 Twitter: rjmendoza444 Twitter: rjmmendoza444 Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Angels in our Atmosphere</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-8-36ae/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing collage my dudes. From brainstorm to submission with was about 75 minutes. The prompt had me thinking about metal in art, so i drew images from photography (silver bromide development) to lithography/etching (metal plate prints) to digital art (like&amp;hellip; computers and stuff). The birds are just to cover her nipples</description></item><item><title>Brooke Rivers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-8-3521/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wow! This was stressful! The time limit and outside stressors made this a particularly bad drawing experience, buuut I did finish this at the very least. There are things about it I would&amp;rsquo;ve added or changed if I had the time, but I obviously had to rush, so&amp;hellip; oh well.
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Fixation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-8-0f99/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A visual ode to my need for repetitious tasks and the nonsensical thoughts that pass through my brain when I&amp;rsquo;m half asleep. I love focusing on the materiality of objects and photos, so I focused on using just pieces of the photo to construct an abstract image and let it tell its own story.</description></item><item><title>Foish</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-8-71ed/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: graphic, Illustrator.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now? i love him&amp;rsquo;st tho hehehe practiced some illustrator too
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 **Title: Foish** Medium: graphic, Illustrator Description: Something about a brassy steam punk-y fish, it looks a tad japanese now?</description></item><item><title>Just a couple of Daft Punks</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt image immediately made me think of a vinyl record so I was thinking of doing something with Daft Punk as soon as I read the prompt. I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty big fan of theirs and was disappointed to hear that they were splitting up. But boy do they have a metal sheen.</description></item><item><title>Out of Touch Tuesday</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I saw the swirl of the image and straight away wanted to do something kind of surreal but still quick and readable. I won&amp;rsquo;t lie, this probably took a bit over the 2 hour time limit, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a brainstorming session so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna count it as a work hour. Also I got the day wrong but shhh that adds to the out of touch-ness.</description></item><item><title>Swim for the Ball</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-8-f7d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-8-f7d9/</guid><description> Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: Swim for the Ball Medium: Pencil on Paper Description: Don&amp;#39;t have a printer so had to trace off my computer screen</description></item><item><title>The Herald</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TWO HOURS! incoherent eldritch screeching
Firstly: WHY!!!
Secondly: I would like the record to show that I did in fact completely this piece within the two hours (brainstorming included)
So for this I figured we&amp;rsquo;d go back to &amp;ldquo;basics&amp;rdquo; and hop on board the spoopy train. Since the og pics were from a church, I started thinking along the line of angels, creepy angels&amp;hellip; then got inspired by Peter Mohrbacher&amp;rsquo;s angel paintings and ended up with a Dark Souls boss 🤷‍♀️</description></item><item><title>Wall- E fan Art</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-8-fde4/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes so as soon as I look at the photo the light caught my eyes immediately. I have been thinking about Wall-E a lot this week because of Do-E, and then I saw Jump in the bin submission which is &amp;ldquo;trashbin&amp;rdquo; and then my brain just blink and connect everything together&amp;hellip;.Here we go, my boy Wall-E using the photo supplied.</description></item><item><title>Jupiter Falling</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-8-bf02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-8-bf02/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Really just leaned into the original photograph, only removing the outer rim and clone stamping out some of the edge punctures. Took visual inspiration from the recent NASA/Juno pictures of Jupiter, just played with colors and swirls.
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>One Drug Please</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-8-0c0e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-8-0c0e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Audio/Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Alternative title: playing around with Live 11&amp;rsquo;s new cool features.
&amp;ldquo;High Sheen&amp;rdquo; reminds me of a few things. Getting high (on life) in a club, shiny lights from the sun and from stage lights, bright, natural naive feelings. &amp;ldquo;Sheen&amp;rdquo; of youth, so to speak, and stuff I have nearly no experience with at all.</description></item><item><title>1:43:51 (PB)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-8-fb4e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Oil sticks &amp;amp; oil crayons + some paper cutout.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Printed out the prompt&amp;rsquo;s image - turns out I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any black ink, just color so it looked .. yeah. Took a different approach on each of the two canvas. Finally, after painting was done, I cut out some parts of the prompt image from the paper and just sort of slapped it on.</description></item><item><title>Do what make you happy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-6-0868/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Don’t think I’ll have time to do week 8 art cause of midterms but I manage to finish week 6 ; Life can be a little stressful sometimes so take the time to do the things u love; happy late lunar new year everyone 😃
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Pretty, Ain't It?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Someone had a mighty fine belt-buckle, so I.. borrowed it.&amp;rdquo;
This was a very interesting challenge! Decided to go for a painting-like piece with the belt-buckle being the main focus! If it&amp;rsquo;s hard to see, the texture from the resource is on the belt buckle! I timed myself and I had 7 minutes before the two hour mark!</description></item><item><title>Spicy Tuna</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-8-6a17/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional art. Copic markers and pens, gell pen..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Spicy Tuna
A delicious Japanese meal for lunch - a bowl of spicy tuna and rice with chopped onion garnish, along with a cup of maccha.
I applied the photo texture to the maccha cup, the rice bowl, and the ground tuna. I drew in gel pen white on the cup and bowl surfaces to simulate ceramic gloss.</description></item><item><title>Desert~~ (Creative I know)~~</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-7-c62c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-7-c62c/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Keeping a focus on form, shape, and color contrast.
IG/tumblr: lithiumreflections
((Oops initially uploaded with a layer missing))
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 **Title: ** Desert~~ (Creative I know)~~ Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: Keeping a focus on form, shape, and color contrast.</description></item><item><title>felled tree</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-8-24cb/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes only used the picture and the colors of the picture. Plus the little tree dawing I made and a leaf brush. Forgot to stay metallic
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: felled tree Medium: ibispaint x Description: only used the picture and the colors of the picture.</description></item><item><title>High Sheen from Jimmy Neutron</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-8-41d3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-8-41d3/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Woman in armour&amp;hellip; high sheen from Jimmy Neutron
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 8 Title: High Sheen from Jimmy Neutron Medium: Procreate Description: Woman in armour.</description></item><item><title>My favourite artist</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-8-02a0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-8-02a0/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: : Phone.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My favourite music artist Ariana Grande and her sing 34 35.
I wanted to draw her for a while but was never really good enough so I tried again and think this turned out really well
The shiny white on the cardigan jacket thingy is the light to show how it&amp;rsquo;s reflective I incorporated the wood in the base of the &amp;ldquo;snow globe?</description></item><item><title>Trashbin</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Autodesk sketch.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw the prompt, saw time-limit, thought to self &amp;ldquo;what do i draw well?&amp;rdquo;. Answer: Trash. This is a warning, dont read too much into my thinking process (colours were abstracted from the source image)
, / (cuz symbolisms)
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Angry Bird</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-7-fbb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-7-fbb3/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ballpoint and hand smudge.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Who is the intruder in the desert? Is it the bird? Is it the sun? Is it Super Mario Bros?
No thanks
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Angry Bird Medium: Ballpoint and hand smudge Description: Who is the intruder in the desert?</description></item><item><title>Academy, Disrepair</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;rsquo;t normally draw backgrounds. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a colour scheme I liked that worked with the monochrome sketch so I kept it minimal.
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Academy, Disrepair Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;#39;t normally draw backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Desert Plains</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-7-a9a8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-7-a9a8/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I fucking love NieR:Automata.
Social Media Instagram: poruchan_920 Twitch: poru_chan Twitter: poruchan09 Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Desert Plains Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: I fucking love NieR:Automata. Social Media: https://twitter.</description></item><item><title>desert strands</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 80 minute speed draw this time happy with the result though ! inspired by a lot of the stippling i&amp;rsquo;ve seen entered by the amazing artists in this week&amp;rsquo;s submissions ! attempted to tie the sand dunes into the hair? no real reason why other than i thought it might be fun to try ;; (to whom it may concern at turnitin, originally submitted at 11:57pm)</description></item><item><title>Dune Surfing</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-7-3510/</guid><description> Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: clip studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes has anyone ever tried it?
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Medium: clip studio Title: Dune Surfing Description: has anyone ever tried it?</description></item><item><title>Footprints</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-7-9d88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-7-9d88/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4nay640JrxBZhNMiVIYTFg
(Headphones will benefit you for this song).
&amp;ldquo;Desert&amp;rdquo; to me means the mixolydian mode (a tonal &amp;ldquo;pattern&amp;rdquo;). You know, like The Beatles (Norwegian Wood, I Feel Fine) and a lot of classic rock around that era. &amp;ldquo;Space&amp;rdquo; sounds like space emulation: reverb. The theme also influenced the lyrics greatly, which were written before the music.</description></item><item><title>Hey you! Yeah, up here!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-aa73/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-7-aa73/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I didn&amp;rsquo;t really get to post many wips for this piece because Discord decided it was too unholy to be seen before it was fully developed, but here it is! Did a screenshot redraw of a place called Scorched Gorge, which a desert area in Bugsnax :3</description></item><item><title>placeholder edit later</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-7-c2c0/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Scene: Oh no, one of the remnant forces of the humans are being hunted by the reptilian empire led by Hiss Majesty - but the sand starts rumbling and what rises out of it?
Three panel piece, there&amp;rsquo;s some storyboarding done for the pre-first-panel storytelling as well, but cut it down to two of the nicest looking key panels (+ a dramatic final one).</description></item><item><title>SOL 0</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This morning the Perseverance Rover landed safely in the Jezero Crater on Mars. It&amp;rsquo;s NASA&amp;rsquo;s fifth Rover to land on the red planet and, other than Curiosity, is the only thing &amp;lsquo;alive&amp;rsquo; on the dusty world.
Art wise, a bit of a quick and dirty one. (Was starting to run out of time 😅) I used the 3D model viewer of Perseverance to get the rover as accurate as possible.</description></item><item><title>Strange Sands</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-7-78e8/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ink on paper, a comic!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love alliteration lol!
hey isn&amp;rsquo;t is kinda mysterious? I got this idea from when crabs would dig holes at the beach and spit out the water. Finding that in the desert would be super creepy&amp;hellip; also stippling is hard. I do really like this though and hope you do too!</description></item><item><title>The Sandstorm</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TW FOR &amp;ldquo;BLOOD&amp;rdquo; (just in case)
This sandstorm is fogging up my judgement. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see you. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see my goddamn hand out in front of me&amp;hellip; Please. Don&amp;rsquo;t blame yourself, none of this is your fault. I was the one who killed them, can&amp;rsquo;t you see the blood? Just.</description></item><item><title>Three Celebrations (Change)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography, Clay Figure &amp;amp; Cake.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 3 white chocolate caramel souffle cakes to celebrate three different events.
Growth: 1st cake for Herschel&amp;rsquo;s birthday, sadly we missed his birthday party due to lockdown.
Goodbyes: 2nd cake for my roommate who decided his job wasn&amp;rsquo;t worth his sanity anymore and quit.
New Beginnings: 3rd cake for my friend Pete who&amp;rsquo;s moving to a new place!</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-7-911a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Everyone have their own desert to carry. And flower can grow in the desert you know 🙂
Inspiration: orange sand colour of Australian desert and Goodenia-one of Australian desert Plants Combined with my goal of digital portrait painting this year.
Hope you all enjoy this work.
And yes flowers can grow in the desert.</description></item><item><title>A Flash of Peace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-6-68da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-6-68da/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A blanket, the sound of rain, a chill breeze, and distant thunder&amp;hellip; these were the things I summoned up when I thought about simple joys in my life. This is pretty outside my comfort zone but I like the piece still.
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Rain Over the Desert</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-7-42e5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-7-42e5/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A panorama of a rainstorm passing through the Sonoran Desert
https://500px.com/p/antiiobs08
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Rain Over the Desert Medium: Photography Description: A panorama of a rainstorm passing through the Sonoran Desert Social Media: https://500px.</description></item><item><title>Resistance 3: When The Lands Become Graveyards</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-6498/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-7-6498/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes @rjmmendoza on IG/Twitter | A1EwanRichards on Twitch
It&amp;rsquo;s not a desert in the typical sense. It&amp;rsquo;s an amalgam of sugar cane farms and the concept of &amp;ldquo;peace of the cemetery,&amp;rdquo; referring to a quote by St. Oscar Romero. The title is a rough translation of a poem by Filipino poet Axel Pinpin, originally titled &amp;ldquo;Kung Puntod na ang Lupa&amp;rdquo; (literal: If the Land is a Tomb&amp;quot;).</description></item><item><title>Seconds in Sand</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-7-7f38/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (shot w/ a Canon 40D).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s often times when I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in an internal &amp;lsquo;desert&amp;rsquo;, where ideas don&amp;rsquo;t come easily and time slips by. Yet somehow the creative spark is always hovering in between this barren space and the looming deadline, and often I just find myself having to be patient for the right moment rather than to grasp at the sands.</description></item><item><title>Skull</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-7-c59a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-7-c59a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes big skull&amp;hellip; in desert&amp;hellip; giant? Who kno&amp;hellip;.?
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Skull Medium: Procreate Description: big skull... in desert... giant? Who kno....? Socials: @paintsepsi on everything!</description></item><item><title>Sunset at Calico Desert</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-7-cd92/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes When I heard the prompt was about deserts and what lived in them I immediately thought of stardew valley! I love that big dragon skeleton, hungering for the sun. I was aiming for a phone background look, so please feel free to use it!
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Sandy Point! Population: me</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-7-d10c/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes dropped randomly in death valley on google maps and used that as my reference. Drew a bighorn&amp;rsquo;s head, decided to make it a sassy cowboy.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Welcome to Sandy Point!</description></item><item><title>Ghost City (ft bad cropping)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The huge creature was a character that I had written about, inspired by League of Legend&amp;rsquo;s RekSai and Pokemon&amp;rsquo;s Garchomp. styles influenced by chinese/japanese calligraphy cuz was triggered that i had to do a calligraphy work in non-chinese/japanese materials.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Nian Gao, old and new</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes For this years cny my mom shared some old memories of her grandma making nian gao and having mom man the steamer for hours until it was done. We then made some ourselves as a way of passing on a tradition I never knew we had. My mom doesn&amp;rsquo;t normally share fond memories of her childhood so this felt like something worth commemorating.</description></item><item><title>Desert heat</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: blender.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i wanted to try a new something new so instead of photoshop i used blender this is my first time using the program and i think it came out pretty good i dont really have a but i hope I did a ok job 😊
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Tenacity (Year of the Ox)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eyyojimbo-week-6-fd6f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eyyojimbo-week-6-fd6f/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought I’d do a piece that describes the appreciation I have for the resilience of humankind through the struggles that we’ve faced this past year, and how that strength will continue into the next. Going for a Magic the Gathering vibe. Also, this is my first post so hello!
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Perspectives of Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-6-9323/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-6-9323/</guid><description> Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The cubes are symbolic of the fragments of love and how each fragment, although individually &amp;lsquo;rough-edged&amp;rsquo; can together create a smooth whole 🙂
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Title: Perspectives of Love** Medium: Paint Tool SAI Description: The cubes are symbolic of the fragments of love and how each fragment, although individually &amp;#39;rough-edged&amp;#39; can together create a smooth whole 🙂 Socials: @Scimister on twitch</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: Smile and Smile</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-3360/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-6-3360/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ink on paper, 9x12 inches..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ink on paper, 9x12 inches.
Another week, another rush job lol. I had an initial idea but I dumped it since I couldn&amp;rsquo;t execute it. I made this just now.
Anyway&amp;hellip; I tried to recreate the moment I shared with friend and a crush from around 2015. I earlier sent her a message apologizing for &amp;ldquo;being weird&amp;rdquo; (not my words) after being scolded by someone for acting weird towards two girls.</description></item><item><title>Ghosties</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was meant to be a Week 5 submission but it fits Week 6 for me too. I love my OCs, and it&amp;rsquo;s been great to have them as a creative &amp;amp; emotional outlet! (Also love being able to finish art even if it&amp;rsquo;s not on time LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>It's just a painting why does it have to have a title? But fine, the title as a noise, like horses neigh kind of.</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-6-9a3d/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Trad art, watercolor.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Interpretation of the prompt; I sat down and did some painting that I simply loved doing, no research, no finding references, no working through a concept, just doing a sketch and putting paint on paper, feeling a harmonious flow in the work itself unlike the frustration I usually feel while doing art. It was kind of nice.</description></item><item><title>Love in the air</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-6-834b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-6-834b/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: : Ibis paint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes twitch: leo_d3mom
based from girl in red . I&amp;rsquo;m part of the LGBTQ+ community and it basically represents us
Sorry the is a mess also I&amp;rsquo;m a growing artist so sorry if it&amp;rsquo;s bad it cringe
Medium : Ibis paint x
Sorry the is a mess
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Midnight Magic Musings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The late nights we stay up talking about D&amp;amp;D. Those quiet moments when the rest of the world is asleep. We bounce dumb ideas off each other just to see where they&amp;rsquo;ll land. You have no idea how much I appreciate my Resident Wizard&amp;hellip;
On the art side of things; I really enjoy drawing characters and their interactions, and believe it or not, I do like drawing cute things 😛</description></item><item><title>Paper Aeroplanes demo.mp3, collab with @papapastry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A demo track of our collab song &amp;lsquo;Paper Aeroplanes&amp;rsquo;, capturing an instance between two lovers and what their simple but gentle love brings.
paper aeroplanes DEMO track: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/fuck-so-late-god-fucking-damnit
the lyrics were based off poetry i wrote: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1v7MNRHeg6fDwUsURPJAf1XSptglTolwA1KtohM_4Rbk/edit?usp=sharing
charmandaar on twitch ()</description></item><item><title>Paper Pond</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-6-56a2/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Origami + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Going back to my first art love - paper. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been surrounded by paper and origami ever since I was kid, and wanted to pay homage to both my roots and the medium that has so much potential. Also I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting a piece to bring in the two parts of my heritage in one piece; my last name roughly translates to &amp;lsquo;ferry across the river&amp;rsquo; and my chinese name means &amp;lsquo;yellow love lotus&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Roleplay! (and a puppet show I suppose)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-6-46a6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes After a lot of thinking about the prompt, I&amp;rsquo;d say that I love to roleplay! Dyno and I rp all the time, so I drew us performing a puppet show! Just to give you an idea, there are 723,445 words across all our rp transcripts including ones that aren&amp;rsquo;t finished lmao
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Self portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-6-eb83/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;rsquo;s still a long way to go. so here it is first time drawing myself haha
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6- Simple love Title: Self portrait Description: Learning to love myself is not easy and It&amp;#39;s still a long way to go.</description></item><item><title>Slice of Life</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Cutting close again, wowie! Oh well, I like how this came out even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a few doodles of me and my best friend! She&amp;rsquo;s the light of my life and I love her with all my heart, she makes me so incredibly happy and has probably indirectly saved my life. Oh, and she&amp;rsquo;s in the server, so expect a long-ass wall of appreciation in discussions eventually!</description></item><item><title>solemn night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/okie.dokie.enoki-week-6-42f0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/okie.dokie.enoki-week-6-42f0/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i didn’t want to study so i made this ❤️
pov: you’re god but also a third wheel&amp;lt;/3
Social Media Instagram: okie.dokie.enoki Twitch: okie_dokie_enoki Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: week: 6 title: solemn night medium: procreate description: i didn’t want to study so i made this ❤️ pov: you’re god but also a third wheel&amp;lt;/3 social: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Sweet Nothings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Modelling Clay (Sculpey).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A lot of people give chocolates for Valentines and other romantic holidays. I&amp;rsquo;m not a huge fan of chocolate but I really like the little gourmet ones. I think these ones will last a little longer than most.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Week 6</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-6-1936/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-6-1936/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The earliest time I can remember myself loving drawing was when I was 5 and completely immersed in the given task of drawing a yellow house with a red roof, with apple trees, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s favourite quarter sun. Something about the way the pencil felt scraping across the paper encapsulated me, and before I knew it, 3 hours had past before I even looked away from the page.</description></item><item><title>Dreams in TechieLand</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-6-f17c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-6-f17c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes San Francisco, sunsets, stargazing, and day dreaming are what inspired this piece. 🙂 The simple things.
Social Media Instagram: austeezus Twitter: psykoframe Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: Dreams in TechieLand Medium: Krita Description: San Francisco, sunsets, stargazing, and day dreaming are what inspired this piece.</description></item><item><title>Simple Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-6-1e74/</guid><description>Direct link to a .pdf file.
Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, and publication.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t like Valentines Days but I wanted to talk about what I loved, pets!
Animals show love in such wonderful ways and I&amp;rsquo;m so happy!!!!
The main submission is a lil A6 zine you can fold yourself if you have a b+W a4 printer!</description></item><item><title>Cyber Love</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-6-44f6/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes reminds me of my best friend in the world (we were friends for almost 13 years, till they&amp;rsquo;ve moved to Egypt) we still talk, but it&amp;rsquo;s not like before cz we&amp;rsquo;re both a bit busy. Like that heart, our friendship became cold and hollow, with the screens being our only connection. Lol, that&amp;rsquo;s so depressive; anyway, Alexa play Driver&amp;rsquo;s license by Olivia Rodrigo.</description></item><item><title>inanimate objects that give me comfort</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</guid><description> Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;rsquo;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: inanimate objects that give me comfort Medium: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil Description: I don&amp;#39;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;#39;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down</description></item><item><title>Magical girl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-6-7ed9/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love doing character design, and with simple love the first thing I thought of was Madoka and magical girls. For ‘balance’ I made her very symmetrical. She’s inspired by roses. I can imagine her on a team of flower magical girls fighting against weed monsters of the week. Very Tokyo mew style! I wanna draw their whole team&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Everlasting Hope</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-6-d09a/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night. Why is it called Everlasting Hope? well, that&amp;rsquo;s just something i need in life i guess. hope you enjoyed it!
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 6 Title: Everlasting Hope Medium: Photoshop Description: I like the oceans and i like the city skyline in the night.</description></item><item><title>Ducks by docks</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-6-3827/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I like ducks. A mama duck loves her ducklings. I love the water texture stamp.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: Ducks by docks Medium: Krita with mouse Description: I like ducks.</description></item><item><title>green eyed girl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes another last minute entry really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !
Social Media Twitch: fonzaku Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: green eyed girl Medium: csp Description: another last minute entry really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !</description></item><item><title>It's Not Living (If It's Not With You)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-6-185c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-6-185c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to do a non paint style for this one and was hugely hugely inspired by elliotisacoolguy on twitch and made something in his style. The title comes from this great The 1975 song, recc you all listen to it!. I made a few options just to make it a bit more interesting</description></item><item><title>The introspection of self, the different facades of life and embrace of the multifaceted appearences</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Video of beansz wearing clothing (aka i ran out of mediums, time to recycle).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In life we wear many masks (or shirts cuz i dont know the art of 变脸, aka chinese face mask changing), they are the many aspects of self, whether or not we like it or not. The introspection of the multiple sides is what makes us individuals and whole.</description></item><item><title>[Title Too Long]</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-4a75/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-5-4a75/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: digital/ photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have
Social Media Instagram: soleil.boo Twitch: soleilboo Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5- Royal Green- Jade Stone I don&amp;#39;t have title for this portrait. Can someone name it?I just took on the meaning of Jade Stone which bring good luck, peace and harmony just like a smile did.</description></item><item><title>Big Green Dragon Kingdom</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-5-1d3c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-5-1d3c/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Music/Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In this technical folk metal piece, I focus on changing textures. The video will explain. This piece is very experimental and not meant for human consumption.
&amp;ldquo;Royal green&amp;rdquo; is musical imagery: &amp;ldquo;cold and hard&amp;rdquo; sounds like heavy metal and &amp;ldquo;jade&amp;rdquo; implies an opulence that cuts through: the kanun and saz instruments.</description></item><item><title>Decay</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-5-657f/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: colored pencils + ink.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Based off of the jade burial suits of the Han dynasty, which were ceremonial suits constructed from squares of jade and gold thread. There&amp;rsquo;s something very somber for me about these suits, where they are nearly identical and often have jade features placed to represent their face. also remind me never to do colored pencil drawings again cuz its too hard</description></item><item><title>Flow</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-5-f1a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/psyko-week-5-f1a7/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Acrylics.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took a lot of influence from the messy textures created by Jade. I made the loops start from point a to point b and have continuous flow while adding in different textures through paint splatters, sponges, and various paint strokes. I really just let it happen as I painted, while focusing on trying to create different textures.</description></item><item><title>Jade Bee</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-5-af61/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-5-af61/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A bee carved of jade, with translucent jade wings. Background flowers are a free CSP asset (ie I didn&amp;rsquo;t draw them).
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 5 **Title: ** Jade Bee Medium: Digital (Clip Studio Paint) Description: A bee carved of jade, with translucent jade wings.</description></item><item><title>Jade Dragon on plinth</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-5-8cfe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-5-8cfe/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital 3D (Blender).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not my model. I tried to model a dragon in 3D but I&amp;rsquo;m not good at sculpting, but the shading of the model, lighting and environment are my work. Added 4 pin lights to get the translucent jade effect inside the model.
Screen shot of my setup
Social Media Twitch: magus_hellwalker Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jaysom Kim</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-5-8858/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes There&amp;rsquo;s honestly a lot more to this but the concept was &amp;ldquo;jade teeth grills&amp;rdquo; and turned into asian fucc boi. This is like one of those pictures from a high concept idol photo book LOL///
((The bigger project will be worked on but have this pick up line as a sneak peak: Do you like curry?</description></item><item><title>Not My Forte</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Dragon shown (Astro): &amp;ldquo;Erhm&amp;hellip; are you sure all of this jade jewelry is considered attractive? There&amp;rsquo;s so many piercings&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Dragon offscreen (Backey): &amp;ldquo;Of course, your Highness! People will swoon for you and your glittery glory.&amp;rdquo;
Astro: &amp;ldquo;How do you know?&amp;rdquo;
Backey: &amp;ldquo;Uhm.. your Highness, word gets around eheh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; (sweating) &amp;hellip;Got this done without stress, yay!</description></item><item><title>Prosperity</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-5-ba91/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pretty busy this week, so something simple. The image of the expensive jade necklace reminded me of my string of pearls plant. Jade symbolises purification, nourishment and growth, so a plant seemed a perfect fit. My little SOP isn&amp;rsquo;t huge and majestic yet, but it grows a little and becomes a little more regal every day</description></item><item><title>Queen of the Skies</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt immediately made me think of the Rathian from Monster Hunter, the female counterpart to the series' flagship monster Rathalos. I tried to follow the prompt resource on recreating the jade effect using a small jade dragon as a reference.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Seal soapstone carving</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ocean-week-5-cdf0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ocean-week-5-cdf0/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: soapstone carving.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Although the prompt centres around green jade, I carved a piece of soapstone under the pretense of it as white jade. The design is influenced by a well known chinese poem: Quiet Night Thoughts by LiBai, it describes looking up at the moon and thinking of one’s family at home.
I have lightly inked the carving to contrast the details.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-5-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: A3 watercolor, some fine liners, autumn gold ink, a color pencil from a dusty box.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes On her birthday stream, cindy&amp;rsquo;s birthday wishes were &amp;ldquo;read chainsaw man&amp;rdquo; (lol no you read it) and &amp;ldquo;draw a dragon&amp;rdquo;. So here&amp;rsquo;s the dragon. Couple weeks late, but still.</description></item><item><title>Irene</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-5-79ae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-5-79ae/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes It’s a quick piece I drew based on Irene from Red Velvet! I tried to make her look kind of like a jade statue but the reflections and lighting I don’t quite understand yet&amp;hellip; time for some studies
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jade Possessions</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-5-f303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-5-f303/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: i love airbrushes.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Master of possession by games workshop base layer chaos black, Mr surfacer 1200 for zenithal shading then vallejo green ink airbrushed. The head and any other skulls had badab black wash applied just before the vallejo green ink was sprayed on.
i hate cleaning up after airbrushing.
a better angle</description></item><item><title>Jade scales</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-5-1b42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/d3m0n_msc-week-5-1b42/</guid><description> Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Ibis Paintx.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (double underscore
Social Media Instagram: leo__layne Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5 Title : Jade scales Medium: Digital - Ibis Paintx Socials: Insta-leo__layne (double underscore</description></item><item><title>Jade Temple</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-5-0702/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Procreate).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I started this piece by chaotically&amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple. it&amp;rsquo;s pretty messy &amp;lt;a:Bonk:769829350622232587&amp;gt;
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 5 Title: Jade Temple Medium: Digital (Procreate) Description: I started this piece by *chaotically*&amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; flicking my strokes everywhere cuz my brain cant think of anything, and now i have this abstract-y jade temple.</description></item><item><title>Jadeite</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-5-5cd3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/poru-week-5-5cd3/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital - Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes When I about the prompt being Jade related. I thought of the anime Houseki no Kuni, and am eager to try my hand to personify a crystal. My goal is to design a character that fits with the existing characters.
Social Media Instagram: poruchan_920 Twitch: poru_chan Twitter: poruchan09 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The Vessel</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-5-2ea5/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is my first time using photoshop for art, i tried making the short sword the centre piece of the piece, and i think the eyes make it pop. Hope people realise this is Itadori Yuuji from Jujutsu Kaisen
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Need a Hand?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-5-1fa0/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Finally, something not last minute! I decided to be experimental, doing a lineless piece to try and draw something more simple to avoid deadline anxiety. The hand was originally supposed to look like stone, but it looks more like a bush&amp;hellip; so I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a bush now lol
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Flawless</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Firstly; if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of &amp;ldquo;Kintsugi&amp;rdquo; before, you&amp;rsquo;re welcome 😛
Secondly, rendering jade is a mood&amp;hellip; cheers for that
This one took me a hot minute, but I think I&amp;rsquo;m starting to get the hang of digital painting somewhat 😅
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Jade Jian</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-5-d857/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ``
I painted the outline for the sword, tried painting the jade texture, but was displeased with the result, so I went and took a photo of the metal part of a local ww2 bunker and used it to make the texture by adjusting stuff here and there. The handle has the original bunker color</description></item><item><title>Behind The Doors</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (PhotoShop).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to make something that has a backstory so basically i had a friend that loved ninjas and they passed away a few years back so i wanted to do something not just for me but for them so i used the green (jade) as a representation of harmony/peace i hope you like it 😊</description></item><item><title>Green Emerald</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-5-6fad/</guid><description> Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Music cover
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 5 Title: Green Emerald Medium: ClipStudio Description: Music cover</description></item><item><title>Just Smile &amp; Smell the Flowers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-4-3b95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-4-3b95/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sometimes all it takes is the wonderful smell of flowers to put a smile on your face.
Social Media Instagram: moonlit_narcy Twitter: moonlit_narcy Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: Just Smile &amp;amp; Smell the Flowers Medium: Procreate Description: sometimes all it takes is the wonderful smell of flowers to put a smile on your face.</description></item><item><title>Coconut Crab</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-6b0e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-6b0e/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional, Copic markers.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: &amp;#34;Coconut Crab&amp;#34; Medium: Traditional, Copic markers Description: Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.</description></item><item><title>Green mOon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-4-54e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-4-54e5/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: PS.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Silhouette using negative space and texture to bring forward the figure and clothing. For movement, I went more subtle with hair flow that cuts through the face rather than drawn in. Note: save your work&amp;hellip;i lost the first draft and finished this 1 hr before deadline
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Here we go again</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Installation.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes stickman doesn&amp;rsquo;t go brrrrrr. stickman goes mining. but seriously though, royal green reminded me of the military (for some reason) and jade was the other prompt. so i had my uniform become be a jade mine. :P
ps i failed kindergarten, i cant use a pair of scissors
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Assimilation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i read a cool tumble post about a botanist burying a lamb bone under a tree and when they came back a few months later the tree had completely absorbed it. Left it to the last minute so it’s not exactly what I had in mind but better done than not so 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Bloody Fields</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Felt pen on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I actually struggled with the theme, but this came suddenly one day ago. Killing of farmers is still an issue in the Philippines as they struggle for genuine and lasting land reform. January 22 was also the anniversary of the Mendiola Massacre, where 13 farmers were killed when police dispersed a large farmer&amp;rsquo;s protest.</description></item><item><title>Blue</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/linalifox-week-4-9594/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/linalifox-week-4-9594/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I began this piece with a cyan background and started painting in a dark blue. I found it a challenge as I did not have the usual variety of colours to work with, especially with no red tone at all used in the skin. However I eventually learnt to blend the two blues and make them work and thoroughly enjoyed the process.</description></item><item><title>Bog</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, Pixaloop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At Camp Laywick, Raya’s peers are unable to see the silhouette of her distress against the thick of the fog&amp;hellip;
yet she is unable to see the silhouette beneath the water&amp;hellip;
[ I went for a “cover of a horror novel for teen readers” approach and did some video-editing to further portray rhythm and movement &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt; ]</description></item><item><title>Current</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-4-222a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-4-222a/</guid><description> Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes just an otter floating by, moving with the water
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 Title: Current Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: just an otter floating by, moving with the water</description></item><item><title>Dead Squats</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: Dead Squats Medium: Digital (Photopea) Description: I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.</description></item><item><title>Family Portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had the idea to do a cute wild west family portrait featuring the gays(tm) and their daughter, so I went with it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to spend as much time on this as I wanted to, but I&amp;rsquo;m still happy with it (also here&amp;rsquo;s a non-monochrome version lol)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Giraffe</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-4-427d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-4-427d/</guid><description> Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: PaintToolSAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A simplified digital wood carving of a giraffe 🐘
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 **Title: Giraffe** Medium: PaintToolSAI Description: A simplified digital wood carving of a giraffe 🐘 Socials: @Scimister on twitch 🦒</description></item><item><title>mask</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i really just wanted to create something ambiguous with this piece, no clear expression of good or evil, menacing or innocent completely up to interpretation. &amp;ldquo;movement&amp;rdquo; really got me thinking about the creeping of shadows so i tried to subject that in the piece! i guess it&amp;rsquo;s less of a silhouette but still a retreat into complete darkness/murkiness very last minute but happy with the outcome!</description></item><item><title>Morning Breeze</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Animation, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog. Low key a vibe, animation is hell, and I hope everyone likes it!
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Morning Breeze** Medium: Animation, CSP Description: Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog.</description></item><item><title>MURKE SHADOES</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-4-64a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-4-64a1/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Murky silhouettes&amp;rdquo; sounds metal and I got my wisdom teeth out so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really do what I usually do.
&amp;ldquo;Tone&amp;rdquo; reminds me of a sick and phat guitar toan that has &amp;ldquo;value.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Rhythm&amp;rdquo; obviously means blastbeats and &amp;ldquo;movement&amp;rdquo; means the movement of the head up and down as the music flows through your soul and out your butt.</description></item><item><title>POV you dust off an old VHS tape and slot it in the player…</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes took a video while i was lightly messing around on the pole and here we are..! thought the glitchy parts would be a fun way to transition between clips. i love playing with silhouettes when i dance and thought this may be a cool idea to encompasses murky shadows and rhythm/movement too.</description></item><item><title>Snap Shot 1</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/av-week-4-3f90/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/av-week-4-3f90/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes OKAY so this is a snapshot of life. There is a little darkness and a little light in everything you do. #yinandyangvibes
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: Week 4 Title: Snap Shot 1 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: OKAY so this is a snapshot of life.</description></item><item><title>You Ain't No Bounty Hunter</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Whew, this one was close! Sucks that I had to kinda rush at the end because this was submitted on a school night, but I think it still came out really well! I hope his expression scares you because it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to lol. The only story I&amp;rsquo;ll give is something/someone hurt his boyfriend pretty badly and he&amp;rsquo;s not happy about it.</description></item><item><title>1:21 AM</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Acrylic paint (Magenta/yellow mix for orange, winsor violet with a bit of magenta for the hand).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tried to capture desperation, intensity and passion. Didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to make the indentations left by the fingers the way I wanted - the idea of the situation is someone digging her nails into the back of her lover.</description></item><item><title>costume change</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw &amp;lsquo;state of change&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;movement&amp;rsquo; and that was it for me! i forgot it was monochromatic entirely oops
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: costume change Medium: csp!</description></item><item><title>Dancing Cloud</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-4-c9e7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-4-c9e7/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A one minute gesture sketch turned into a monochrome piece where negative space was used to explore values. Internally mad at the anatomy being off but I promised myself to only work from the gesture and not to spend an hour fussing over making the form precise. It was fun erasing to add value though.</description></item><item><title>Façade</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ink + paper collage.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Delving a bit personal with this piece. Often there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between the person I present to others - usually my business persona I use for my work that seems to have everything orderly and &amp;lsquo;put together&amp;rsquo;, while my internal self always feels like it&amp;rsquo;s in a state of at least minor chaos and has to navigate the unknown without guidance.</description></item><item><title>Practice</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil , sketch pens.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is a martial arts style from India called Kalari, it&amp;rsquo;s really aggressive and involves lots of movement. I tried gesture drawing for the first time, so i guess not bad?
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm and Tones Outine</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-4-0b03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-4-0b03/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: free photo editor thing idk.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw rhythm and tones in the outines of the prompt.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 Title: Rhythm and Tones Outine Medium: free photo editor thing idk Description: i saw rhythm and tones in the outines of the prompt.</description></item><item><title>The Search</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Search
Murky, silhouette&amp;hellip; well, I must oblige! (It&amp;rsquo;s like you want me to draw spoopy shit) 😛
Decided to contrast this with my last two pieces by using mainly lighter values. And since we&amp;rsquo;re looking at movement, thought I&amp;rsquo;d try and pump in some more overt narrative stuff too.
Enjoy!
Social Media N/A.</description></item><item><title>cat&lt;a:B8vibe:776693937498095637> (cant think of a title xd)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes It&amp;rsquo;s my first time creating something graphic art-y I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt;
(might stream sometime in 2021 &amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; )
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: cat&amp;lt;a:B8_vibe:776693937498095637&amp;gt; (cant think of a title xd) Medium: Procreate Description: It&amp;#39;s my first time creating something *graphic art-y* I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt; Socials: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Sleepless Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn’t use one color but I tried to stick with cold colors? Worked on value and tones? Is floating considered rhythm and movement? (Honestly idk, still new to all these art vocabulary xD). i hope this respect the rules of the challenge Implemented some contrast and circle shape from week 3 challenge so I don’t forget the notions I’ve learned.</description></item><item><title>Stress</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</guid><description>View on External Website. Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Game.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought I could finish this within 2 days (including learning + execution), ended up having to scrap a lot of the ideas due to my lack of knowledge and sleep deprivation. (definitely not my proudest project, bad coding ethics, cutting corners)
https://jumpingbeans.itch.io/week4 (&amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; aka shitpost download page)
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Icarus and the Sun</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soggyissoggy-week-3-433e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/soggyissoggy-week-3-433e/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Pretty late to the party but here we go.
a reimagination of the classical story. I try to make use of circular composition to portray the relationship between the two figures.
Social Media Twitch: soggyricecracker Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Pretty late to the party but here we go.</description></item><item><title>Joker</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-4-e553/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-4-e553/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes SO, I started a concept on stream, I wasn’t happy with it, and then continued working on it until it became completely different (other than being P5 related). So now I’m here, 4 hours later, with a different piece. I love the use of silhouettes in P5 and it just clicked with me to do something related to it for this submission!</description></item><item><title>Orange jump</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Orange jump ** Medium: Krita with mouse Description: Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.</description></item><item><title>beach 🙂</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-4-1ce3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-4-1ce3/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Photo and Adobe Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes this image was captured a few years ago on the southwest coast, at sunset as the sky cleared after a storm. it was already near monochrome, but i dropped the exposure to play with the value a bit
edit: this came out a bit dim in discord yikes
nah 🙂
Social Media N/A.</description></item><item><title>Gui</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-3-4532/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-3-4532/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Felt and ink on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I looked up the flag of Okinawa and it was perfect with what I had in mind. The man in the center is a sketch of Kamejiro Senaga, one of the pioneers of the peace movement in Okinawa to expel the US bases hosted in the islands. &amp;ldquo;Gui&amp;rdquo; is the title of a composition by Japanese composer Ryuichi Sakamoto created for a feature film about Kamejiro&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Lonely in the Quartz desert</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-3-8cfa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/thelagexpert-week-3-8cfa/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Affinity Photo.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes lost in the desert, not really what I imagined (was afraid to post it), but will finish it as soon as I get better; it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to give lonely and cold vibes. Will do better next week hopefully.
Social Media Instagram: billelhambli Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Shine No Shogun</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-3-a911/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-3-a911/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Shogun of Death is a character ive been working on for a while ( i say working, its an idea in my head). Shoguns are really cool and ive been wanting to draw one so i did. The Shoguns were generals, and the shogun of death leads the army of the dead alongside his opposite, the Shogun of Light (more on that later)</description></item><item><title>'0</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-3-292d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-3-292d/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to draw so I drew something horny, sorry. She sure has a lot of red circles tho.
@/jorchaelp on twitter and @/jrchlp.png on insta
Social Media Instagram: jrchlp.png Twitter: jorchaelp Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: :&amp;#39;0 Medium: Photoshop Description: Didn&amp;#39;t know what to draw so I drew something horny, sorry.</description></item><item><title>A Shining Star</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-3-4fca/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-3-4fca/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sooo, week 3, huh? Due to school and my personal life, this came out rather rushed&amp;hellip; However, I still like the character design I came up with! The background was inspired by a certain rhythm game, kudos to you if you know the one I&amp;rsquo;m talking about ;p
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>am i coming outta left field</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-3-c968/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-3-c968/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i have a really involved animatic in my head set to rebel just for kicks. i will complete it One Day. here&amp;rsquo;s a gal from it
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: am i coming outta left field Medium: csp Description: i have a really involved animatic in my head set to rebel just for kicks.</description></item><item><title>Bat Cave</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-3-4d1b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-3-4d1b/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes put a circle on top of another and used the eraser tool to create the image and expose the red underneath
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: Bat Cave Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: put a circle on top of another and used the eraser tool to create the image and expose the red underneath</description></item><item><title>Behold my stand - [BRIGHT EYES!!]</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-3-b87b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-3-b87b/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Ink (+watercolour for the red), a little bit of digital post editing to even out the whiteout and broken paper (PLEASE TEACH ME DIGITAL EDITING SOMEONE).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes DAMN IT DIDN&amp;rsquo;T KEEP THE IN CLIPBOARD WHEN DELETING THE SUBMISSION but from memory:
A JoJo-esque pre-fight peacocking scene. Imagine this being followed by the villain capturing the hero from behind, whispering some sort of mockery in the hero&amp;rsquo;s ear with his deep voice.</description></item><item><title>Blood Moon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-3-ee54/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-3-ee54/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: First week where I did stuff, hah! I hope I can start to follow the weeks more now that I exist here. You might recognize the character on the left, and if you do, then you&amp;rsquo;ll know who my friend is lol. These two boyos have a lot of story put into them, and I know a lot more about the Wild West than the average person might suspect.</description></item><item><title>Blood Moon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-3-c664/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-3-c664/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: PaintToolSAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes An archer wanders the wilderness under under the blood moon.
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 3 Title: Blood Moon Medium: PaintToolSAI Description: An archer wanders the wilderness under under the blood moon.</description></item><item><title>cirque of monkeys except it's me. i am the monkey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-3-6e93/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-3-6e93/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: photography/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes this is just me being a monkey in aerial silks. except many of me. in many silks. made with lots of ?? wtf how do i use this app? ?what is going on? ?? and photoshop crashing and p a n i k and stress but here we are i guess…
Social Media Instagram: charmandaar_ Twitch: charmandaar Twitter: charmandaar_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Harbinger</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-3-bdd0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-3-bdd0/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional, Copic markers &amp;amp; pens.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took a regular goldfinch, and jammed it full of steroids and heavy metal. &amp;ldquo;Beware the red moonlight,
Across the Black Forest night,
The deathwings in the tree,
Kill everything they see.&amp;rdquo;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>koi 🙂</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-3-e121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-3-e121/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Ps.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes fish 🙂
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: koi 🙂 Medium: Ps Description: fish 🙂</description></item><item><title>Out of Your Depth</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-3-a45d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-3-a45d/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes missed the week 2 prompt but wanted to work on the idea. Been thinking about running my own D&amp;amp;D session and was inspired by the grotesque and unknown of classic creatures and came up with a giant deep sea mimic. Wanted to invoke the idea of an angler fish lure but using red instead of the usual blue/white.</description></item><item><title>Tamago Tama</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-3-31f0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-3-31f0/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. View on SoundCloud. Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Audio (Ableton Live 10).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Red circle was Japan for me this week. It should be obvious where I went with that in the recording.
To me &amp;ldquo;garnet red&amp;rdquo; meant a very bold sound that&amp;rsquo;s not lowkey at all. Gems are formed under pressure, which to me means heavy distorted guitars, improvisation, garage drums, intentional but fun mistakes in instrument runs, and a very fast tempo.</description></item><item><title>Tesseract</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-3-f068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-3-f068/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Vector illustration.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Rather than a finalized illustration, I wanted to use this week as a way to push myself to complete a concept art for a story I&amp;rsquo;ve been slowly developing. A lot of the story revolved around shapes with very graphic elements, so I wanted to push that and also do a medium completely different from the previous weeks.</description></item><item><title>The Red Circle</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zja2damax-week-3-f85c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zja2damax-week-3-f85c/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Charcoal, Acrylic, and Watercolor on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: A photoshopped composition focused around the red circle. The circle is embraced by the hopeful and the hopeless. The circle is prominent in the light and the dark. The circle is constant in each instance. Layered over by each passing entity, immovable from its position.
Social Media N/A.</description></item><item><title>Week 3 Submission 👄</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-3-19e1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-3-19e1/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;hellip; week 3 submission 👄 tried to go for something a bit cleaner, simpler.
urmom3.0
Here&amp;rsquo;s my second piece:
Title: Red Circle
Medium: Discord Emote
Contrast. 🙏
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: Week 3 Submission 👄 Medium: Procreate Description: .</description></item><item><title>Appoh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-3-0e2f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-3-0e2f/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Round pony. Red like an apple. And an appaloosa. Tried to focus on character design and form exaggeration since that&amp;rsquo;s an area I want to grow better at.
IG/Tumblr lithiumreflections / Twitter jaimeskelton
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Cindy’s Imaginary Friend</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-3-d3de/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-3-d3de/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes no flash photography!!
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Cindy’s Imaginary Friend** Medium: Procreate Description: no flash photography!! Social Media: https://instagram.com/Dough.Yeast || https://twitch.tv/DoughYeast</description></item><item><title>Eye to the stars</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-3-6f68/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/zat-week-3-6f68/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Photographs/Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Photo of a section of Markarian&amp;rsquo;s Chain, a part of the Virgo cluster set as the pupil of a photo of an eye.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Medium: Photographs/Krita Title: Eye to the stars Description: Photo of a section of Markarian&amp;#39;s Chain, a part of the Virgo cluster set as the pupil of a photo of an eye.</description></item><item><title>Fire Fist Ace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-3-6fd7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-3-6fd7/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I read one piece, everyone read one piece.
Also ace is cool ace is really cool, tried to keep it simple and I really tried ;;;;
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Fire Fist Ace** Medium: Digital, SAI Description: I read one piece, everyone read one piece.</description></item><item><title>Shadow of the Red Sun</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-3-ffb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/rainydaze-week-3-ffb6/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Marker, brush pen, acrylic (red).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Assassin in training with like two knives cuz stab stab v cool
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Shadow of the Red Sun** Medium: Marker, brush pen, acrylic (red) Description: Assassin in training with like two knives cuz stab stab v cool Social Media: twitch.</description></item><item><title>The Forest King</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-3-7d52/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-3-7d52/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Rubber stamp block + ink, procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Bc this prompt focusses on contrast I wanted to explore black and white stamp printing! This is the 3rd stamp I&amp;rsquo;ve done and by far the biggest. I dont have red ink so I had to add that digitally. Kinda bummed that the scan was so unkind to it, but it was a nice change from the stuff I usually do</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ichika-week-3-911a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ichika-week-3-911a/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wolf idk what to say im new to this👁️👄👁️✨
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 3? Description: wolf idk what to say im new to this👁️👄👁️✨</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-3-911a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-3-911a/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Simple profile draw based on Akihiko Yoshida’s art. Was trying to do a new rendering style with the hair and am not quite happy with it yet, but it’s getting there!
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>神人</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/draco-week-3-2a39/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/draco-week-3-2a39/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In a decrepit dojo lies a gi. The gi is ragged, likely from years of training. However, as you draw closer it emanates a murderous aura and a voice speaks. &amp;ldquo;You shall know Pain&amp;rdquo;
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Medium: Krita Title: 神人 Description: In a decrepit dojo lies a gi.</description></item><item><title>compassionate eye</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-3-2ab1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-3-2ab1/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes tattoo style strippling &amp;amp; color. I’m pursuing tattooing, reason why I took this approach. Peonies symbolizes compassion. Would love to hear your thoughts on the design.
IG&amp;amp;Twitter| Moonlit_narcy. Twitch| MoonlitNarcy
Social Media Instagram: moonlit_narcy Twitter: moonlit_narcy Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: compassionate eye ** Medium: Procreate Description: tattoo style strippling &amp;amp; color.</description></item><item><title>A circle in abstractness</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-3-19ab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-3-19ab/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: 3D Digital.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was playing around with some atmospheric lighting in Blender and started playing with some circles and then this happened. Kind of weird but I like it the result.
Social Media Twitch: magus_hellwalker Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: A circle in abstractness Medium: 3D Digital Description: I was playing around with some atmospheric lighting in Blender and started playing with some circles and then this happened.</description></item><item><title>Brain Echo</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-3-e808/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-3-e808/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Bit out of my comfort zone but tried to do something artsy
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: Brain Echo Medium: Clipstudio Description: Bit out of my comfort zone but tried to do something artsy</description></item><item><title>Summon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-3-efde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-3-efde/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I heard something about &amp;lsquo;expand beyond the circle&amp;rsquo; and next thing you know we&amp;rsquo;re summoning entities from another reality 😛
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Summon ** Medium: Sketchbook Pro Description: I heard something about &amp;#39;expand beyond the circle&amp;#39; and next thing you know we&amp;#39;re summoning entities from another reality 😛 Social Media:</description></item><item><title>Temple discovery</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-2-9ff9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-2-9ff9/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: 3D Digital.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Using Blender 3D I created the Greek temple about 6 years ago and always had a vision about creating an underwater scene. Today I accomplished something that resembles an underwater Greek Temple or could it be the edge of Atlantis?</description></item><item><title>Circle and flow</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-3-e80d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-3-e80d/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: illustrator.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week:
Just dropping this idea down during stream. Currently practicing colour blocking and intersecting shapes.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: Title: Circle and flow Medium: illustrator Description: Just dropping this idea down during stream.</description></item><item><title>cold inside</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-3-9ea7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-3-9ea7/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint and phone photos.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission Template ``Week:
a view from my house at opposite ends of the year. Could have been a bigger contrast if we had snow, but we don&amp;rsquo;t atm.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Submission Template ``Week: Title: cold inside Medium: ibispaint and phone photos Description: a view from my house at opposite ends of the year.</description></item><item><title>It Spins</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-1-d71e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-1-d71e/</guid><description> The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: 3D Digital.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 3 hoops that are spinning on the X, Y and Z axis respectfully
Social Media Twitch: magus_hellwalker Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 (I know I&amp;#39;m late) Title: It Spins Medium: 3D Digital Description: 3 hoops that are spinning on the X, Y and Z axis respectfully</description></item><item><title>Untitled (society)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-3-e514/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-3-e514/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: autodesk sketchbook (mobile).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes felt destructive, might delete later
alternate universal beauty, the demand for universal balance and stability henceforth beauty. this molds the artificiality of man, but how long could one maintain such standards of being toys to the system?
bonus points for whoever could guess my inspiration :p
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Ah, Bright Light</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At the end of a long twisty cavern a diver finds a little rabbit shrimp thing! How cute and not at all dangerous.
I wanted to design a creature for this week and accidentally made a kaiju looking thing. Space wise I think I messed up translating how deep the ocean is but we can pretend I wanted it to come accross as claustrophobic.</description></item><item><title>Jormungandr</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-2-b1aa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-2-b1aa/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Jormangandr releasing toxic gas during Ragnarok. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d try a different style. Also wanted to do more fishies and ships and and and and but here it is nonetheless.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Jormungandr Medium: Procreate Description: Jormangandr releasing toxic gas during Ragnarok.</description></item><item><title>The Deep End</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Manga-inspired illustration where a warrior meets their maker in the Deep Realm &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt;
( Resubmitting the piece I had just done, because I was honestly disappointed in how much of the hatch work was covered and I didn’t want to do another red piece this upcoming week. Had to switch it up! )
Social Media Instagram: dough.</description></item><item><title>Ascend</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-2-17d4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-2-17d4/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: PaintToolSAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ascending towards the light and away from theL, whatever that may be
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week 2** Title: Ascend Medium: PaintToolSAI Description: Ascending towards the light and away from theL, whatever that may be **Social Media:** @Scimister on twitch</description></item><item><title>b̴͆͘e̸̲͌w̵͑͘ả̴̀r̶̾̎ȅ̷̌ ̶̃̎t̸͋̈́h̵̎̇e̴͑͂ ̸͑̇d̶̈́͝ě̵̤e̶͊͘p̵̒̀</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-2-99c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-2-99c5/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Audio (Ableton Live 10) and a Fender Stratocaster.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not entirely an aesthetic adherence to the theme but more of a compositional one. A morphing of flowing chords with a watery bongo drum (ocean) moves into a Lydian (scale) section. The main focus of the track was about contrast to adhere to &amp;ldquo;space&amp;rdquo;: the differences between the size of objects in the ocean.</description></item><item><title>Deep Discovery</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: 2 page comic, Ink on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be weird to find light in a deep ocean dive? Kinda scary if you ask me.
I love the idea of discovering something once lost, unsure if peaceful or dangerous waiting to be explored. Really just inspired by series like Made in Abyss and Jigokuraku!</description></item><item><title>felix, the jellyfish</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: traditional, embroidery on tulle.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes embroidered this cutie across two streams! freehanded off.. a questionable draft but first time embroidering on tulle! inspired after seeing some talented tulle art. lots of fun, and P A N I K and tears lol but happy with how it turned out. meet felix! named by my dearest chat (iykyk&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title>Hello there!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-a77b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-a77b/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, ok, I see your tiny human and large creature entries, but I raise you this,,, large human and tiny creature! But in all seriousness, whaaat, I&amp;rsquo;ve drawn something that isn&amp;rsquo;t just a character standing in a void? Shocking! I really challenged myself lol, hope I&amp;rsquo;ll continue to improve :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Little Dragons</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Gyotaku (traditional jp printmaking method using ink on fish, tho I used shrimp for this so I guess ebitaku lol) + dyed paper napkin.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had a dream a while back of seeing a group of shrimp, much larger than possible in real life, and having the feeling I was amidst something otherworldly. Rather than seeing them as food, I wanted to show the shrimp in their element and with regal-ness akin to dragons.</description></item><item><title>oarfish</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;rsquo;s been living in my mind rent free for years
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: oarfish Medium: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool Description: oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;#39;s been living in my mind rent free for years Social Media: @/rybaris on twitter and insta</description></item><item><title>Perspective is fun</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-2-4cb4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-2-4cb4/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m bad with s so I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna put this here and dip
Social Media Twitch: hadespsd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Title: Perspective is fun Medium: CSP Description: I&amp;#39;m bad with descriptions so I&amp;#39;m just gonna put this here and dip Social Media: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Galaxy Beneath</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-2-22bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-2-22bc/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Conceptual piece - a look at the depth of the ocean and how far light reaches down below, with a mix of imagining a galaxy of bioluminescent, living starlight. And maybe something larger&amp;hellip;
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>This is why I drink</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor (Arches A5 rough).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;In the year 20XX
Every living being on Earth
Is late for dinner&amp;rdquo;
Had to redo the whole thing after being unhappy with the first go at it - and I feel like the &amp;ldquo;SPACE&amp;rdquo; keyword wasn&amp;rsquo;t given any justice. I have some ideas on how it could have been dealt with better, but alas, we&amp;rsquo;ll just see that as part of the lesson and learning.</description></item><item><title>You have new text message! High five!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wanted to draw a mermaid. I really wanted to show this massive lady with something strange and unexpected. And those nokia phones are probably the only thing that could survive the crushing depths of the deep sea
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>King of the Sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week:2 Title: King of the Sea Medium: Clipstudio Description: Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.</description></item><item><title>bright sea</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-2-d908/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-2-d908/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m bad with s so I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna put this here and dip
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: bright sea Medium: photoshop Description: I&amp;#39;m bad with descriptions so I&amp;#39;m just gonna put this here and dip</description></item><item><title>Atlantis</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-2-a425/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-2-a425/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Since we were talking about Dragons in a previous stream I felt like drawing one&amp;hellip; like a sea dragon, those exist right? I rarely draw things like this so I’m a little shy to submit this one, but we’re all learning right?
paintsepsi
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Engulf</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: SketchBook.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread! Trying to up my digital art skills as well. Enjoy 😛
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Engulf Medium: SketchBook Description: You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread!</description></item><item><title>Maw of the Deep</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/capokey-week-2-7802/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/capokey-week-2-7802/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ``
The majority of the deep sea is still unexplored, who knows what kind of creatures could be hiding in the neverending darkness?
Social Media Instagram: caposketch Twitter: capokeyt Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: ``Week: 2 **Title: Maw of the Deep** Medium: Procreate Description: The majority of the deep sea is still unexplored, who knows what kind of creatures could be hiding in the neverending darkness?</description></item><item><title>simple angler pog</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission Template ``
just wanted to make something really simple
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Submission Template ``Week: 2 Title: simple angler pog Medium: ibispaint x Description: just wanted to make something really simple Social Media: ``</description></item><item><title>Luminated Darkness</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-1-ce9d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-1-ce9d/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So I finally finished my week 1 prompt. Full time momma here. But wanted to share even tho I’m late !
pretty much the darkness symbolizes my emotions how they tend to take over. The sun here is shining light and making me see the positive things in life.
Twitch:MoonlitNarcy
Social Media Instagram: moonlit_narcy Twitter: moonlit_narcy Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>the movement of water in two cups multiplicative of volumetric estimated measurement of water</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: pErForMaNcE aRT in video form / video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes it rained today, it rained yesterday, cyclical circle of movement of water, convulge in one directions, then splits into many. should have dinged my mug in hind sight.
not youtube, only using youtube as a platform to post this video
inspirations-&amp;gt; john cage &amp;lt;3
https://youtu.be/3imOd-rOjr8
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Four of Pumpkins</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-1-e8d5/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to do something elegant with pattern. However, when I streamed this like an hour ago, I was aggressively persuaded (bullied) into adding more pumpkins, and now it’s a tarot card of the suit of pumpkins. 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>sunny day, pouring rain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to try play with the rain patterns but rushed them a little. References are godsend. I was going for a minimal editorial look and limited pallette because those are outside of my comfort zone.
Social Media Instagram: jrchlp.png Twitter: jorchaelp Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Distance...</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/madboi-week-1-608f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/madboi-week-1-608f/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: : Traditional (fine liner, artist pitt pen, paper).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Distancing concept from the WiFi Symbol applied to current situation
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week : 1 Title : Distance... Medium : Traditional (fine liner, artist pitt pen, paper) Description : Distancing concept from the WiFi Symbol applied to current situation</description></item><item><title>egg galaxy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow! with some stars.
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: egg galaxy Medium: csp Description: a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow!</description></item><item><title>Noodle Dancer</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-1-0370/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛
Social Media Instagram: dough.yeast Twitch: doughyeast Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: **Noodle Dancer** Medium: Procreate Description: Chef dressed in black and yellow hand-pulling noodles in a chaotic, yet harmonious, fashion 💛 Social Media: https://instagram.</description></item><item><title>Plaid &amp; Lace sans Lace</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-1-44e7/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Ink, watercolour.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was originally going for &amp;ldquo;Plaid &amp;amp; Lace&amp;rdquo; as my keywords, but &amp;hellip; no way I&amp;rsquo;m putting down work on the &amp;ldquo;Lace&amp;rdquo; part as well. The yellow is &amp;ldquo;Gold Star&amp;rdquo; ink from Diamine, the rest is fineliner, uni-ball for white and some cobalt+ultramarine for shaded areas.
Social Media Instagram: arancil Twitch: arancil Twitter: arancil Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Rat 1 and Rat 2</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-1-64a9/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes gay rat wedding
I went a bit crazy on SAI which is a huge guilty pleasure. In the end it&amp;rsquo;s a bit cute and a good mood so I&amp;rsquo;m happy with what I made. Looking forward definitely going to use more references since i should, this is a bit surreal.
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>upon sunflowers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: digital, procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes going for simple w line work + pantone yellow. i also really love sunflowers. like a lot.
an accompanying haiku:
like the sunflowers / i look towards the sunlight /
to moving forwards / Social Media Instagram: charmandaar_ Twitch: charmandaar Twitter: charmandaar_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Week 1 submission 👁️ 👄 👁️</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-1-3d18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-1-3d18/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes done in ~6 hours.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: Week 1 submission 👁️ 👄 👁️ Medium: Procreate Description: done in ~6 hours. Socials: urmom</description></item><item><title>sparkly mandrake</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes here&amp;rsquo;s a sparkly mandrake gif that I made, file was too big so I had to resize it to fit
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: sparkly mandrake Medium: photoshop Description: here&amp;#39;s a sparkly mandrake gif that I made, file was too big so I had to resize it to fit</description></item><item><title>Honey, I'm Home!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-1-61ec/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw my oc in a dress, so I drew him in a dress! He likes wearing dresses from time to time. The sketchy plants in the bg are mostly to fill the space, but I thought they would look nice :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Just a Peep</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/boyf-week-1-b79d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/boyf-week-1-b79d/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca64.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought for a second, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do though I knew I wanted to use my OC. It sorta just flowed and this was the outcome. I kinda like it though sorta don&amp;rsquo;t lol.
Social Media Instagram: _daniluvsyou Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>New Year's Compass</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-1-8366/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-1-8366/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes An eight point radial design in the style of a compass rose. Lines are all in the Pantone Yellow, while the background is two shades of blue: classic blue (2020&amp;rsquo;s Pantone color of the year) inside the design and a darker contrasted blue outside of it.
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Origin Point</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-1-fa7e/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Processing (program) + Java.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Circle created with Java code that randomizes the spiral variance and the stroke; I wanted to challenge myself to learn a new programming language this year since I enjoy using them for both work and side projects. I&amp;rsquo;d love to be able to do a different medium for each week if I&amp;rsquo;m able.</description></item><item><title>Yellow Ice Bar</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-1-7b09/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-1-7b09/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Switch Harv&amp;rsquo;s Island.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I cannot art so here are yellow ACNH vibes, maybe (big maybe) I&amp;rsquo;ll actually draw for future weeks
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: Yellow Ice Bar Medium: Switch Harv&amp;#39;s Island Description: I cannot art so here are yellow ACNH vibes, maybe (big maybe) I&amp;#39;ll actually draw for future weeks</description></item><item><title>flush</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/malorbaker-week-1-86f3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/malorbaker-week-1-86f3/</guid><description> Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: ms paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sideways yellow waterfall there is harmony in all the whoosh&amp;rsquo;s and they are also lines i win
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: flush Medium: ms paint Description: sideways yellow waterfall there is harmony in all the whoosh&amp;#39;s and they are also lines i win</description></item><item><title>Objects</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ramen-week-1-c830/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/ramen-week-1-c830/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i made this at 2 am. there is something special about this drawing. i really like all of these objects. i love ducks, bananas, stars, the sun, sunflowers, lemon, and cheese. i dont really like paprika tbh, but its yellow anyways :3
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Profile</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-1-cce9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-1-cce9/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate Digital Painting.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Basically a portrait of a model but using the Pantone colour of the year as the background. I thought the brightness of the yellow really stood out and so I ended up really appreciating the way it turned out!
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Bowl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: MS Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes simple geometry shape of a bowl highlighted using pre-programmed algorithm of MS Paint, the yellow used to demonstrate the 3 dimensionality of bowl&amp;hellip; aaaa theres a cat in it &amp;hellip;. oh welp if it fits, it sits ¯_(ツ)_/¯
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>