<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rainydaze on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/artists/rainydaze/</link><description>Recent content in rainydaze on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://inklingtest.com/artists/rainydaze/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>d'Eggfsg</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-16-21e5/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to draw big egg. Smol soldier. In combination, they make a pretty striking pair. I&amp;rsquo;ve been having really out of the world dreams lately, and some of them feel like Neil Gaiman stories, but them sometimes they feel like this piece. It&amp;rsquo;s both familiar and not, something that we&amp;rsquo;ve all been feeling after being stuck inside for so long.</description></item><item><title>Anarchy Loves Fire</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-14-c8c8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate (and DaVinci Resolve).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a piece of an animatic I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on about an anarchist pig and his contemporaries and their relationship with violence. (edit: it&amp;rsquo;s a little heavy so pls don&amp;rsquo;t be wearing headphones if you&amp;rsquo;re not used to heavy music)
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>glitch clouds inc</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-11-c4f8/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Medium: Procreate Title: glitch clouds inc Description: sky with slightly glitched-out clouds plus reflection in water, i like pretty stuff ❤️ gonna use it in my panels ehehe</description></item><item><title>inanimate objects that give me comfort</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-6-0452/</guid><description> Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I don&amp;rsquo;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;rsquo;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 6 Title: inanimate objects that give me comfort Medium: Procreate, with the Narinder Pencil Description: I don&amp;#39;t have many people to rely on for emotional support, so it&amp;#39;s really nice to have some old comforting things with me when feeling down</description></item><item><title>Shadow of the Red Sun</title><link>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-3-ffb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://inklingtest.com/blog/rainydaze-week-3-ffb6/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Marker, brush pen, acrylic (red).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Assassin in training with like two knives cuz stab stab v cool
Social Media Twitch: rainydazedoeslife Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Shadow of the Red Sun** Medium: Marker, brush pen, acrylic (red) Description: Assassin in training with like two knives cuz stab stab v cool Social Media: twitch.</description></item></channel></rss>