<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 02: Deep Ocean on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-02-deep-ocean/</link><description>Recent content in Week 02: Deep Ocean on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-02-deep-ocean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Under the Sea</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-2-41fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/heidelburger-week-2-41fd/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Game, Animal Crossing.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (I didn’t actually post at the time so here we are&amp;hellip;)
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Under the Sea Medium: Game, Animal Crossing Description: (I didn’t actually post at the time so here we are.</description></item><item><title>Temple discovery</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-2-9ff9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/magus_hellwalker-week-2-9ff9/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: 3D Digital.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Using Blender 3D I created the Greek temple about 6 years ago and always had a vision about creating an underwater scene. Today I accomplished something that resembles an underwater Greek Temple or could it be the edge of Atlantis?</description></item><item><title>Ah, Bright Light</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At the end of a long twisty cavern a diver finds a little rabbit shrimp thing! How cute and not at all dangerous.
I wanted to design a creature for this week and accidentally made a kaiju looking thing. Space wise I think I messed up translating how deep the ocean is but we can pretend I wanted it to come accross as claustrophobic.</description></item><item><title>Jormungandr</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-2-b1aa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-2-b1aa/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Jormangandr releasing toxic gas during Ragnarok. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d try a different style. Also wanted to do more fishies and ships and and and and but here it is nonetheless.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Jormungandr Medium: Procreate Description: Jormangandr releasing toxic gas during Ragnarok.</description></item><item><title>The Deep End</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-2-20a3/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Manga-inspired illustration where a warrior meets their maker in the Deep Realm &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt;
( Resubmitting the piece I had just done, because I was honestly disappointed in how much of the hatch work was covered and I didn’t want to do another red piece this upcoming week. Had to switch it up! )
Social Media Instagram: dough.</description></item><item><title>Ascend</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-2-17d4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-2-17d4/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: PaintToolSAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ascending towards the light and away from theL, whatever that may be
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week 2** Title: Ascend Medium: PaintToolSAI Description: Ascending towards the light and away from theL, whatever that may be **Social Media:** @Scimister on twitch</description></item><item><title>b̴͆͘e̸̲͌w̵͑͘ả̴̀r̶̾̎ȅ̷̌ ̶̃̎t̸͋̈́h̵̎̇e̴͑͂ ̸͑̇d̶̈́͝ě̵̤e̶͊͘p̵̒̀</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-2-99c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-2-99c5/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Audio (Ableton Live 10) and a Fender Stratocaster.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not entirely an aesthetic adherence to the theme but more of a compositional one. A morphing of flowing chords with a watery bongo drum (ocean) moves into a Lydian (scale) section. The main focus of the track was about contrast to adhere to &amp;ldquo;space&amp;rdquo;: the differences between the size of objects in the ocean.</description></item><item><title>Deep Discovery</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-2-5c23/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: 2 page comic, Ink on Paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be weird to find light in a deep ocean dive? Kinda scary if you ask me.
I love the idea of discovering something once lost, unsure if peaceful or dangerous waiting to be explored. Really just inspired by series like Made in Abyss and Jigokuraku!</description></item><item><title>felix, the jellyfish</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: traditional, embroidery on tulle.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes embroidered this cutie across two streams! freehanded off.. a questionable draft but first time embroidering on tulle! inspired after seeing some talented tulle art. lots of fun, and P A N I K and tears lol but happy with how it turned out. meet felix! named by my dearest chat (iykyk&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title>Hello there!</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-a77b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-2-a77b/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Ok, ok, I see your tiny human and large creature entries, but I raise you this,,, large human and tiny creature! But in all seriousness, whaaat, I&amp;rsquo;ve drawn something that isn&amp;rsquo;t just a character standing in a void? Shocking! I really challenged myself lol, hope I&amp;rsquo;ll continue to improve :)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Little Dragons</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-2-4b63/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Gyotaku (traditional jp printmaking method using ink on fish, tho I used shrimp for this so I guess ebitaku lol) + dyed paper napkin.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had a dream a while back of seeing a group of shrimp, much larger than possible in real life, and having the feeling I was amidst something otherworldly. Rather than seeing them as food, I wanted to show the shrimp in their element and with regal-ness akin to dragons.</description></item><item><title>oarfish</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;rsquo;s been living in my mind rent free for years
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: oarfish Medium: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool Description: oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;#39;s been living in my mind rent free for years Social Media: @/rybaris on twitter and insta</description></item><item><title>Perspective is fun</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-2-4cb4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hadespsd-week-2-4cb4/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m bad with s so I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna put this here and dip
Social Media Twitch: hadespsd Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Title: Perspective is fun Medium: CSP Description: I&amp;#39;m bad with descriptions so I&amp;#39;m just gonna put this here and dip Social Media: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Galaxy Beneath</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-2-22bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-2-22bc/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Conceptual piece - a look at the depth of the ocean and how far light reaches down below, with a mix of imagining a galaxy of bioluminescent, living starlight. And maybe something larger&amp;hellip;
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>This is why I drink</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-2-a4b4/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Watercolor (Arches A5 rough).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;In the year 20XX
Every living being on Earth
Is late for dinner&amp;rdquo;
Had to redo the whole thing after being unhappy with the first go at it - and I feel like the &amp;ldquo;SPACE&amp;rdquo; keyword wasn&amp;rsquo;t given any justice. I have some ideas on how it could have been dealt with better, but alas, we&amp;rsquo;ll just see that as part of the lesson and learning.</description></item><item><title>You have new text message! High five!</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-2-2932/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Wanted to draw a mermaid. I really wanted to show this massive lady with something strange and unexpected. And those nokia phones are probably the only thing that could survive the crushing depths of the deep sea
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>King of the Sea</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-2-1981/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week:2 Title: King of the Sea Medium: Clipstudio Description: Started Digital art few month ago, First art post ever so feel free to give all kinds of advice to improve.</description></item><item><title>bright sea</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-2-d908/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-2-d908/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m bad with s so I&amp;rsquo;m just gonna put this here and dip
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: bright sea Medium: photoshop Description: I&amp;#39;m bad with descriptions so I&amp;#39;m just gonna put this here and dip</description></item><item><title>Atlantis</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-2-a425/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-2-a425/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Since we were talking about Dragons in a previous stream I felt like drawing one&amp;hellip; like a sea dragon, those exist right? I rarely draw things like this so I’m a little shy to submit this one, but we’re all learning right?
paintsepsi
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Engulf</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: SketchBook.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread! Trying to up my digital art skills as well. Enjoy 😛
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Engulf Medium: SketchBook Description: You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread!</description></item><item><title>Maw of the Deep</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/capokey-week-2-7802/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/capokey-week-2-7802/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ``
The majority of the deep sea is still unexplored, who knows what kind of creatures could be hiding in the neverending darkness?
Social Media Instagram: caposketch Twitter: capokeyt Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: ``Week: 2 **Title: Maw of the Deep** Medium: Procreate Description: The majority of the deep sea is still unexplored, who knows what kind of creatures could be hiding in the neverending darkness?</description></item><item><title>simple angler pog</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-2-d6f4/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: ibispaint x.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission Template ``
just wanted to make something really simple
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Submission Template ``Week: 2 Title: simple angler pog Medium: ibispaint x Description: just wanted to make something really simple Social Media: ``</description></item><item><title>the movement of water in two cups multiplicative of volumetric estimated measurement of water</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: pErForMaNcE aRT in video form / video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes it rained today, it rained yesterday, cyclical circle of movement of water, convulge in one directions, then splits into many. should have dinged my mug in hind sight.
not youtube, only using youtube as a platform to post this video
inspirations-&amp;gt; john cage &amp;lt;3
YouTube External Link Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>