<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>winsome on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/winsome/</link><description>Recent content in winsome on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/winsome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mandrake Reflecting</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @arren&amp;rsquo;s Week 1 submission &amp;ldquo;Sparkly Mandrake&amp;rdquo; (https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arren-week-1-9c0e/) This was one of the first pieces I saw when watching design refresh and it really captured my attention. I utilised my own Mandrake model from Week 7 (https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/). I tried to capture a video of it to replicate the glitter of the original gif, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t look very good.</description></item><item><title>Broccaiju</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-16-aef1/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Godzilla v Kong cut content. Actually though, heavily inspired by an old PS2 game called War of the Monsters that is a Kaiju-filled beat-em-up.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 16 Title: Broccaiju Medium: Photo + CLIP STUDIO PAINT Description: Godzilla v Kong cut content.</description></item><item><title>Hi! I like shorts! They're comfy and easy to wear!</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-9-c5dc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-9-c5dc/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Photography (Photo set).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Celebrating the 25th Anniversary of Pokemon and myself, with a Pokemon that I like a lot. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;m still a youngster trainer class.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>Just a couple of Daft Punks</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-8-1c0e/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Digital collage (photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt image immediately made me think of a vinyl record so I was thinking of doing something with Daft Punk as soon as I read the prompt. I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty big fan of theirs and was disappointed to hear that they were splitting up. But boy do they have a metal sheen.</description></item><item><title>Three Celebrations (Change)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-7-16e6/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Photography, Clay Figure &amp;amp; Cake.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 3 white chocolate caramel souffle cakes to celebrate three different events.
Growth: 1st cake for Herschel&amp;rsquo;s birthday, sadly we missed his birthday party due to lockdown.
Goodbyes: 2nd cake for my roommate who decided his job wasn&amp;rsquo;t worth his sanity anymore and quit.
New Beginnings: 3rd cake for my friend Pete who&amp;rsquo;s moving to a new place!</description></item><item><title>Sweet Nothings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-6-92a1/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Modelling Clay (Sculpey).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A lot of people give chocolates for Valentines and other romantic holidays. I&amp;rsquo;m not a huge fan of chocolate but I really like the little gourmet ones. I think these ones will last a little longer than most.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Queen of the Skies</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-5-4c35/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The prompt immediately made me think of the Rathian from Monster Hunter, the female counterpart to the series' flagship monster Rathalos. I tried to follow the prompt resource on recreating the jade effect using a small jade dragon as a reference.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Dead Squats</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: Dead Squats Medium: Digital (Photopea) Description: I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.</description></item><item><title>Out of Your Depth</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-3-a45d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-3-a45d/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes missed the week 2 prompt but wanted to work on the idea. Been thinking about running my own D&amp;amp;D session and was inspired by the grotesque and unknown of classic creatures and came up with a giant deep sea mimic. Wanted to invoke the idea of an angler fish lure but using red instead of the usual blue/white.</description></item></channel></rss>