<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jumpingbeans on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/jumpingbeans/</link><description>Recent content in jumpingbeans on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/jumpingbeans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ThankEgg</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ive ran out of ideas and time
; YouTube External Link ;
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: ThankEgg Medium: video Description: ive ran out of ideas and time Social Media: https://www.</description></item><item><title>what is bigger, a giant bidoof or an individual's life?</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-16-2be7/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes subject matters of artists like Edward Hopper tends to place equal weight for the furniture and the human matter, for example, the parallelism of the shapes of his human subject and non-human subjects, the compositions as well. Edward Hopper has invoked thought within his audience, how important is life? Are our lives just as unimportant than the furniture we buy?</description></item><item><title>illiteracy</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-15-f94f/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: chinese calligraphy.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The art philosophy known as &amp;ldquo;Nanyang Art Style&amp;rdquo; is a fusion of western and eastern art style. Often, pioneers of this art styles employed western mediums and materials, paired with subject matters of eastern origins / things you commonly see in asia. Some of the pioneering artists are Georgette Chen, Liu Kang etc.</description></item><item><title>Fire Sale</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-14-e259/</guid><description> Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Krita w/ mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Think about the value
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 14 Title: Fire Sale Medium: Krita w/ mouse Description: Think about the value Social Media: https://www.twitch.com/jumpingbeansz</description></item><item><title>Things you use to see yourself with</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-13-0c7e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-13-0c7e/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: MS paint /some online video compiler.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes My sister took my computer, so i used a potato to do this work.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item><item><title>wrod</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-12-215e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-12-215e/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: gif.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes im clown, im illiterate, face go brrrrrrr (had to resubmit, the previous submission had weird colouring issues )
edit: redid the gif, its still giving the weird coloured background thingy, even though on my comp its not like that, idk whats going on, so i guess its epilepsy warning.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Are we at the weekends yet?</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-11-0c75/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw this artist&amp;rsquo;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired. also, i like weekends.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Are we at the weekends yet? Medium: Krita Description: Saw this artist&amp;#39;s (ig: mofu_sand) work, saw cute cat, inspired.</description></item><item><title>Apple 16</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-10-0414/</guid><description> Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Apple.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This apple has weird fashion.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Title: Apple 16 Medium: Apple Description: This apple has weird fashion. Social Media: https://www.instagram.com/jumpingbeansz/; https://www.twitch.tv/jumpingbeansz ;</description></item><item><title>This is the literal worst shit i have created, i think my parent think im weird.</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-9-ef37/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw a dude making cool advertisement with a TV as background and thought &amp;quot; hmmmm seems easy&amp;quot; then i proceed to do stupid things. my parents saw me do stupid things, and editing is hell. overall i rate the experience 4/10, maybe i would increase the score if I were more familiar with video editing</description></item><item><title>Trashbin</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-8-af29/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Autodesk sketch.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Saw the prompt, saw time-limit, thought to self &amp;ldquo;what do i draw well?&amp;rdquo;. Answer: Trash. This is a warning, dont read too much into my thinking process (colours were abstracted from the source image)
, / (cuz symbolisms)
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Ghost City (ft bad cropping)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-7-f970/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Krita.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The huge creature was a character that I had written about, inspired by League of Legend&amp;rsquo;s RekSai and Pokemon&amp;rsquo;s Garchomp. styles influenced by chinese/japanese calligraphy cuz was triggered that i had to do a calligraphy work in non-chinese/japanese materials.
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>The introspection of self, the different facades of life and embrace of the multifaceted appearences</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-6-21a4/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Video of beansz wearing clothing (aka i ran out of mediums, time to recycle).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes In life we wear many masks (or shirts cuz i dont know the art of 变脸, aka chinese face mask changing), they are the many aspects of self, whether or not we like it or not. The introspection of the multiple sides is what makes us individuals and whole.</description></item><item><title>Here we go again</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-5-328d/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Installation.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes stickman doesn&amp;rsquo;t go brrrrrr. stickman goes mining. but seriously though, royal green reminded me of the military (for some reason) and jade was the other prompt. so i had my uniform become be a jade mine. :P
ps i failed kindergarten, i cant use a pair of scissors
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Stress</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</guid><description>View on External Website. Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Game.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought I could finish this within 2 days (including learning + execution), ended up having to scrap a lot of the ideas due to my lack of knowledge and sleep deprivation. (definitely not my proudest project, bad coding ethics, cutting corners)
itch.io External Link (&amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; aka shitpost download page)
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Untitled (society)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-3-e514/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-3-e514/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: autodesk sketchbook (mobile).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes felt destructive, might delete later
alternate universal beauty, the demand for universal balance and stability henceforth beauty. this molds the artificiality of man, but how long could one maintain such standards of being toys to the system?
bonus points for whoever could guess my inspiration :p
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>the movement of water in two cups multiplicative of volumetric estimated measurement of water</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-2-73ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: pErForMaNcE aRT in video form / video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes it rained today, it rained yesterday, cyclical circle of movement of water, convulge in one directions, then splits into many. should have dinged my mug in hind sight.
not youtube, only using youtube as a platform to post this video
inspirations-&amp;gt; john cage &amp;lt;3
YouTube External Link Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Bowl</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-1-d1b6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: MS Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes simple geometry shape of a bowl highlighted using pre-programmed algorithm of MS Paint, the yellow used to demonstrate the 3 dimensionality of bowl&amp;hellip; aaaa theres a cat in it &amp;hellip;. oh welp if it fits, it sits ¯_(ツ)_/¯
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>