<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fonz on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/fonz/</link><description>Recent content in fonz on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/fonz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>desert strands</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-7-532a/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes 80 minute speed draw this time happy with the result though ! inspired by a lot of the stippling i&amp;rsquo;ve seen entered by the amazing artists in this week&amp;rsquo;s submissions ! attempted to tie the sand dunes into the hair? no real reason why other than i thought it might be fun to try ;; (to whom it may concern at turnitin, originally submitted at 11:57pm)</description></item><item><title>green eyed girl</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes another last minute entry really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !
Social Media Twitch: fonzaku Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: green eyed girl Medium: csp Description: another last minute entry really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !</description></item><item><title>mask</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i really just wanted to create something ambiguous with this piece, no clear expression of good or evil, menacing or innocent completely up to interpretation. &amp;ldquo;movement&amp;rdquo; really got me thinking about the creeping of shadows so i tried to subject that in the piece! i guess it&amp;rsquo;s less of a silhouette but still a retreat into complete darkness/murkiness very last minute but happy with the outcome!</description></item></channel></rss>