<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Charmandaar on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/charmandaar/</link><description>Recent content in Charmandaar on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/charmandaar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>unspoken words of affirmation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-12-9763/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-12-9763/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes not sure if this counts as typography hahaha oOPs but uhh i really like writing even tho my handwriting is illegible at times so i honestly just wrote what came to mind which is that hm i guess i’m havin a tough time lately and i know a lot of my community is as well, so i kind of wrote this as a reminder for them (and myself, and you!</description></item><item><title>POV you find another VHS tape, and your sleep deprived self slots it in the player…</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-9-79a8/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes !!!epilepsy warning!!!
rhythm and flow? say no more.. didn’t have much time this week so this was a very quickly put-together and rushed but i found this super funky cmyk filter on insta… this was such a headache to edit lol, but hope you enjoy!! you asked for statement so… i look like a giant but i promise you it’s 60% camera angle 40% my 8” pole heels xd</description></item><item><title>Paper Aeroplanes demo.mp3, collab with @papapastry</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-6-7344/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud.
The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A demo track of our collab song &amp;lsquo;Paper Aeroplanes&amp;rsquo;, capturing an instance between two lovers and what their simple but gentle love brings.
paper aeroplanes DEMO track: https://soundcloud.com/papapastry/fuck-so-late-god-fucking-damnit the lyrics were based off poetry i wrote: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1v7MNRHeg6fDwUsURPJAf1XSptglTolwA1KtohM_4Rbk/edit?usp=sharing
charmandaar on twitch () papapastry on yt (https://www.</description></item><item><title>POV you dust off an old VHS tape and slot it in the player…</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes took a video while i was lightly messing around on the pole and here we are..! thought the glitchy parts would be a fun way to transition between clips. i love playing with silhouettes when i dance and thought this may be a cool idea to encompasses murky shadows and rhythm/movement too.</description></item><item><title>cirque of monkeys except it's me. i am the monkey</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-3-6e93/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-3-6e93/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: photography/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes this is just me being a monkey in aerial silks. except many of me. in many silks. made with lots of ?? wtf how do i use this app? ?what is going on? ?? &amp;lt;:charma22THONK:780825723681898517&amp;gt; &amp;lt;:charma22THONK:780825723681898517&amp;gt; and photoshop crashing and p a n i k and stress but here we are i guess…
Social Media Instagram: charmandaar_ Twitch: charmandaar Twitter: charmandaar_ Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>felix, the jellyfish</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-2-210a/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: traditional, embroidery on tulle.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes embroidered this cutie across two streams! freehanded off.. a questionable draft but first time embroidering on tulle! inspired after seeing some talented tulle art. lots of fun, and P A N I K and tears lol but happy with how it turned out. meet felix! named by my dearest chat (iykyk&amp;hellip;)</description></item><item><title>upon sunflowers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-1-4283/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: digital, procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes going for simple w line work + pantone yellow. i also really love sunflowers. like a lot.
an accompanying haiku: like the sunflowers / i look towards the sunlight /
to moving forwards / Social Media Instagram: charmandaar_ Twitch: charmandaar Twitter: charmandaar_ Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item></channel></rss>