<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chari on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/chari/</link><description>Recent content in chari on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/chari/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>iPod Nano</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-9-318e/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I&amp;rsquo;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;rsquo;d enjoy from the prompt. (Late as usual LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 9 Title: iPod Nano Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: I&amp;#39;m trying to move away from using super bright palettes so I tried to think of ways I could make something I&amp;#39;d enjoy from the prompt.</description></item><item><title>Academy, Disrepair</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-7-b2ee/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;rsquo;t normally draw backgrounds. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a colour scheme I liked that worked with the monochrome sketch so I kept it minimal.
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 7 Title: Academy, Disrepair Medium: Digital, Clip Studio Paint Description: Sort of a composition exercise since I don&amp;#39;t normally draw backgrounds.</description></item><item><title>Ghosties</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/chari-week-6-3bfe/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Was meant to be a Week 5 submission but it fits Week 6 for me too. I love my OCs, and it&amp;rsquo;s been great to have them as a creative &amp;amp; emotional outlet! (Also love being able to finish art even if it&amp;rsquo;s not on time LOL)
Social Media Twitter: hogfriendz Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item></channel></rss>