<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 04: Murky Silhouettes on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-04-murky-silhouettes/</link><description>Recent content in Week 04: Murky Silhouettes on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-04-murky-silhouettes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>green eyed girl</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-ad79/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes another last minute entry &amp;lt;:wow:649902323191119882&amp;gt; really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !
Social Media Twitch: fonzaku Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: green eyed girl Medium: csp Description: another last minute entry &amp;lt;:wow:649902323191119882&amp;gt; really just wanted to explore lighting after seeing a reference and thought jade lighting might be a cool variation !</description></item><item><title>Just Smile &amp; Smell the Flowers</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-4-3b95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/moonlit-narcy-week-4-3b95/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes sometimes all it takes is the wonderful smell of flowers to put a smile on your face.
Social Media Instagram: moonlit_narcy Twitter: moonlit_narcy Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: Just Smile &amp;amp; Smell the Flowers Medium: Procreate Description: sometimes all it takes is the wonderful smell of flowers to put a smile on your face.</description></item><item><title>Coconut Crab</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-36dc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/space-warfare-development-week-4-36dc/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Traditional, Copic markers.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: &amp;#34;Coconut Crab&amp;#34; Medium: Traditional, Copic markers Description: Gray background, black silhouette of palm tree and grass.</description></item><item><title>Green mOon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-4-54e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/askpatt-week-4-54e5/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: PS.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Silhouette using negative space and texture to bring forward the figure and clothing. For movement, I went more subtle with hair flow that cuts through the face rather than drawn in. Note: save your work&amp;hellip;i lost the first draft and finished this 1 hr before deadline
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Assimilation</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-4-bb08/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i read a cool tumble post about a botanist burying a lamb bone under a tree and when they came back a few months later the tree had completely absorbed it. Left it to the last minute so it’s not exactly what I had in mind but better done than not so 🤷🏻‍♀️
Social Media Twitch: pumpkanart Twitter: pumpkanart Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Bloody Fields</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-4-759c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Felt pen on paper.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I actually struggled with the theme, but this came suddenly one day ago. Killing of farmers is still an issue in the Philippines as they struggle for genuine and lasting land reform. January 22 was also the anniversary of the Mendiola Massacre, where 13 farmers were killed when police dispersed a large farmer&amp;rsquo;s protest.</description></item><item><title>Blue</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/linalifox-week-4-9594/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/linalifox-week-4-9594/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I began this piece with a cyan background and started painting in a dark blue. I found it a challenge as I did not have the usual variety of colours to work with, especially with no red tone at all used in the skin. However I eventually learnt to blend the two blues and make them work and thoroughly enjoyed the process.</description></item><item><title>Bog</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/doughyeast-week-4-cdf9/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate, Pixaloop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At Camp Laywick, Raya’s peers are unable to see the silhouette of her distress against the thick of the fog&amp;hellip;
yet she is unable to see the silhouette beneath the water&amp;hellip;
[ I went for a “cover of a horror novel for teen readers” approach and did some video-editing to further portray rhythm and movement &amp;lt;a:JamCat:768213145008210012&amp;gt; ]</description></item><item><title>Current</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-4-222a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jzann-week-4-222a/</guid><description> Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes just an otter floating by, moving with the water
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 Title: Current Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: just an otter floating by, moving with the water</description></item><item><title>Dead Squats</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-4-fa6e/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Photopea).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.
Social Media Twitch: winsomeorc Twitter: winsomeorc Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: Dead Squats Medium: Digital (Photopea) Description: I wanted to focus on figure drawing so used the classic slav squat as a ref, the character is the protagonist from the game Dead Cells.</description></item><item><title>Family Portrait</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-4-b8b8/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I had the idea to do a cute wild west family portrait featuring the gays(tm) and their daughter, so I went with it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to spend as much time on this as I wanted to, but I&amp;rsquo;m still happy with it (also here&amp;rsquo;s a non-monochrome version lol)
Social Media Tumblr: bellbones1207 Twitter: bbart1207 Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Giraffe</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-4-427d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/scimister-week-4-427d/</guid><description> Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: PaintToolSAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A simplified digital wood carving of a giraffe 🐘
Social Media Twitch: scimister Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 **Title: Giraffe** Medium: PaintToolSAI Description: A simplified digital wood carving of a giraffe 🐘 Socials: @Scimister on twitch 🦒</description></item><item><title>mask</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/fonz-week-4-f2ce/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i really just wanted to create something ambiguous with this piece, no clear expression of good or evil, menacing or innocent completely up to interpretation. &amp;ldquo;movement&amp;rdquo; really got me thinking about the creeping of shadows so i tried to subject that in the piece! i guess it&amp;rsquo;s less of a silhouette but still a retreat into complete darkness/murkiness &amp;lt;:wow:649902323191119882&amp;gt; very last minute but happy with the outcome!</description></item><item><title>Morning Breeze</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-4-2681/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Animation, CSP.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog. Low key a vibe, animation is hell, and I hope everyone likes it!
Social Media Instagram: fiveclawd Twitch: cindrytuna Twitter: cindrytuna Twitter: fiveclawd Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Morning Breeze** Medium: Animation, CSP Description: Made a character based off the feeling of morning grogginess and brain fog.</description></item><item><title>MURKE SHADOES</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-4-64a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-4-64a1/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud.
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Murky silhouettes&amp;rdquo; sounds metal and I got my wisdom teeth out so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really do what I usually do.
&amp;ldquo;Tone&amp;rdquo; reminds me of a sick and phat guitar toan that has &amp;ldquo;value.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Rhythm&amp;rdquo; obviously means blastbeats and &amp;ldquo;movement&amp;rdquo; means the movement of the head up and down as the music flows through your soul and out your butt.</description></item><item><title>POV you dust off an old VHS tape and slot it in the player…</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/charmandaar-week-4-36cd/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: video/photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes took a video while i was lightly messing around on the pole and here we are..! thought the glitchy parts would be a fun way to transition between clips. i love playing with silhouettes when i dance and thought this may be a cool idea to encompasses murky shadows and rhythm/movement too.</description></item><item><title>Snap Shot 1</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/av-week-4-3f90/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/av-week-4-3f90/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes OKAY so this is a snapshot of life. There is a little darkness and a little light in everything you do. #yinandyangvibes
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: Week 4 Title: Snap Shot 1 Medium: Clip Studio Paint Description: OKAY so this is a snapshot of life.</description></item><item><title>You Ain't No Bounty Hunter</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Whew, this one was close! Sucks that I had to kinda rush at the end because this was submitted on a school night, but I think it still came out really well! I hope his expression scares you because it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to lol. The only story I&amp;rsquo;ll give is something/someone hurt his boyfriend pretty badly and he&amp;rsquo;s not happy about it.</description></item><item><title>1:21 AM</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-4-ac13/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Acrylic paint (Magenta/yellow mix for orange, winsor violet with a bit of magenta for the hand).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Tried to capture desperation, intensity and passion. Didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to make the indentations left by the fingers the way I wanted - the idea of the situation is someone digging her nails into the back of her lover.</description></item><item><title>costume change</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw &amp;lsquo;state of change&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;movement&amp;rsquo; and that was it for me! i forgot it was monochromatic entirely oops
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: costume change Medium: csp!</description></item><item><title>Dancing Cloud</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-4-c9e7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-4-c9e7/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (Clip Studio Paint).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A one minute gesture sketch turned into a monochrome piece where negative space was used to explore values. Internally mad at the anatomy being off but I promised myself to only work from the gesture and not to spend an hour fussing over making the form precise. It was fun erasing to add value though.</description></item><item><title>Façade</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-4-b82c/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ink + paper collage.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Delving a bit personal with this piece. Often there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between the person I present to others - usually my business persona I use for my work that seems to have everything orderly and &amp;lsquo;put together&amp;rsquo;, while my internal self always feels like it&amp;rsquo;s in a state of at least minor chaos and has to navigate the unknown without guidance.</description></item><item><title>Practice</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/kami-week-4-8c00/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Pencil , sketch pens.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is a martial arts style from India called Kalari, it&amp;rsquo;s really aggressive and involves lots of movement. I tried gesture drawing for the first time, so i guess not bad?
Social Media Twitch: kamiofthesouth Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Socials: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Rhythm and Tones Outine</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-4-0b03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/meplaysgamez-week-4-0b03/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: free photo editor thing idk.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw rhythm and tones in the outines of the prompt.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week 4 Title: Rhythm and Tones Outine Medium: free photo editor thing idk Description: i saw rhythm and tones in the outines of the prompt.</description></item><item><title>The Search</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Search
Murky, silhouette&amp;hellip; well, I must oblige! (It&amp;rsquo;s like you want me to draw spoopy shit) 😛 Decided to contrast this with my last two pieces by using mainly lighter values. And since we&amp;rsquo;re looking at movement, thought I&amp;rsquo;d try and pump in some more overt narrative stuff too. Enjoy!
Social Media N/A.</description></item><item><title>cat&lt;a:B8vibe:776693937498095637> (cant think of a title xd)</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrtnong-week-4-4f54/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes It&amp;rsquo;s my first time creating something graphic art-y I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt;
(might stream sometime in 2021 &amp;lt;a:ultra_fast_parrot:800558785907261441&amp;gt; )
Social Media Instagram: mrtnong Twitch: mrtnong Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: cat&amp;lt;a:B8_vibe:776693937498095637&amp;gt; (cant think of a title xd) Medium: Procreate Description: It&amp;#39;s my first time creating something *graphic art-y* I usually paint my stuff in a more painterly way &amp;lt;a:2534_ablobblastoff:795931611375337472&amp;gt; Socials: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Sleepless Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-4-e6d0/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: ClipStudio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn’t use one color but I tried to stick with cold colors? Worked on value and tones? Is floating considered rhythm and movement? (Honestly idk, still new to all these art vocabulary xD). i hope this respect the rules of the challenge &amp;lt;:PepeHands:779990751429918720&amp;gt; Implemented some contrast and circle shape from week 3 challenge so I don’t forget the notions I’ve learned.</description></item><item><title>Stress</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-4-43e3/</guid><description>View on External Website.
Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Game.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I thought I could finish this within 2 days (including learning + execution), ended up having to scrap a lot of the ideas due to my lack of knowledge and sleep deprivation. (definitely not my proudest project, bad coding ethics, cutting corners)
https://jumpingbeans.itch.io/week4 (&amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; aka shitpost download page)
Media:
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Joker</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-4-e553/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-4-e553/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes SO, I started a concept on stream, I wasn’t happy with it, and then continued working on it until it became completely different (other than being P5 related). So now I’m here, 4 hours later, with a different piece. I love the use of silhouettes in P5 and it just clicked with me to do something related to it for this submission!</description></item><item><title>Orange jump</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-4-6b80/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Krita with mouse.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 **Title: Orange jump ** Medium: Krita with mouse Description: Chose orange, quickly doodled a jumping person, decided to make some kind of parkour picture.</description></item><item><title>beach 🙂</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-4-1ce3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-4-1ce3/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Photo and Adobe Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes this image was captured a few years ago on the southwest coast, at sunset as the sky cleared after a storm. it was already near monochrome, but i dropped the exposure to play with the value a bit edit: this came out a bit dim in discord yikes
nah 🙂
Social Media N/A.</description></item></channel></rss>