<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jorchael_p on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jorchael_p/</link><description>Recent content in jorchael_p on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jorchael_p/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Out of Touch Tuesday</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-8-5f75/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I saw the swirl of the image and straight away wanted to do something kind of surreal but still quick and readable. I won&amp;rsquo;t lie, this probably took a bit over the 2 hour time limit, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really have a brainstorming session so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna count it as a work hour. Also I got the day wrong but shhh that adds to the out of touch-ness.</description></item><item><title>Nian Gao, old and new</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-6-92bc/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes For this years cny my mom shared some old memories of her grandma making nian gao and having mom man the steamer for hours until it was done. We then made some ourselves as a way of passing on a tradition I never knew we had. My mom doesn&amp;rsquo;t normally share fond memories of her childhood so this felt like something worth commemorating.</description></item><item><title>'0</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-3-292d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-3-292d/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to draw so I drew something horny, sorry. She sure has a lot of red circles tho.
@/jorchaelp on twitter and @/jrchlp.png on insta
Social Media Instagram: jrchlp.png Twitter: jorchaelp Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: :&amp;#39;0 Medium: Photoshop Description: Didn&amp;#39;t know what to draw so I drew something horny, sorry.</description></item><item><title>Ah, Bright Light</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-2-3cec/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes At the end of a long twisty cavern a diver finds a little rabbit shrimp thing! How cute and not at all dangerous.
I wanted to design a creature for this week and accidentally made a kaiju looking thing. Space wise I think I messed up translating how deep the ocean is but we can pretend I wanted it to come accross as claustrophobic.</description></item><item><title>sunny day, pouring rain</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-1-81a6/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to try play with the rain patterns but rushed them a little. References are godsend. I was going for a minimal editorial look and limited pallette because those are outside of my comfort zone.
Social Media Instagram: jrchlp.png Twitter: jorchaelp Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer.</description></item></channel></rss>