<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dylan on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/dylan/</link><description>Recent content in Dylan on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/artists/dylan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloudy Night</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-11-d4a7/</guid><description> Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 11 Title: Cloudy Night Medium: Photoshop Description: I usually draw night scenes all the time so this time I tried adding some more colours then your basic black and white added some purple and blue clouds and a heart</description></item><item><title>Desert heat</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-7-384d/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: blender.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i wanted to try a new something new so instead of photoshop i used blender this is my first time using the program and i think it came out pretty good i dont really have a but i hope I did a ok job 😊
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Behind The Doors</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/dylan-week-5-7bf8/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Digital (PhotoShop).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I wanted to make something that has a backstory so basically i had a friend that loved ninjas and they passed away a few years back so i wanted to do something not just for me but for them so i used the green (jade) as a representation of harmony/peace i hope you like it 😊</description></item></channel></rss>