<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Week 17: The 4 R's: Finale on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-17-the-4-rs-finale/</link><description>Recent content in Week 17: The 4 R's: Finale on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/themes/week-17-the-4-rs-finale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Farewell Glance</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-17-93bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/lithium-week-17-93bc/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A glance back at the months of creation, experimentation, and learning. Style inspired on &amp;ldquo;upon sunflowers&amp;rdquo; by Charmandaar from week one! Just really liked the simple lines and two-color aspect.
IG/tumblr lithiumreflections, twitter lireflections
Social Media Instagram: lithiumreflections Tumblr: lithiumreflections Twitter: jaimeskelton Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>Footprints</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-17-9d88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-17-9d88/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clipstudio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
Alternative title - I had an idea, but I suck at timing
So you all remember @papapastry&amp;rsquo;s week 7 song? Well I was do, and I was gonna do a cover, but instead I made a cover&amp;hellip; still plan to make a cover
Also, I am still learning clipstudio (Pumpka, I blame you entirely) So the actual piece: I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about that damn red panda since week 7!</description></item><item><title>Hatsune Miku plays the hits feat. Kagamine Rin</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-17-a86b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jorchael_p-week-17-a86b/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes A big ol' wheres waldo of past submissions! I&amp;rsquo;m super late so I&amp;rsquo;ll probs tag the appropriate tags later. Design Refresh has really been an exercise in time management lmao. Inspired by @papapastry week 3 entry! And everyone else, its been a wild ride. (Also ngl this is very unfinished lmao)
medias:</description></item><item><title>I AM LITERAL SPED</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-17-fcd6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/eggyolk-week-17-fcd6/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Didn&amp;rsquo;t really reuse any pieces, moreso a reflection piece now that everything&amp;rsquo;s coming to an end. This challenge has honestly made me pump out more work than I have in the last&amp;hellip;.decade LOL, and it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been possible without everyone who participated, inspiring each other. YOU ALL INSPIRE ME. YEAH YOU LIKE THAT CHEESE?</description></item><item><title>Mandrake Reflecting</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/winsome-week-17-8612/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photography.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @arren&amp;rsquo;s Week 1 submission &amp;ldquo;Sparkly Mandrake&amp;rdquo; (FiveClawd External Link ) This was one of the first pieces I saw when watching design refresh and it really captured my attention. I utilised my own Mandrake model from Week 7 (FiveClawd External Link ). I tried to capture a video of it to replicate the glitter of the original gif, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t look very good.</description></item><item><title>Shorts</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-7ac3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-7ac3/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 10/11 Suite, Steinberg Cubase 5, FL Studio 12/20, &amp;amp; DaVinci Resolve.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Hey team, this 8-minute video would do best when left to last. Thanks!
Submission 5/5.
I took a work from every week (without repeats of artists) and wrote 30 second shorts for each one. Most of these shorts are from work that I wrote in the past that has not seen the light of day.</description></item><item><title>Untitled</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/arancil-week-17-911a/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: various traditional.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Images in the imgur link: Imgur External Link It&amp;rsquo;s been fun. Thanks everyone participating. Seeing everyone&amp;rsquo;s work in this showcase format week by week has been a really great way to share art with each other, inspire, motivate, develop and helping me and others appreciate more things about the work people do as we&amp;rsquo;re enabled to get into closer detail on the what, how &amp;amp; why in regards to the art people do.</description></item><item><title>[Title Too Long]</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-17-4a75/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mrop2000-week-17-4a75/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: unknown medium.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
I chose to base this week&amp;rsquo;s drawing on a1ewanrichards&amp;rsquo;s work. The subjects, the markers, the honesty of the strokes really amazes me.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: So this week I am not submitting anything really, but I did draw something based on the prompt (attached image is more proof than anything else).</description></item><item><title>Amalgamation: Ewan's Summer - Season's End</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-17-eeb3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/a1ewanrichards-week-17-eeb3/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio Paint, Adobe Photoshop, and E-portfolio (Flip Book made on https://fliphtml5.com/ ).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes [REVISED, REUPLOAD] This is my own refresh/summary of my past works, with in-depth elaboration for each work. Each entry is lengthy, so for the sake of the actual showcase, please read the foreword and the Week 17 instead, especially the finale where I wrote something special, hopefully.</description></item><item><title>fruit that isn't fruit</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-17-8df0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/hamishmr-week-17-8df0/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: keeb.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes shutuphamish (twitch)
for a while i didn&amp;rsquo;t have an idea for the final refresh, but i knew i wanted to enter. i missed (a lot) more showcases than i wanted to at the start and only entered twice before this (and really only one good entry) but i&amp;rsquo;ve been here the whole time, watching vods and enjoying the submissions!</description></item><item><title>Inspiration</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-17-cbc8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/mimichair-week-17-cbc8/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Toon Boom Harmony.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I am late but still on time for the showcase Thanks to all the deadline extensions I was still able to make the morphing gif idea I had for this!
Because I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to draw anything dedicated for Designrefresh at all I decided to do all of them at once on the final week.</description></item><item><title>Keep It Simple</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-17-1b83/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/cindry-week-17-1b83/</guid><description>Direct link to a .pdf file.Direct link to a .pdf file.
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Publication with InDesign.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I made a zine that is basically a doodling book where I included previous submissions to serve as inspiration. Thought this would be a fun thing that people can print off themselves and keep as a sketch book to fill out as something to do after the project is over.</description></item><item><title>Lonely Light</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-342b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-342b/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 11 Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 3/5.
Preamble:
I planned to do a colossal anthology of pieces, week after week, each with different artists to create a storyline and a concept EP in addition to the five pieces of work I actually did for the final week of the refresh. The planning document I have for that clocks in at just under 2,000 words, uses art from 16 artists, and is a coming-of-age story about an immortal wizard.</description></item><item><title>Medley</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-95b8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-95b8/</guid><description>View on SoundCloud. Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Ableton Live 11 Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes If time is a factor, please skip this for the showcase!
Submission 4/5.
A throwback to all of my audio pieces (all 17 of them!) over the design refresh.
YT: YouTube External Link SC: SoundCloud External Link Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>MUSE</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-17-7c5e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/soleilboo-week-17-7c5e/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Photoshop/ digital painting/ cover album.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So this is it! This is finale of 17 weeks of Designrefesh! I participated in this awesome community since week 5 and haven’t dropped a single prompt! I’m proud of myself for this commitment. Thank you @cindry for hosting and everyone who helping and participating! You all inspired me to stick to this all along.</description></item><item><title>Peace is Dynamism</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/pumpkan-week-17-3356/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Digital, Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I took inspiration from @a1ewanrichards &amp;ldquo;When the land becomes graveyards&amp;rdquo; (FiveClawd External Link ) I loved this piece because it tapped into a vivid memory of playing soccer opposite sugarcane fields, watching them slowly disintegrate into flames and having the ash gently fall on us as we practiced. Life felt like it was so vividly coloured back then.</description></item><item><title>Re:dux</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-093b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-093b/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Since I had more time than I initially thought, I decided to add a little more to the piece! I don&amp;rsquo;t think I need to say more than I initially wrote in the original piece but I hope you enjoy the Directors Extended Cut of the piece haha
Social Media Instagram: paintsepsi Twitch: paintsepsi Twitter: paintsepsi Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>wittle whale</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-17-05c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/goblet-week-17-05c2/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: wood, knife.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Week: 17
liked the whale from the deep sea week (2). Inspired by bright sea by arren. Made from spalted birch
Social Media Twitch: cup_o_rice Twitter: cup_o_rice Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: wittle whale Medium: wood, knife Description: liked the whale from the deep sea week (2).</description></item><item><title>Part of Your World</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/bell-bones-week-17-b157/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: FireAlpaca.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Waaaa, week 17,,, it&amp;rsquo;s here,, and I actually come with a piece of quality (thanks to the extensions lmao). This piece was inspired by @Linalifox&amp;rsquo;s submission for week 4, titled &amp;ldquo;Blue&amp;rdquo;. Their piece reminded me of mermaids, which reminded me of The Little Mermaid and my merman AU that I have for Backey,,, so I drew him and took the pose from the &amp;ldquo;Part of Your World&amp;rdquo; scene in The Little Mermaid.</description></item><item><title>End of a Chapter</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-17-3f12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/titan011-week-17-3f12/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Clip Studio.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Nothing fancy for the last week of the design refresh 2021 as I want to take this time to praise all the wonderful artists that submitted their art. It was only a few month ago that a picked up my first drawing tablet and started digital art (I was so scared to even use colors 🤣 ).</description></item><item><title>#2021DesignRefresh Portfolio</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/vectorong-week-17-85ff/</guid><description>The image above leads to an external website. Please be careful!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: E-portfolio (flipbook made on https://fliphtml5.com ).
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I find it&amp;rsquo;s always nice to look back whenever you complete a series / project and celebrate, so this is my way of doing so - creating a book with all the pieces I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted. I&amp;rsquo;ve really enjoyed this challenge and trying all these new mediums, even when I felt like my brain might explode.</description></item><item><title>Re:create</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-ac8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/paintsepsi-week-17-ac8e/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Procreate.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes wowwww, another side profile of an anime girl, how creative of me&amp;hellip;. I tried to incorporate some of my previous works in this piece&amp;hellip; Week 1 - with the yellow background, Week 3 - Red Circle with the red earrings, Week 4 - Murky silhouette with the persona style art, Week 8 - high sheen from jimmy neutron, Week 9 - the devil girl that I drew, Week 10 - Folds and folds and the anime style.</description></item><item><title>things you use to look at yourself with (the musical/remix)</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-a37a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-a37a/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Whatever beans used + Ableton Live 11 Suite.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 2/5.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist. Thanks to @jumpingbeans for the script and visuals.
I used a guitar with a steel slide, a special piano that uses one string per key (originally created by David Klavins), and Balinese Gamelan instruments.
YouTube External Link Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub .</description></item><item><title>refresh.fiveclawd.com</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-09eb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/papapastry-week-17-09eb/</guid><description>Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: Go + Hugo, Python..
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Submission 1/5.
Yeah, this totally counts.
No need to showcase it, I just wanted to pad my stats. Five submissions!
FiveClawd External Link Social Media Twitch: papapastry Twitter: papapastry_ Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: **Week**: 17 **Title:** refresh.</description></item><item><title>ThankEgg</title><link>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh21.fiveclawd.com/blog/jumpingbeans-week-17-5412/</guid><description>The above is an MP4 video link. Please click it to view the video!
Week 17: The 4 R&amp;rsquo;s: Finale. This art was lovingly created using: video.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes ive ran out of ideas and time
; YouTube External Link ;
Social Media Instagram: jumpingbeansz Twitch: jumpingbeansz Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 17 Title: ThankEgg Medium: video Description: ive ran out of ideas and time Social Media: https://www.</description></item></channel></rss>