<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DynoLoafer on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/dynoloafer/</link><description>Recent content in DynoLoafer on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/dynoloafer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The ~~Diving~~ Maternal Legendary</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-16-e690/</guid><description>Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes (a small TW for alcohol and drug abuse) I decided to draw not my most favorite pokemon for this week, but the pokemon I respect* the most. Lugia&amp;rsquo;s past is quite depressing. The creator of Lugia, Takeshi Shudo, heavily relied on alcohol, pills and even *tranquilizers* to get his mind in the workspace, which sadly isn&amp;rsquo;t an uncommon practice with creators.</description></item><item><title>Red Delicious with a Red Delicious</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-15-4f6d/</guid><description>Week 15: Back to Basics. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Whoopsies, I&amp;rsquo;m late again! Oh well, school finals are happening right now and, particularly in math (I&amp;rsquo;m a grade ahead of my peers in it) homework likes to pile up. But, even if I&amp;rsquo;m late, I know that this would&amp;rsquo;ve came out really bad if I rushed it, so I took my time and.</description></item><item><title>My Protective Assistant</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-14-dd61/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I was late, sad. &amp;lt;:CattoCry:800558786418835477&amp;gt; Buut I got this done tho! I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved whenever I got the change to draw fire and fire effects. Again, I actually learned a technique on youtube on how to do this, and I think it works out really well for my style! This is dragon Backey (I know they&amp;rsquo;re also cowboys, please don&amp;rsquo;t ask how many alternate universes we have) attacking a rowdy dragon who got too aggro with Prince Astro!</description></item><item><title>P̷̑̚Ä̴́̅I̴͒̚N̷̈͠F̵̳̂Ű̷͓L̵̛͝ ̶̓̏B̷̈́̔L̴̅̂Ī̶̈́S̵̓̾S̷̐̐</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-13-77c7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-13-77c7/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes bright colors, just as a warning &amp;ldquo;AST̶̉̽Ŕ̴̊O̷͑͑, ASTRO! P̷̦͠L̸͋̒Ẽ̷̙A̶̓̔S̵̓̉É̶̅!̴̏̾ ̷̀̂B̶̐̚L̸͑̍I̸̺̓N̷͗̾K̵͌̾ ̴̕͝A̷͗̚T̶̂͌ ̴̐̓M̶̐̀E̵̍́!̵̄̌ WHAT HAPPENED? W̶̟̉H̶̒͗Ÿ̵́͂ ̶̘̇D̶̽͜I̴̛̓D̴̯̂ ̸̈́̂T̷̀͊H̵̋̓Í̶͙S̶̍̆ ̴̅͆Ḧ̵́APPEN?! NO! WAKE UP WAKE UP!!&amp;rdquo; (Don&amp;rsquo;t bother trying to read that if you struggle lmao) I got this piece in, yay! More crazy eyes and insight into the story lol. If only this were an April Fools so Astro could go &amp;ldquo;It was just a prank, bro!</description></item><item><title>Crazy Bird</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-12-6b6a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-12-6b6a/</guid><description>Week 12: Visual Words. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I made it after all, sweet! Anyways, I decided to use a sharp type of typography I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the past to help emphasize the power in this picture. Yes this is the gay cowboys (I draw them both as humans and as people.) No spoilers for part 2, (part 1 is finished) but someone is struck by a smooth criminal.</description></item><item><title>They Come Out at Night</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-11-ff87/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Getting into dragons again more than I usually do, so I decided to draw some dragon silhouette&amp;rsquo;s against a pretty night sky! I learned an easy trick to making galaxy/night sky patterns awhile back, so I put that to use in the top part of the screen! I like how this came out, even if it&amp;rsquo;s more simple because I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy and tired with the new time change.</description></item><item><title>Pico's Target</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-10-1d26/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol' Pico from Pico&amp;rsquo;s School and Friday Night Funkin'. He&amp;rsquo;s a good edgy boy.
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 10 Medium: Paint Tool SAI Title: __Pico&amp;#39;s Target__ Description: Not too much behind this lol, just wanted to draw some fanart for good ol&amp;#39; Pico from Pico&amp;#39;s School and Friday Night Funkin&amp;#39;.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Collage</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-9-09aa/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Wow I&amp;rsquo;m the first one submitting this week? That&amp;rsquo;s weird. Anyways, I decided for this week to draw a bunch of dragons because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t decide on just one with all the thumbnails I made! Each piece has it&amp;rsquo;s own title, as well as a color palette of only 10 colors (9 not including black) and wow it makes this bright!</description></item><item><title>Pretty, Ain't It?</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-8-03c2/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes &amp;ldquo;Someone had a mighty fine belt-buckle, so I.. borrowed it.&amp;rdquo; This was a very interesting challenge! Decided to go for a painting-like piece with the belt-buckle being the main focus! If it&amp;rsquo;s hard to see, the texture from the resource is on the belt buckle! I timed myself and I had 7 minutes before the two hour mark!</description></item><item><title>The Sandstorm</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-7-8d7b/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TW FOR &amp;ldquo;BLOOD&amp;rdquo; (just in case) This sandstorm is fogging up my judgement. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see you. I can&amp;rsquo;t even see my goddamn hand out in front of me&amp;hellip; Please. Don&amp;rsquo;t blame yourself, none of this is your fault. I was the one who killed them, can&amp;rsquo;t you see the blood?</description></item><item><title>Slice of Life</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-6-f33c/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Cutting close again, wowie! Oh well, I like how this came out even if it&amp;rsquo;s just a few doodles of me and my best friend! She&amp;rsquo;s the light of my life and I love her with all my heart, she makes me so incredibly happy and has probably indirectly saved my life.</description></item><item><title>Not My Forte</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-5-e0bc/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Dragon shown (Astro): &amp;ldquo;Erhm&amp;hellip; are you sure all of this jade jewelry is considered attractive? There&amp;rsquo;s so many piercings&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; Dragon offscreen (Backey): &amp;ldquo;Of course, your Highness! People will swoon for you and your glittery glory.&amp;rdquo; Astro: &amp;ldquo;How do you know?&amp;rdquo; Backey: &amp;ldquo;Uhm.. your Highness, word gets around eheh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; (sweating) &amp;hellip;Got this done without stress, yay!</description></item><item><title>You Ain't No Bounty Hunter</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-4-b341/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Desc: Whew, this one was close! Sucks that I had to kinda rush at the end because this was submitted on a school night, but I think it still came out really well! I hope his expression scares you because it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to lol. The only story I&amp;rsquo;ll give is something/someone hurt his boyfriend pretty badly and he&amp;rsquo;s not happy about it.</description></item><item><title>Blood Moon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-3-ee54/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/dynoloafer-week-3-ee54/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Paint Tool SAI.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes _
Desc: First week where I did stuff, hah! I hope I can start to follow the weeks more now that I exist here. You might recognize the character on the left, and if you do, then you&amp;rsquo;ll know who my friend is lol. These two boyos have a lot of story put into them, and I know a lot more about the Wild West than the average person might suspect.</description></item></channel></rss>