<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TrixyNetex on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/trixynetex/</link><description>Recent content in TrixyNetex on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/trixynetex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ozymandias</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-16-31cb/</guid><description>View on Webtoons.
Week 16: Scaling Giants. This art was lovingly created using: Clip studio paint.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes So this is an idea have had since week 7, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to pull it off and also had too many ideas for that week. However I honestly think it fits with this week&amp;rsquo;s theme better 😛 So this is based off the poem &amp;ldquo;Ozymandias&amp;rdquo; by Percy Bysshe Shelley.</description></item><item><title>Flames of Phlegethos</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-14-6ff8/</guid><description>Week 14: Absolute Fire. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Let&amp;rsquo;s draw another one of my D&amp;amp;D characters, because dang it! Why not!? Met Athenaeum; tiefling lore bard/warlock and general wielder of hell fire. So fun fact, when I started digital art about a year ago one of my first pieces was of Ath doing neato flame shit. Thought I&amp;rsquo;d revisit the concept with this one.</description></item><item><title>Fake Animu Screenshot</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-13-b7c6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-13-b7c6/</guid><description>Week 13: Look At Me. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook pro &amp;amp; paint.net.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Super last minute submission, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss two weeks in a row! So you know when you have a plan, but then you realise you did not give yourself enough time?
&amp;hellip;yeah that was me 😅
Originally was gonna have like 3 or 4 fake screenshots. But time is a cruel mistress.</description></item><item><title>Liminal Sky</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-11-ca4c/</guid><description>Week 11: Atmosphere Spectrum. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I love the sky at dusk, a storm looming on the horizon. The brilliant colours doomed to a few moments before the sky grows dark and the rain begins. That liminal space where you just look at the sky in awe.
Trying to get better at digital painting. Think I got the vibe at least 😊</description></item><item><title>Sunset Vibes, aka it was 30° degrees today</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-10-b389/</guid><description>Week 10: Folds and Folds. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes GUESS WHOES FIVECLAWD MERCH ARRIVED TODAY!!!! #notsponseredjustexcited Thought I&amp;rsquo;d draw last week&amp;rsquo;s CMYK Dragon jacket and pair it with the Perseverance shirt cause who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want double dragons? Bit of a quick one today cause running out of time. Yes, I did use a photo of my shirt for the shirt. No, I am not copy Cindy&amp;rsquo;s dragoon by hand, how much time do you think I have!</description></item><item><title>Chromatic Dragon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-9-d8ff/</guid><description>Week 9: Bold Strokes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This is what happens when I stare at Hydro74&amp;rsquo;s work for long enough&amp;hellip; Something very different for me, but I really love how this turned out! A CMYK Dragon, just for you Cindy 😘 Technically based of the Black Dragons from D&amp;amp;D cause I&amp;rsquo;m a nerd. Enjoy!
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>The Herald</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-8-f626/</guid><description>Week 8: High Sheen. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes TWO HOURS! incoherent eldritch screeching Firstly: WHY!!! Secondly: I would like the record to show that I did in fact completely this piece within the two hours (brainstorming included)
So for this I figured we&amp;rsquo;d go back to &amp;ldquo;basics&amp;rdquo; and hop on board the spoopy train. Since the og pics were from a church, I started thinking along the line of angels, creepy angels&amp;hellip; then got inspired by Peter Mohrbacher&amp;rsquo;s angel paintings and ended up with a Dark Souls boss 🤷‍♀️</description></item><item><title>SOL 0</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-7-f8df/</guid><description>Week 7: Disturbed Desert. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes This morning the Perseverance Rover landed safely in the Jezero Crater on Mars. It&amp;rsquo;s NASA&amp;rsquo;s fifth Rover to land on the red planet and, other than Curiosity, is the only thing &amp;lsquo;alive&amp;rsquo; on the dusty world.
Art wise, a bit of a quick and dirty one. (Was starting to run out of time 😅) I used the 3D model viewer of Perseverance to get the rover as accurate as possible.</description></item><item><title>Midnight Magic Musings</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-6-af98/</guid><description>Week 6: Simple Love. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The late nights we stay up talking about D&amp;amp;D. Those quiet moments when the rest of the world is asleep. We bounce dumb ideas off each other just to see where they&amp;rsquo;ll land. You have no idea how much I appreciate my Resident Wizard&amp;hellip;
On the art side of things; I really enjoy drawing characters and their interactions, and believe it or not, I do like drawing cute things 😛</description></item><item><title>Flawless</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-5-f539/</guid><description>Week 5: Royal Green. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes Firstly; if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of &amp;ldquo;Kintsugi&amp;rdquo; before, you&amp;rsquo;re welcome 😛 Secondly, rendering jade is a mood&amp;hellip; cheers for that This one took me a hot minute, but I think I&amp;rsquo;m starting to get the hang of digital painting somewhat 😅
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>The Search</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-4-4be9/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes The Search
Murky, silhouette&amp;hellip; well, I must oblige! (It&amp;rsquo;s like you want me to draw spoopy shit) 😛 Decided to contrast this with my last two pieces by using mainly lighter values. And since we&amp;rsquo;re looking at movement, thought I&amp;rsquo;d try and pump in some more overt narrative stuff too. Enjoy!
Social Media N/A.</description></item><item><title>Summon</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-3-efde/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-3-efde/</guid><description> Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: Sketchbook Pro.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes I heard something about &amp;lsquo;expand beyond the circle&amp;rsquo; and next thing you know we&amp;rsquo;re summoning entities from another reality 😛
Media:
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 **Title: Summon ** Medium: Sketchbook Pro Description: I heard something about &amp;#39;expand beyond the circle&amp;#39; and next thing you know we&amp;#39;re summoning entities from another reality 😛 Social Media:</description></item><item><title>Engulf</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/trixynetex-week-2-f7ac/</guid><description>Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: SketchBook.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread! Trying to up my digital art skills as well. Enjoy 😛
Media:
Social Media N/A. Other Edit this page on GitHub. Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: Engulf Medium: SketchBook Description: You give me the prompt of Deep Ocean, of course I have to draw some existential dread!</description></item></channel></rss>