<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jc on 2021 Design Refresh</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jc/</link><description>Recent content in jc on 2021 Design Refresh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/artists/jc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>costume change</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-4-1490/</guid><description>Week 4: Murky Silhouettes. This art was lovingly created using: csp!.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i saw &amp;lsquo;state of change&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;movement&amp;rsquo; and that was it for me! i forgot it was monochromatic entirely oops
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 4 Title: costume change Medium: csp!</description></item><item><title>am i coming outta left field</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-3-c968/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-3-c968/</guid><description>Week 3: Red Circle. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes i have a really involved animatic in my head set to rebel just for kicks. i will complete it One Day. here&amp;rsquo;s a gal from it
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 3 Title: am i coming outta left field Medium: csp Description: i have a really involved animatic in my head set to rebel just for kicks.</description></item><item><title>oarfish</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-2-86d7/</guid><description> Week 2: Deep Ocean. This art was lovingly created using: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;rsquo;s been living in my mind rent free for years
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 2 Title: oarfish Medium: csp &amp;amp; lasso tool Description: oarfish swim vertically and that&amp;#39;s been living in my mind rent free for years Social Media: @/rybaris on twitter and insta</description></item><item><title>egg galaxy</title><link>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://refresh.fiveclawd.com/blog/jc-week-1-c31f/</guid><description>Week 1: Yellow Lines. This art was lovingly created using: csp.
Artist&amp;rsquo;s Notes a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow! with some stars.
Social Media Instagram: rybaris Tumblr: rybaris Twitter: rybaris Other Edit this page on GitHub . Create a bug ticket for the developer. Parsed source from Discord is as follows: Week: 1 Title: egg galaxy Medium: csp Description: a girl drawn in contrasting linework in all yellow!</description></item></channel></rss>